<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<wpiedata>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Chef Swap At The Beach' Season Three to Premiere on August 17]]></title>
    <date><![CDATA[2024-07-26 9:25:00]]></date>
    <content><![CDATA[<div>
<p><strong>Myrtle Beach, S.C. (July 22, 2024)</strong> &mdash; Visit Myrtle Beach is excited to announce that &ldquo;Chef Swap at The Beach&rdquo; is back for a captivating third season this summer. Showcasing the incredible culinary talent throughout the Grand Strand, the new season of &ldquo;Chef Swap at The Beach&rdquo; premieres Saturday, Aug. 17 at 7 p.m. EDT on the Cooking Channel. Season three features an all-new lineup of 16 skilled and innovative chefs from the Myrtle Beach area across seven captivating episodes that will air weekly on Saturdays.</p>

<p>&ldquo;Bringing viewers another season of &lsquo;Chef Swap at the Beach&rsquo; is a testament to the vibrant culinary scene that continues to flourish throughout the Myrtle Beach area,&rdquo; said Stuart Butler, Chief Marketing Officer, Visit Myrtle Beach. &ldquo;This season highlights yet another batch of our world-class chefs, their elevated menus featuring rich, farm-to-table and sea-to-table ingredients and the diverse array of flavors they bring to the area. Building on the success of the first two seasons, this third season will further showcase the passion and support our community has for the local culinary scene.&rdquo;</p>

<p>Chef Mason Zeglen, two-time winner of Food Network&rsquo;s &ldquo;Guy&rsquo;s Grocery Games,&rdquo; previous contestant on HBO Max&rsquo;s &ldquo;The Big Brunch&rdquo; and owner of Milk &amp; Honey Coffee Caf&eacute; in Surfside Beach, S.C., will reprise his role as the show&rsquo;s host. Each fast-paced episode will feature two regional chefs who will swap kitchens and prepare a new dish for evaluation by veteran judges and industry experts Dylan Foster and Johanna Wilson Jones. The finale episode, an hour-long special, will feature students from the International Culinary Institute alongside local chef mentors, adding an exciting new twist to the show.</p>

<p>&ldquo;Throughout season one and two, the sheer talent on the show was nothing short of spectacular. I am genuinely honored to return and continue showcasing Myrtle Beach&rsquo;s incredible chefs,&rdquo; said Zeglen. &ldquo;This season is not just about the competition&mdash;it&rsquo;s about the incredible stories of the diverse, passionate and dedicated chefs who truly fuel our community.&rdquo;</p>

<p>The 16 distinguished chefs competing this season represent the diverse culinary scene of the area, from the North and South Strands to West of the Waterway and the heart of downtown Myrtle Beach. This season&rsquo;s chefs are:</p>
</div>

<div>
<ul>
<li>Kenny Adams, <a href="https://www.playwildwing.com/dining-catering/">Wild Wing Golf Course</a></li>
<li>Aquib Ahmed, <a href="https://bombayatthebeach.com/">Bombay at the Beach</a></li>
<li>Ivan Almeida,<a href="https://whiskeyrootsbar.com/"> Whiskey Roots </a></li>
<li>Sundy Barth, <a href="https://www.hgtc.edu/academics/academic-departments/culinary-institute/index.html">International Culinary Institute</a></li>
<li>Steve Brown, <a href="https://thebrentwoodrestaurant.com/">The Brentwood</a></li>
<li>Lauren Clever, <a href="https://thebougiefoodiemb.com/">Bougie Foodie</a></li>
<li>Jef Cornelison, <a href="https://hotfishclub.com/">Hot Fish Club</a></li>
<li>Kamal Fraser, <a href="https://caribbeanjerkfood.com/">Caribbean Jerk</a></li>
<li>Martin Graham, <a href="https://pinelakes.com/">Pine Lakes Country Club</a></li>
<li>Steve Hock, <a href="https://hippiehen.co/">Hippie Henhouse</a></li>
<li>Billy Horner, <a href="https://www.rustictable.com/">Rustic Table</a></li>
<li>Ricky Lang, <a href="https://gringoninja.com/">Gringo Ninja </a></li>
<li>Paul Kelly Renault, <a href="https://chiveblossom.com/">Chive Blossom</a></li>
<li>Jason Trinh, <a href="https://www.jem-social.com/">JEM Social </a></li>
<li>Charles Unger, <a href="https://www.hgtc.edu/academics/academic-departments/culinary-institute/index.html">International Culinary Institute</a></li>
<li>Richard Ward, <a href="https://www.visitmyrtlebeach.com/listings/ritchies-general-store-eatery">Ritchie&#39;s General Store &amp; Eatery</a></li>
</ul>
</div>

<p>For more on &ldquo;Chef Swap at the Beach,&rdquo; including behind-the-scenes photos, featured restaurants, chef tips and more on the Myrtle Beach area&rsquo;s culinary scene, visit <a href="http://www.chefswap.com">ChefSwap.com</a> and follow on <a href="https://www.facebook.com/chefswapshow">Facebook</a> (@chefswapshow), <a href="https://www.instagram.com/chefswapshow">Instagram</a> (@chefswapshow) and <a href="https://www.tiktok.com/@chefswapshow">TikTok</a> (@chefswapshow).</p>

<p><strong>Streaming options: </strong>Fans of the show can catch up on the excitement of season 1 and 2, which are available for streaming on <a href="http://chefswap.com">ChefSwap.com</a>, <a href="https://trybinge.tv/programs/beach-easy">Binge TV</a> and <a href="https://www.visittheusa.com/gousa-tv">GoUSA TV</a>.</p>

<hr />
<p><strong>About Myrtle Beach, S.C.</strong></p>

<p>Myrtle Beach isn&rsquo;t just a beach. It&rsquo;s The Beach. Popularly known as the Grand Strand, Myrtle Beach is one destination made up of 14 unique communities that stretch 60 miles along the northeast coast of South Carolina. Families, couples, and those in search of a warm welcome will find more than just a day at The Beach when they come together to connect and enjoy vibrant entertainment and family attractions, including world-class golf, shopping and fresh coastal Carolina cuisine. From the moment you arrive, you&rsquo;ll find you belong at The Beach &ndash; Myrtle Beach, South Carolina. For additional information on tourism offerings in the Myrtle Beach area, visit <a href="http://www.visitmyrtlebeach.com">www.visitmyrtlebeach.com</a> or call (888) Myrtle-1.</p>

<p><strong>About The WorkShop Content Studios:</strong></p>

<p>Formed in 2007 The WorkShop Content Studios has grown to become a prominent, vertically integrated company serving clients from the creative development stages of a project through final production. The company has had great success in structuring compelling stories and bringing them to life on the screen for platforms and networks ranging from Amazon, Netflix, PBS and TLC to name a few. In addition to working with the major television networks the company&rsquo;s productions span virtually all of today&rsquo;s established and emerging platforms &ndash; ranging from linear to digital - with the goal being to entertain, inform and inspire the largest audience possible.</p>

<hr />
<p><strong>Editor&rsquo;s Note:</strong> Visual assets and further information available to download <a href="https://visitmyrtlebeach.box.com/s/xuvmxut4cy6wd1uftb1digjxexmrn54m">HERE </a>(Credit: Visit Myrtle Beach).</p>

<p><strong>Media Contact:</strong><br />
Kimberly Miles<br />
Fahlgren Mortine<br />
843.655.7902<br />
mbteam@fahlgren.com&nbsp;</p>
]]></content>
    <teaser_image_url><![CDATA[https://www.myrtlebeachareachamber.com/img/cache/blog/BlogPosts/700/teaser_image/34836-590-394f-4d22ac6ad028bf35f2a8ff07772b1b94]]></teaser_image_url>
    <teaser_image_alt_text/>
    <categories><![CDATA[News]]></categories>
    <author/>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Keep Myrtle Beach Beautiful Seeks Volunteers for Back-To-School Roadside Cleanup on August 15]]></title>
    <date><![CDATA[2024-07-23 9:39:00]]></date>
    <content><![CDATA[<p>MYRTLE BEACH, S.C.&mdash;To help welcome teachers, staff, students and parents back to school, Keep Myrtle Beach Beautiful is planning a special roadside cleanup near Doug Shaw Memorial Stadium, the recreation center and surrounding areas on Thursday, Aug. 15, 2024, from 8 to 11 a.m.</p>

<p>Volunteers are asked to park near the Doug Shaw Stadium or at the recreation center and check in at the Keep Myrtle Beach Beautiful booth at 32nd Ave. North and Oak St. near the Pepper Geddings Recreation Center.</p>

<p>Trash bags, gloves, vests and easy-reach grabbers will be provided and school supply donations such as pencils, crayons, glue, and notebooks will be collected.</p>

<p>Visit the events calendar on <a href="http://www.KeepMyrtleBeachBeautiful.com">KeepMyrtleBeachBeautiful.com</a> for further details.</p>

<hr />
<p><strong>Editor&rsquo;s Note:</strong> <a href="https://drive.google.com/drive/folders/1zxH6ZANikPFo-vQNdkUgixgSSaHVpEiV?usp=share_link">Press Images</a></p>

<p><strong>About Keep Myrtle Beach Beautiful</strong></p>

<p>Keep Myrtle Beach Beautiful, a program of the Myrtle Beach Area Chamber of Commerce, is an official affiliate of Palmetto Pride, Keep South Carolina Beautiful and Keep America Beautiful. The program focuses on three pillars: litter removal, recycling and beautification. Keep Myrtle Beach Beautiful aims to bring together the City of Myrtle Beach, community organizations and residents under one umbrella to focus on various efforts to keep Myrtle Beach clean and green. <a href="http://www.KeepMyrtleBeachBeautiful.com">KeepMyrtleBeachBeautiful.com</a></p>
]]></content>
    <teaser_image_url><![CDATA[https://www.myrtlebeachareachamber.com/img/cache/blog/BlogPosts/701/teaser_image/34836-590-394f-4d22ac6ad028bf35f2a8ff07772b1b94]]></teaser_image_url>
    <teaser_image_alt_text/>
    <categories><![CDATA[Keep Myrtle Beach Beautiful]]></categories>
    <author/>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[New Department of Labor Ruling]]></title>
    <date><![CDATA[2024-07-17 9:17:00]]></date>
    <content><![CDATA[<p>New overtime rules are now in place for salaried positions following updated regulations from the U.S. Dept. of Labor (DOL) which took effect July 1.</p>

<p>The rule, which falls under the Fair Labor and Standards Act (FLSA), raises the minimum salary threshold for employees to be considered exempt from receiving overtime. To qualify as exempt, employees must be paid on a salary basis, be paid at least the minimum salary level, and have primarily executive, administrative or professional duties.</p>

<p>Previously, the minimum salary level was $35,568 annually, or $684 per week. Now, the threshold is $43,888 annually or $844 per week.</p>

<p>The threshold will rise again Jan. 1, 2025, with a new minimum salary level of $58,656 per year or $1,128 per week.</p>

<p>The DOL rule also increased standards for &ldquo;Highly Compensated Employees&rdquo; or HCEs a from a minimum of $107,432 to $132,964 as of July 1 and increasing to $151,164 on Jan. 1, 2025.</p>

<p>The new regulations have impacted an estimated 1 million employees and will impact 3 million after the new year.&nbsp;</p>

<p>Multiple lawsuits have been brought against the DOL by opponents to rule. A federal judge in Texas granted the state a temporary pause for certain workers employed by the state. Elsewhere, the new rule is in full effect, while litigation remains pending. This means employers must increase pay for workers to be considered exempt from overtime pay or begin paying overtime for workers who work more than 40 hours per week.&nbsp;</p>

<p>Learn more about the rule by visiting dol.gov.</p>

<p>&nbsp;</p>
]]></content>
    <teaser_image_url><![CDATA[https://www.myrtlebeachareachamber.com/img/cache/blog/BlogPosts/699/teaser_image/34836-590-394f-4d22ac6ad028bf35f2a8ff07772b1b94]]></teaser_image_url>
    <teaser_image_alt_text/>
    <categories><![CDATA[News]]></categories>
    <author><![CDATA[by Jada Hudson, Public Policy Coordinator]]></author>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Horry County Home Consortium Competitive Application for Homeowner and TBRA Projects Is Now Open]]></title>
    <date><![CDATA[2024-07-16 14:02:00]]></date>
    <content><![CDATA[<p>The Horry County HOME Consortium is seeking applications from developers, non-profits, local governments, and Community Housing Development Organizations (CHDOs) for eligible HOME Investment Partnerships Program (HOME) homeowner and tenant based rental assistance projects.&nbsp;</p>

<p>HOME funds may be used to develop affordable homeownership housing through the acquisition, new construction, reconstruction, or rehabilitation of affordable housing.&nbsp;Activities may include acquisition of single family housing for homeownership, new construction, rehabilitation, reconstruction, conversion, and other expenses including financing costs and temporary relocation expenses of any households, businesses, or organizations. HOME funds may also be used to provide tenant based rental assistance, a rental subsidy that serves to fill the funding gap between what a household is able to pay towards rent and the fair market rent for a housing unit.</p>

<p>The deadline for submission of applications is August 12, 2024 at 5 p.m.</p>

<p>Additionally, applications for CHDO certification and CHDO operating assistance are available for qualifying organizations with a CHDO-eligible project submission. Applications and reference documentation are also available at: <a data-auth="Verified" data-linkindex="2" href="https://nam12.safelinks.protection.outlook.com/?url=https%3A%2F%2Fdn54hf4ab.cc.rs6.net%2Ftn.jsp%3Ff%3D001_3_NmbudJmDhJzqQJ5c9ngwo5jAUuF8Epb99TEyfLjvhY8Kw06lxfkBXu_-AxRYrQ2nPRjv5fyHqUYgH9i9in-dpkHDArxT_k6y-o1CdqK3raITBEeKDw7rYa7Ev2-josWGB4nyCXiPotYD8cLw5taf0Oa1PngCQwhuWGESfsojAHqTwGyZ_Plb3WY5ofLkV_18tGI7qYkkEbIDbLUK4gUKMI4PNxIqXhGs2gMdeyKE%3D%26c%3DrWI6hx34VaviyeCyp4Rw3zSTK6L_Fj5tjDhKd6UMD9d3pkwFQBTtqA%3D%3D%26ch%3DVcFgAuBQKiUWqo8pZgW2ENYmAp9PCcrqI3js-w3bWN96S7-x26Dh_g%3D%3D&amp;data=05%7C02%7Cfaith.schmeizl%40visitmyrtlebeach.com%7C0ee4185663584217770608dca4ce940b%7C81d417a4e3dd45fc965205e902b9d96e%7C0%7C0%7C638566454370385295%7CUnknown%7CTWFpbGZsb3d8eyJWIjoiMC4wLjAwMDAiLCJQIjoiV2luMzIiLCJBTiI6Ik1haWwiLCJXVCI6Mn0%3D%7C0%7C%7C%7C&amp;sdata=w2qA8O%2FBeucvhS%2F1WKYAMEytFQu3LRpN64DPHWs8gZ8%3D&amp;reserved=0" title="Original URL: https://dn54hf4ab.cc.rs6.net/tn.jsp?f=001_3_NmbudJmDhJzqQJ5c9ngwo5jAUuF8Epb99TEyfLjvhY8Kw06lxfkBXu_-AxRYrQ2nPRjv5fyHqUYgH9i9in-dpkHDArxT_k6y-o1CdqK3raITBEeKDw7rYa7Ev2-josWGB4nyCXiPotYD8cLw5taf0Oa1PngCQwhuWGESfsojAHqTwGyZ_Plb3WY5ofLkV_18tGI7q">horrycountysc.gov/departments/community-development/public-notices/</a>. For more information on HOME Program eligibility and requirements, please visit the <a data-auth="Verified" data-linkindex="3" href="https://nam12.safelinks.protection.outlook.com/?url=https%3A%2F%2Fdn54hf4ab.cc.rs6.net%2Ftn.jsp%3Ff%3D001_3_NmbudJmDhJzqQJ5c9ngwo5jAUuF8Epb99TEyfLjvhY8Kw06lxfl_jR-2esQilrOgx7OJdwlWfDOZiASW3jjBnhxuGEygIWdmRoqxl5-AGyfArfFknGotY6gGp-X9dOmbymZChxdAa_xb2NWyH6aGTqm__vq372ufnoSNzmsqvuLI1kH3ExY6xG6erILMt0OzJ8zTtVF2vsLcYN_Z1zQ%3D%3D%26c%3DrWI6hx34VaviyeCyp4Rw3zSTK6L_Fj5tjDhKd6UMD9d3pkwFQBTtqA%3D%3D%26ch%3DVcFgAuBQKiUWqo8pZgW2ENYmAp9PCcrqI3js-w3bWN96S7-x26Dh_g%3D%3D&amp;data=05%7C02%7Cfaith.schmeizl%40visitmyrtlebeach.com%7C0ee4185663584217770608dca4ce940b%7C81d417a4e3dd45fc965205e902b9d96e%7C0%7C0%7C638566454370399170%7CUnknown%7CTWFpbGZsb3d8eyJWIjoiMC4wLjAwMDAiLCJQIjoiV2luMzIiLCJBTiI6Ik1haWwiLCJXVCI6Mn0%3D%7C0%7C%7C%7C&amp;sdata=W4rGB6ilJBEeg80VG0vTDyUbbGQPAS%2FcWZI2RhgCStY%3D&amp;reserved=0" title="Original URL: https://dn54hf4ab.cc.rs6.net/tn.jsp?f=001_3_NmbudJmDhJzqQJ5c9ngwo5jAUuF8Epb99TEyfLjvhY8Kw06lxfl_jR-2esQilrOgx7OJdwlWfDOZiASW3jjBnhxuGEygIWdmRoqxl5-AGyfArfFknGotY6gGp-X9dOmbymZChxdAa_xb2NWyH6aGTqm__vq372ufnoSNzmsqvuLI1kH3ExY6xG6erILMt0OzJ8zTt">Community Development Webpage</a>&nbsp;or visit the <a data-auth="Verified" data-linkindex="4" href="https://nam12.safelinks.protection.outlook.com/?url=https%3A%2F%2Fdn54hf4ab.cc.rs6.net%2Ftn.jsp%3Ff%3D001_3_NmbudJmDhJzqQJ5c9ngwo5jAUuF8Epb99TEyfLjvhY8Kw06lxfgUiFhlIuf7tP_lD1sUx59JPQoQF5QHGNblZWCuFgxuCSp0-RNx93LYSEUN7siDMXYyAS0Bl-8uHxZPeVsvbCe8acNSiUQsGfW0_m1NRtg44%26c%3DrWI6hx34VaviyeCyp4Rw3zSTK6L_Fj5tjDhKd6UMD9d3pkwFQBTtqA%3D%3D%26ch%3DVcFgAuBQKiUWqo8pZgW2ENYmAp9PCcrqI3js-w3bWN96S7-x26Dh_g%3D%3D&amp;data=05%7C02%7Cfaith.schmeizl%40visitmyrtlebeach.com%7C0ee4185663584217770608dca4ce940b%7C81d417a4e3dd45fc965205e902b9d96e%7C0%7C0%7C638566454370409179%7CUnknown%7CTWFpbGZsb3d8eyJWIjoiMC4wLjAwMDAiLCJQIjoiV2luMzIiLCJBTiI6Ik1haWwiLCJXVCI6Mn0%3D%7C0%7C%7C%7C&amp;sdata=Dz8Hg9tu%2FWHD5%2F0uRC%2FSojzSNnboH8zUgoi1XCCz1MI%3D&amp;reserved=0" title="Original URL: https://dn54hf4ab.cc.rs6.net/tn.jsp?f=001_3_NmbudJmDhJzqQJ5c9ngwo5jAUuF8Epb99TEyfLjvhY8Kw06lxfgUiFhlIuf7tP_lD1sUx59JPQoQF5QHGNblZWCuFgxuCSp0-RNx93LYSEUN7siDMXYyAS0Bl-8uHxZPeVsvbCe8acNSiUQsGfW0_m1NRtg44&amp;c=rWI6hx34VaviyeCyp4Rw3zSTK6L_Fj5tjDhKd">HUD Exchange</a>.&nbsp;</p>
]]></content>
    <teaser_image_url><![CDATA[https://www.myrtlebeachareachamber.com/img/cache/blog/BlogPosts/698/teaser_image/34836-590-394f-4d22ac6ad028bf35f2a8ff07772b1b94]]></teaser_image_url>
    <teaser_image_alt_text/>
    <categories><![CDATA[News]]></categories>
    <author/>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Myrtle Beach Area Chamber Welcomes Four Summer Interns]]></title>
    <date><![CDATA[2024-07-15 14:28:00]]></date>
    <content><![CDATA[<p>MYRTLE BEACH, S.C.&mdash; The Myrtle Beach Area Chamber of Commerce (MBACC) and Convention and Visitors Bureau (CVB) is excited to announce the addition of four talented interns to its team for summer 2024.</p>

<p>Kaylee Alston, Bryce Graham, Raevyn Ramsey and Faith Schmeizl have joined the organization for a four-month internship program focused on equipping them with hands-on professional skills related to chamber and CVB operations such as marketing and communications, event planning and more.</p>

<p>Alston is a senior at Coastal Carolina University seeking a degree in marketing. She is an intern in the CVB&rsquo;s marketing department, assisting with various tourism marketing campaigns.</p>

<p>Graham is a sophomore at the University of South Carolina pursuing a double major in management and marketing. He is working alongside Alston in the marketing department helping to promote tourism.</p>

<p>Ramsey is a returning intern, assisting the group sales department for the second summer. She graduated from Clemson University in May with a bachelor of science in environmental and natural resources with a concentration in economic policy.</p>

<p>Schmeizl is working as a content creator in the chamber&rsquo;s business development department where she is writing blogs, taking photos and videos, and assisting with website updates. She&rsquo;s a senior at Bryant University in Rhode Island pursuing a degree in digital marketing.</p>

<p>&ldquo;We are thrilled to welcome Kaylee, Bryce, Raevyn and Faith to our team this summer,&rdquo; said Matt Metzger, vice president of human resources and operations. &ldquo;Each brings their own unique skills and perspectives that will help us achieve our goals and better serve our community. We look forward to seeing the positive impact they will make during their time with us.&rdquo;</p>

<p>For more information about the chamber and CVB, visit <a href="https://nam12.safelinks.protection.outlook.com/?url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.myrtlebeachareachamber.com%2F&amp;data=05%7C02%7Cfaith.schmeizl%40visitmyrtlebeach.com%7C280a356a1a19427f5e3708dca277a070%7C81d417a4e3dd45fc965205e902b9d96e%7C0%7C0%7C638563882022220898%7CUnknown%7CTWFpbGZsb3d8eyJWIjoiMC4wLjAwMDAiLCJQIjoiV2luMzIiLCJBTiI6Ik1haWwiLCJXVCI6Mn0%3D%7C0%7C%7C%7C&amp;sdata=um72jSMJEdFzn3dzngUZHvG9%2BBRK2NXPhs0rLELXR%2F8%3D&amp;reserved=0">MyrtleBeachAreaChamber.com</a>.</p>

<hr />
<p>&nbsp;</p>

<p><a name="_Hlk78886154">About Myrtle Beach Area Chamber of Commerce and Convention and Visitors Bureau:</a></p>

<p>Since 1938, the Myrtle Beach Area Chamber of Commerce (MBACC) has stood as the unified voice of the Grand Strand&#39;s business community &mdash; serving Myrtle Beach, North Myrtle Beach, Little River, Loris, Atlantic Beach, Carolina Forest, Conway, Aynor, Socastee, Surfside Beach, Garden City Beach, Murrells Inlet, Litchfield Beach and Pawleys Island. The U.S. Chamber of Commerce has awarded MBACC its five-star accreditation &mdash; one of only a few chambers in South Carolina to earn this distinction. The Myrtle Beach Area Convention and Visitors Bureau (CVB) and its destination marketing arm Visit Myrtle Beach promote tourism through various partnerships and initiatives to advance the economic success of the Grand Strand. For more information, visit <a href="file:///C:/Users/marlane.white/Desktop/PRESS%20RELEASES/DRAFT%20RELEASES/MyrtleBeachAreaChamber.com">MyrtleBeachAreaChamber.com</a>, <a href="https://nam12.safelinks.protection.outlook.com/?url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.myrtlebeachareacvb.com%2F&amp;data=05%7C02%7Cfaith.schmeizl%40visitmyrtlebeach.com%7C280a356a1a19427f5e3708dca277a070%7C81d417a4e3dd45fc965205e902b9d96e%7C0%7C0%7C638563882022233001%7CUnknown%7CTWFpbGZsb3d8eyJWIjoiMC4wLjAwMDAiLCJQIjoiV2luMzIiLCJBTiI6Ik1haWwiLCJXVCI6Mn0%3D%7C0%7C%7C%7C&amp;sdata=wGDdtHUqxDefinp%2FpfxWBtRpVaiov7RV43rjs%2Fm8MRg%3D&amp;reserved=0">MyrtleBeachAreaCVB.com</a> and <a href="https://nam12.safelinks.protection.outlook.com/?url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.visitmyrtlebeach.com%2F&amp;data=05%7C02%7Cfaith.schmeizl%40visitmyrtlebeach.com%7C280a356a1a19427f5e3708dca277a070%7C81d417a4e3dd45fc965205e902b9d96e%7C0%7C0%7C638563882022241106%7CUnknown%7CTWFpbGZsb3d8eyJWIjoiMC4wLjAwMDAiLCJQIjoiV2luMzIiLCJBTiI6Ik1haWwiLCJXVCI6Mn0%3D%7C0%7C%7C%7C&amp;sdata=vJEmgyWjLONQa9KKsLB9KXeHO9CPdUhffMgLSU1TKbE%3D&amp;reserved=0">VisitMyrtleBeach.com</a>.</p>
]]></content>
    <teaser_image_url><![CDATA[https://www.myrtlebeachareachamber.com/img/cache/blog/BlogPosts/697/teaser_image/34836-590-394f-4d22ac6ad028bf35f2a8ff07772b1b94]]></teaser_image_url>
    <teaser_image_alt_text/>
    <categories><![CDATA[News]]></categories>
    <author><![CDATA[by Faith Schmeizl, MBACC Intern]]></author>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Winers of the Minority-Owned Business Contest]]></title>
    <date><![CDATA[2024-07-15 13:26:00]]></date>
    <content><![CDATA[<p>Five minority-owned businesses were awarded membership to Myrtle Beach Area Chamber of Commerce through a partnership with TD Bank.</p>

<p>This is the third year the chamber and TD Bank held the contest during the month of May as part of celebrations for National Small Business Week and continues the chamber&rsquo;s efforts to support and engage minorities in business in the Myrtle Beach area.</p>

<p>TD Bank is sponsoring the cost of one year&rsquo;s dues for five businesses owned by people from a marginalized or underrepresented demographic. The winning businesses and their employees have full access to all benefits of chamber membership including a listing in the business directory, free job listings on our Job Board, discounts through our money-saving programs and invitations to networking events and education classes.</p>

<p>The winning businesses, who were drawn at random, are: Smokin Wit Grace Cigars LLC, Hannah&rsquo;s Nails, Hug a Mug Caf&eacute;, Out of the Ark Educational Animal Shows, and Rices Powerwash.</p>

<p>&ldquo;TD Bank is committed to helping create a more inclusive future for those who live and work in the communities we serve, and we understand how important small businesses are to our local and national economy,&rdquo; said Ryan Spagnolo, relationship manager for TD Bank. &ldquo;We are proud to collaborate with the chamber and provide this opportunity to these five minority-owned businesses in the greater Grand Strand. We look forward to seeing the continued success of the local businesses and supporting them as they grow.&rdquo;</p>

<p>Of the business owners who applied, 31 qualified and five were selected at random on June 4, and notified no later than June 15. The MBACC board of directors finalized their membership on June 27.&nbsp;</p>

<p>Qualifications for the contest required the business be 51 percent or more owned by a minority, marginalized or underrepresented demographic such as: Black or African American, Hispanic, Native American, Asian-Pacific, Subcontinent Asian, woman, veteran, LGBTQ, or disabled person. In addition, the business must be located in Horry or Georgetown counties, legally operating for at least one month and cannot be current investors with the chamber.&nbsp;</p>

<p><strong>LEARN MORE ABOUT THE WINNERS</strong></p>

<p><strong>Smokin wit Grace Cigars llc</strong> is an African American family-owned business operating in all of Horry County and surrounding areas. The Mobile Cigar Lounge brings the cigars to you, without the mess and stress. The service provides a lounge with a built-in humidor, providing a luxurious retreat at your own private event or wedding!</p>

<p><strong>Hannah&rsquo;s Nails</strong> is an Asian owned nail business that provides services for everything nails. They are experts and can provide everything ranging from simple manicures and pedicures to polygel sets and fills. You can make an appointment online, and find them located at 4773 Dick Pond Rd, Myrtle Beach.</p>

<p><strong>Hug a Mug Caf&eacute;</strong> is a coffee shop that is located at 1626 Highway 17 S., North Myrtle Beach, while also providing service at local markets. The caf&eacute; offers drinks from coffee and tea to smoothies, and wraps and desserts to snack on! There is space for local artists to showcase their work as well! Hug a Mug Caf&eacute; also has a truck that travels to local markets! As an LGBTQ+ owned business everyone is welcomed here!</p>

<p><strong>Out of the Ark Educational Animal Shows</strong> provides a fun experience while also being educational. It is a LGBTQ+ and veteran owned company that wants to ensure safety with this hands-on interactive presentation of wildlife. From school events, birthday parties, or craft events, and everything in between, the Out of the Ark Educational Animal Shows will bring the animals to you!</p>

<p><strong>Rices Powerwash</strong> is owned by Paul Rice, who provides power washing services for what is needed! Services are available for individuals in both commercial and residential housing.</p>
]]></content>
    <teaser_image_url><![CDATA[https://www.myrtlebeachareachamber.com/img/cache/blog/BlogPosts/696/teaser_image/34836-590-394f-4d22ac6ad028bf35f2a8ff07772b1b94]]></teaser_image_url>
    <teaser_image_alt_text/>
    <categories><![CDATA[News]]></categories>
    <author/>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Tips to Recognize and Avoid Hackers]]></title>
    <date><![CDATA[2024-07-11 11:30:00]]></date>
    <content><![CDATA[<p>We welcomed Ryan Foultz to Chamber Academy on June 25 to help us gain expertise in understanding attackers&rsquo; methods like malware, phishing and hacking, and how to defend against them. Ryan is the founder of PcRx Computers and has more than 20 years experience in the IT industry. He has been serving local businesses since 2007 and is native to the Conway area. He wrote the book &ldquo;Welcome To The Jungle&rdquo;- a book about cybersecurity, and presented some of the information to us.&nbsp;</p>

<p>74% of organizations in the US have fallen victim to successful phishing attacks, ranging from business email compromise to ransomware. Here are practical steps you can take to identify and avoid potential hackers:</p>

<h3>Learn to recognize phishing attempts</h3>

<p>Be wary of emails impersonating trusted contacts containing suspicious links and watch out for emails demanding immediate payments or urging you to &ldquo;click here.&rdquo;</p>

<p>Phishing has great bait- Phishing emails often create urgency or seem highly believable. Take an extra minute or two to verify unexpected emails and verify authenticity before acting. Instead of clicking links directly, copy and paste them into your browser. Lastly, consult with colleagues to see if they received a similar email.</p>

<h3>Avoid using free Wi-Fi</h3>

<p>Public Wi-Fi networks often advertised as &ldquo;free&rdquo; doesn&rsquo;t always mean free. Hackers can intercept your information through these &ldquo;free&rdquo; Wi-Fi networks. Consider using your phone as a personal hotspot when you&rsquo;re on the go.</p>

<h3>Implement Two-Factor Authentication (2FA)</h3>

<p>An additional layer of verification makes it significantly harder for hackers to gain unauthorized access to company information. The most common method of verification is via SMS, or text message. Other methods include an authenticator app, hardware token, or fingerprint scanners,</p>

<p>By adopting these proactive measures, you can significantly reduce the risk of falling victim to cyberattacks and protect both personal and organizational information.</p>
]]></content>
    <teaser_image_url><![CDATA[https://www.myrtlebeachareachamber.com/img/cache/blog/BlogPosts/695/teaser_image/34836-590-394f-4d22ac6ad028bf35f2a8ff07772b1b94]]></teaser_image_url>
    <teaser_image_alt_text/>
    <categories><![CDATA[News]]></categories>
    <author><![CDATA[by Faith Schmeizl, MBACC Intern]]></author>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[The PGA Tour's Myrtle Beach Classic is set for May 8-11 in 2025]]></title>
    <date><![CDATA[2024-07-09 9:20:00]]></date>
    <content><![CDATA[<p>Myrtle Beach, S.C. (July 8, 2024) &ndash; The PGA TOUR&rsquo;S Myrtle Beach Classic will again be played in early May in 2025, with the competition dates set for May 8-11 at the Dunes Golf and Beach Club. Chris Gotterup won the inaugural Classic in 2024, which was the first PGA TOUR event to be held along the Grand Strand.</p>

<p>&ldquo;Year one exceeded our expectations, and the community is eager to see what is in store for year two,&rdquo; said Darren Nelson, tournament director, who shared the scheduled dates for 2025. &ldquo;With the backing of our title sponsor Visit Myrtle Beach and the support from our business community and public, Myrtle Beach has proven to be a great home for a PGA TOUR event in just one year.&rdquo;</p>

<p>The first-year event drew more than 40,000 fans, and delivered some memorable golf moments, along with the additional entertainment of two free concerts, corporate hospitality options, and a public Fan Zone. It also received rave reviews from the professional golfers.</p>

<p>Thorbjorn Olesen, who set a course record with his 10-under-par 61 on Sunday over the 7,347-yard layout to move into a tie for 16th place, said, &ldquo;I didn&#39;t really know what to expect. I&rsquo;ve never been here before. I think the golf course is great. I think there&#39;s a lot of demanding tee shots out there. I feel like you have to be on your game.&rdquo;</p>

<p>And Robert MacIntyre, who shared the first-round lead with a 7-under 64 before finishing tied for 13th, praised the event. &ldquo;It&#39;s unbelievable. It&#39;s a great track. I didn&#39;t know what to expect, but this is top drawer,&rdquo; said MacIntyre, who went on to claim his first PGA TOUR victory a month later at the RBC Canadian Open. &ldquo;The greens are absolutely perfect.&rdquo;</p>

<p>The Dunes Club layout will not change for 2025, but players may anticipate a golf course that will be a bit more challenging, without any major changes.</p>

<p>&ldquo;The players can expect that the golf course will be very similar to last year,&rdquo; said Steve Hamilton, director of agronomy at the Dunes Club. &ldquo;There won&rsquo;t be any major changes for 2025. This golf course now can be as challenging as the TOUR wants to set it up. I think you&rsquo;ll see that the rough will be a little taller. It was at two inches this year. Maybe we will get it as high as three inches next year, depending on the weather.&rdquo;</p>

<p>The winner of the Myrtle Beach Classic is again expected to earn a spot into the PGA Championship field, which will be contested at Quail Hollow Club in Charlotte, N.C., from May 15-18, 2025.</p>

<p>The Myrtle Beach Classic is managed by SPORTFIVE, a global event management company. The local event was one of two stops in the Palmetto State for the PGA TOUR in 2024, joining with the RBC Heritage in April at Harbour Town Golf Links.</p>

<hr />
<p><strong>About Myrtle Beach Classic</strong></p>

<p>The Myrtle Beach Classic, a dual-field PGA TOUR event hosting 132 players, will be played May 8-11, 2025, at Dunes Golf and Beach Club in Myrtle Beach, S.C., commonly known as the &ldquo;Golf Capital of the World.&rdquo; Updated information on the 2025 event can be found at myrtlebeachclassic.com. &nbsp;</p>

<p><strong>About PGA TOUR</strong></p>

<p>By showcasing golf&rsquo;s greatest players, the PGA TOUR engages, inspires and positively impacts our fans, partners and communities worldwide.<br />
<br />
The PGA TOUR, headquartered in Ponte Vedra Beach, Florida, co-sanctions tournaments on the PGA TOUR, PGA TOUR Champions, Korn Ferry Tour, PGA TOUR Americas and administers PGA TOUR Q-School presented by Korn Ferry and PGA TOUR University. TOUR members represent the world&rsquo;s best players, hailing from 28 countries and territories. Showcasing the biggest moments in the sport with history and legacy on the line, the PGA TOUR has long-term domestic distribution partnerships for broadcast coverage on CBS, NBC and Golf Channel and video streaming service on ESPN+. Internationally, PGA TOUR coverage is available across 200+ countries and territories in 28 languages via 44 broadcast and digital partners. Virtually all tournaments are organized as non-profit organizations to maximize charitable giving, and to date, tournaments across all Tours have generated almost $4 billion.<br />
<br />
Fans can follow the PGA TOUR on the new PGA TOUR app and PGATOUR.COM, and on social media channels, including&nbsp;<a href="https://nam12.safelinks.protection.outlook.com/?url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.facebook.com%2FPGATour%2F&amp;data=05%7C02%7Cmarlane.white%40visitmyrtlebeach.com%7Cad9ebd62b6294c3f1ed108dc1dd7a569%7C81d417a4e3dd45fc965205e902b9d96e%7C0%7C0%7C638418059226683805%7CUnknown%7CTWFpbGZsb3d8eyJWIjoiMC4wLjAwMDAiLCJQIjoiV2luMzIiLCJBTiI6Ik1haWwiLCJXVCI6Mn0%3D%7C3000%7C%7C%7C&amp;sdata=IwNdqptqg6nVSQybL93f1grwxJ3rwBylOpL7e6PIAfI%3D&amp;reserved=0" target="_blank" title="https://www.facebook.com/pgatour/">Facebook</a>, <a href="https://nam12.safelinks.protection.outlook.com/?url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.instagram.com%2Fpgatour%2F&amp;data=05%7C02%7Cmarlane.white%40visitmyrtlebeach.com%7Cad9ebd62b6294c3f1ed108dc1dd7a569%7C81d417a4e3dd45fc965205e902b9d96e%7C0%7C0%7C638418059226690590%7CUnknown%7CTWFpbGZsb3d8eyJWIjoiMC4wLjAwMDAiLCJQIjoiV2luMzIiLCJBTiI6Ik1haWwiLCJXVCI6Mn0%3D%7C3000%7C%7C%7C&amp;sdata=JKR4MqvHSeg0c403DkNDFVKhGG1QKHv0X5h30BnHJEc%3D&amp;reserved=0">Instagram</a> (in&nbsp;<a href="https://nam12.safelinks.protection.outlook.com/?url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.instagram.com%2Fpgatouresp%2F&amp;data=05%7C02%7Cmarlane.white%40visitmyrtlebeach.com%7Cad9ebd62b6294c3f1ed108dc1dd7a569%7C81d417a4e3dd45fc965205e902b9d96e%7C0%7C0%7C638418059226697240%7CUnknown%7CTWFpbGZsb3d8eyJWIjoiMC4wLjAwMDAiLCJQIjoiV2luMzIiLCJBTiI6Ik1haWwiLCJXVCI6Mn0%3D%7C3000%7C%7C%7C&amp;sdata=cUO4%2Bu3srt3ZKr8xWyO02%2Fb5ot5yyvDc6FFhYJuTYz0%3D&amp;reserved=0" target="_blank" title="https://www.instagram.com/pgatouresp/">Spanish</a>, <a href="https://nam12.safelinks.protection.outlook.com/?url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.instagram.com%2Fpgatour_korea%2F&amp;data=05%7C02%7Cmarlane.white%40visitmyrtlebeach.com%7Cad9ebd62b6294c3f1ed108dc1dd7a569%7C81d417a4e3dd45fc965205e902b9d96e%7C0%7C0%7C638418059226703799%7CUnknown%7CTWFpbGZsb3d8eyJWIjoiMC4wLjAwMDAiLCJQIjoiV2luMzIiLCJBTiI6Ik1haWwiLCJXVCI6Mn0%3D%7C3000%7C%7C%7C&amp;sdata=P4LY%2F4NrfsuEhPR5DST89APSCcMm4wsdK7vZiGivlq4%3D&amp;reserved=0" target="_blank" title="https://www.instagram.com/pgatour_korea/">Korean</a> and <a href="https://nam12.safelinks.protection.outlook.com/?url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.instagram.com%2Fpgatour_japan%2F%3Fhl%3Den&amp;data=05%7C02%7Cmarlane.white%40visitmyrtlebeach.com%7Cad9ebd62b6294c3f1ed108dc1dd7a569%7C81d417a4e3dd45fc965205e902b9d96e%7C0%7C0%7C638418059226710278%7CUnknown%7CTWFpbGZsb3d8eyJWIjoiMC4wLjAwMDAiLCJQIjoiV2luMzIiLCJBTiI6Ik1haWwiLCJXVCI6Mn0%3D%7C3000%7C%7C%7C&amp;sdata=H8Q0FtUzr8VN0ioL3h8pMA%2Bd5L8SJJffFBrQX6qSsF4%3D&amp;reserved=0">Japanese</a>), <a href="https://nam12.safelinks.protection.outlook.com/?url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.linkedin.com%2Fcompany%2Fpga-tour%2F&amp;data=05%7C02%7Cmarlane.white%40visitmyrtlebeach.com%7Cad9ebd62b6294c3f1ed108dc1dd7a569%7C81d417a4e3dd45fc965205e902b9d96e%7C0%7C0%7C638418059226716751%7CUnknown%7CTWFpbGZsb3d8eyJWIjoiMC4wLjAwMDAiLCJQIjoiV2luMzIiLCJBTiI6Ik1haWwiLCJXVCI6Mn0%3D%7C3000%7C%7C%7C&amp;sdata=rGol5AlFyTUDcJzl8YPKl0HDwHLGv1IDYVEDhIkof%2FI%3D&amp;reserved=0" target="_blank" title="https://www.linkedin.com/company/pga-tour/">LinkedIn</a>, <a href="https://nam12.safelinks.protection.outlook.com/?url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.tiktok.com%2F%40pgatour%3Flang%3Den&amp;data=05%7C02%7Cmarlane.white%40visitmyrtlebeach.com%7Cad9ebd62b6294c3f1ed108dc1dd7a569%7C81d417a4e3dd45fc965205e902b9d96e%7C0%7C0%7C638418059226723357%7CUnknown%7CTWFpbGZsb3d8eyJWIjoiMC4wLjAwMDAiLCJQIjoiV2luMzIiLCJBTiI6Ik1haWwiLCJXVCI6Mn0%3D%7C3000%7C%7C%7C&amp;sdata=Lu8ur5hn8M8J%2FdHBHc6GuxVCJb6mCNA9ehrD25CB6HY%3D&amp;reserved=0">TikTok</a>, X (in <a href="https://nam12.safelinks.protection.outlook.com/?url=https%3A%2F%2Ftwitter.com%2FPGATOUR&amp;data=05%7C02%7Cmarlane.white%40visitmyrtlebeach.com%7Cad9ebd62b6294c3f1ed108dc1dd7a569%7C81d417a4e3dd45fc965205e902b9d96e%7C0%7C0%7C638418059226730104%7CUnknown%7CTWFpbGZsb3d8eyJWIjoiMC4wLjAwMDAiLCJQIjoiV2luMzIiLCJBTiI6Ik1haWwiLCJXVCI6Mn0%3D%7C3000%7C%7C%7C&amp;sdata=shFZa9vZYQlmOdT3QalZXJ4lNx9DMhf6X4OznFOebOg%3D&amp;reserved=0">English</a> and <a href="https://nam12.safelinks.protection.outlook.com/?url=https%3A%2F%2Ftwitter.com%2Fpgatouresp&amp;data=05%7C02%7Cmarlane.white%40visitmyrtlebeach.com%7Cad9ebd62b6294c3f1ed108dc1dd7a569%7C81d417a4e3dd45fc965205e902b9d96e%7C0%7C0%7C638418059226737116%7CUnknown%7CTWFpbGZsb3d8eyJWIjoiMC4wLjAwMDAiLCJQIjoiV2luMzIiLCJBTiI6Ik1haWwiLCJXVCI6Mn0%3D%7C3000%7C%7C%7C&amp;sdata=oBeUy%2B2IShzWeAZVwox1qevHqKPF5c2UXWC1AOekWss%3D&amp;reserved=0">Spanish</a>),&nbsp;WhatsApp (in <a href="https://nam12.safelinks.protection.outlook.com/?url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.whatsapp.com%2Fchannel%2F0029Va3nJw68KMqrNum9CW3Q&amp;data=05%7C02%7Cmarlane.white%40visitmyrtlebeach.com%7Cad9ebd62b6294c3f1ed108dc1dd7a569%7C81d417a4e3dd45fc965205e902b9d96e%7C0%7C0%7C638418059226743704%7CUnknown%7CTWFpbGZsb3d8eyJWIjoiMC4wLjAwMDAiLCJQIjoiV2luMzIiLCJBTiI6Ik1haWwiLCJXVCI6Mn0%3D%7C3000%7C%7C%7C&amp;sdata=AN6812kw62riO3bUmedQmzksDUwNqkKCUQ3cuxEXcP0%3D&amp;reserved=0">English</a> and <a href="https://nam12.safelinks.protection.outlook.com/?url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.whatsapp.com%2Fchannel%2F0029VZzjq2e0bIdmjyKUtD1A&amp;data=05%7C02%7Cmarlane.white%40visitmyrtlebeach.com%7Cad9ebd62b6294c3f1ed108dc1dd7a569%7C81d417a4e3dd45fc965205e902b9d96e%7C0%7C0%7C638418059226750259%7CUnknown%7CTWFpbGZsb3d8eyJWIjoiMC4wLjAwMDAiLCJQIjoiV2luMzIiLCJBTiI6Ik1haWwiLCJXVCI6Mn0%3D%7C3000%7C%7C%7C&amp;sdata=u%2FIS371muvsyWcNonDkYSVPYZ7%2BLqjGhEKJkaGB6dbc%3D&amp;reserved=0">Spanish</a>),&nbsp; <a href="https://nam12.safelinks.protection.outlook.com/?url=https%3A%2F%2Fmp.weixin.qq.com%2Fs%3F__biz%3DMjM5NjMwNTMzMw%3D%3D%26mid%3D2651657457%26idx%3D1%26sn%3D88a9d97dee9fd0eb350b328ace823b4e%26chksm%3Dbd12f42b8a657d3d178461a3b1ed1b6698922bb3fcc1c16020dbf44f42f8cf9abac7563e56ef%26mpshare%3D1%26scene%3D1%26srcid%3D%26sharer_sharetime%3D1580779531250%26sharer_shareid%3D058f3b4488554c4e4fcb906fcc49755f%26exportkey%3DAZTD9L7Uprn8iaYs%252BoP6uXw%253D%26pass_ticket%3DFHFQxidNP2QmVAL93G8XgSDIz9a89Mw62Q22VcSKgwg83N9QQqpVQ%252BzVoUDxtSU1%23rd&amp;data=05%7C02%7Cmarlane.white%40visitmyrtlebeach.com%7Cad9ebd62b6294c3f1ed108dc1dd7a569%7C81d417a4e3dd45fc965205e902b9d96e%7C0%7C0%7C638418059226756861%7CUnknown%7CTWFpbGZsb3d8eyJWIjoiMC4wLjAwMDAiLCJQIjoiV2luMzIiLCJBTiI6Ik1haWwiLCJXVCI6Mn0%3D%7C3000%7C%7C%7C&amp;sdata=OHbp6ZZ7R1Xk43kOuWwV6PaGy1jxvNOwO6BTTFeU%2FeQ%3D&amp;reserved=0" target="_blank" title="https://mp.weixin.qq.com/s?__biz=MjM5NjMwNTMzMw==&amp;mid=2651657457&amp;idx=1&amp;sn=88a9d97dee9fd0eb350b328ace823b4e&amp;chksm=bd12f42b8a657d3d178461a3b1ed1b6698922bb3fcc1c16020dbf44f42f8cf9abac7563e56ef&amp;mpshare=1&amp;scene=1&amp;srcid=&amp;sharer_sharetime=1580779531250&amp;sharer_sh">WeChat</a>,&nbsp;<a href="https://nam12.safelinks.protection.outlook.com/?url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.weibo.com%2Fpgatour&amp;data=05%7C02%7Cmarlane.white%40visitmyrtlebeach.com%7Cad9ebd62b6294c3f1ed108dc1dd7a569%7C81d417a4e3dd45fc965205e902b9d96e%7C0%7C0%7C638418059226765607%7CUnknown%7CTWFpbGZsb3d8eyJWIjoiMC4wLjAwMDAiLCJQIjoiV2luMzIiLCJBTiI6Ik1haWwiLCJXVCI6Mn0%3D%7C3000%7C%7C%7C&amp;sdata=971DlAFNFaKowX3npD8%2FrFKCVXoARefmwucqLyXvMjI%3D&amp;reserved=0" target="_blank" title="https://www.weibo.com/pgatour">Weibo</a>,&nbsp;<a href="https://nam12.safelinks.protection.outlook.com/?url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.toutiao.com%2Fc%2Fuser%2F6301181466%2F%23mid%3D6310584897&amp;data=05%7C02%7Cmarlane.white%40visitmyrtlebeach.com%7Cad9ebd62b6294c3f1ed108dc1dd7a569%7C81d417a4e3dd45fc965205e902b9d96e%7C0%7C0%7C638418059226774078%7CUnknown%7CTWFpbGZsb3d8eyJWIjoiMC4wLjAwMDAiLCJQIjoiV2luMzIiLCJBTiI6Ik1haWwiLCJXVCI6Mn0%3D%7C3000%7C%7C%7C&amp;sdata=k1zC1752QeLmMTufp5WNpCYa1FkqCtwep%2F%2FkTAttvYk%3D&amp;reserved=0" target="_blank" title="https://www.toutiao.com/c/user/6301181466/#mid=6310584897">Toutiao</a>,&nbsp;<a href="https://nam12.safelinks.protection.outlook.com/?url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.douyin.com%2F&amp;data=05%7C02%7Cmarlane.white%40visitmyrtlebeach.com%7Cad9ebd62b6294c3f1ed108dc1dd7a569%7C81d417a4e3dd45fc965205e902b9d96e%7C0%7C0%7C638418059226782522%7CUnknown%7CTWFpbGZsb3d8eyJWIjoiMC4wLjAwMDAiLCJQIjoiV2luMzIiLCJBTiI6Ik1haWwiLCJXVCI6Mn0%3D%7C3000%7C%7C%7C&amp;sdata=3r%2BCnZ7W83O8pu%2FmiPs2J6TFlGDIgsL0bfRFio9T4Fs%3D&amp;reserved=0" target="_blank" title="https://www.douyin.com/">Douyin</a> and&nbsp;<a href="https://nam12.safelinks.protection.outlook.com/?url=https%3A%2F%2Fpage.line.me%2F%3FaccountId%3Doa-pgatour%26openerPlatform%3Dnative%26openerKey%3Dtalkroom%253Aheader%23mst_challenge%3DamJN5R0IeHY7hhGr-bGyFiYqhvNvO5PZlQxUFPCQHmw&amp;data=05%7C02%7Cmarlane.white%40visitmyrtlebeach.com%7Cad9ebd62b6294c3f1ed108dc1dd7a569%7C81d417a4e3dd45fc965205e902b9d96e%7C0%7C0%7C638418059226791072%7CUnknown%7CTWFpbGZsb3d8eyJWIjoiMC4wLjAwMDAiLCJQIjoiV2luMzIiLCJBTiI6Ik1haWwiLCJXVCI6Mn0%3D%7C3000%7C%7C%7C&amp;sdata=mqLkSj%2FgNPI4p8cRH%2FCBP6P31SKJP30k0sM6T5uMWqk%3D&amp;reserved=0" title="https://page.line.me/?accountId=oa-pgatour&amp;openerPlatform=native&amp;openerKey=talkroom%3Aheader#mst_challenge=amJN5R0IeHY7hhGr-bGyFiYqhvNvO5PZlQxUFPCQHmw">LINE</a>.</p>

<p><strong>About SPORTFIVE</strong></p>

<p>SPORTFIVE is a global sports marketing agency that delivers customer-centric solutions based on trust and transparency, deep industry experience and global relationships, digital intelligence, and innovation. SPORTFIVE strategically and creatively connects brands, rightsholders, media platforms and fans to create and enable contemporary partnerships in sports.</p>

<p>While creating and growing long-term value for all, SPORTFIVE often leads the sports business into the future through innovative digital solutions and strives to be the most progressive and respected partner in sports.</p>

<p>Being at the center of professional sports, SPORTFIVE will use its unique position to make a positive contribution to sustainability and to live up to the social and economic duty and responsibility, which sport and consequently all parties involved, also have. SPORTFIVE operates with a global mindset and network of over 1,200 local experts based in 15 countries around the world, active in soccer, golf, Esports, motorsport, handball, tennis, football, basketball, ice hockey, rugby, Olympics, multi-sport events, and many more.</p>
]]></content>
    <teaser_image_url><![CDATA[https://www.myrtlebeachareachamber.com/img/cache/blog/BlogPosts/694/teaser_image/34836-590-394f-4d22ac6ad028bf35f2a8ff07772b1b94]]></teaser_image_url>
    <teaser_image_alt_text/>
    <categories><![CDATA[MBACC News Release]]></categories>
    <author><![CDATA[by Marlane White, Director of Communications]]></author>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Welcome New Members - June 2024]]></title>
    <date><![CDATA[2024-07-08 12:09:00]]></date>
    <content><![CDATA[<p>Myrtle Beach Area Chamber of Commerce encourages investors to do business with other chamber members. Please consider these new stakeholders the next time you have a need for products/services. New member&nbsp;referral? Contact&nbsp;<a href="mailto:Pam.Wright@%20VisitMyrtleBeach.com">Pam Wright</a>, business development manager, 843-916-7220. Need to make changes to business information? Contact&nbsp;<a href="mailto:Amanda.Bailey@VisitMyrtleBeach.com">Amanda Bailey</a>, business development coordinator, 843-916-7205.</p>

<hr />
<p><a href="https://web.myrtlebeachareachamber.com/Chiropractic/Align-Chiropractic-and-Massage-31820" target="_blank"><strong>Align Chiropractic and Massage</strong></a><br />
<em>Chiropractic</em><br />
Savannah Penny<br />
640 Hwy. 17 S., Unit E<br />
Surfside Beach, SC 29575<br />
843-940-4087</p>

<p><a href="https://web.myrtlebeachareachamber.com/MedicalServices/All-Health-Mobile-Lab-31646" target="_blank"><strong>All Health Mobile Lab</strong></a><br />
<em>Medical-Services</em><br />
Tanya Jones<br />
3100 Dick Pond Rd.<br />
Myrtle Beach, SC 29588<br />
843-931-4546</p>

<p><a href="https://web.myrtlebeachareachamber.com/Bridal/Amanda%27s-Collection-31749" target="_blank"><strong>Amanda&#39;s Collection</strong></a><br />
<em>Bridal</em><br />
Stephanie Hearn<br />
201 Graduate Rd., Ste. 115<br />
Conway, SC 29526<br />
843-248-3277<br />
<br />
<a href="https://web.myrtlebeachareachamber.com/EngineersGeotechnicalSoils/Applied-Geotech,-LLC-31724" target="_blank"><strong>Applied Geotech, LLC</strong></a><br />
<em>Engineers-Geotechnical/Soils</em><br />
James Nehez<br />
1903 Legion St.<br />
Myrtle Beach, SC 29577<br />
843-957-8166</p>

<p><a href="https://web.myrtlebeachareachamber.com/Accountants/askanyaccountingcom-LLC-31084" target="_blank"><strong>askanyaccounting.com</strong></a><br />
<em>Accountants</em><br />
Oleg Vedmid<br />
Myrtle Beach, SC 29579<br />
646-920-7296</p>

<p><a href="https://web.myrtlebeachareachamber.com/Hair-Salon/Baddhare-Salon-31787" target="_blank"><strong>Baddhare Salon</strong></a><br />
<em>Hair Salon</em><br />
Abigail Brown<br />
4377 N. Kings Hwy., Unit 103<br />
Myrtle Beach, SC 29577<br />
843-839-1805</p>

<p><a href="https://web.myrtlebeachareachamber.com/LandscapeArchitect/Beach-Borders-Curbing-and-Landscaping-31748" target="_blank"><strong>Beach Borders Curbing and Landscaping</strong></a><br />
<em>Landscape-Architect</em><br />
Peter Allen<br />
Longs, SC 29568<br />
843-283-4770</p>

<p><a href="https://web.myrtlebeachareachamber.com/HomeImprovement/Cape-Fear-Solar-Systems-31490" target="_blank"><strong>Cape Fear Solar Systems</strong></a><br />
<em>Home-Improvement</em><br />
Gabe Amey<br />
910 S. 2nd St.<br />
Wilmington, NC 28401<br />
910-409-5533</p>

<p><a href="https://web.myrtlebeachareachamber.com/CarpetFloorCoverings/Carpet-King-Flooring-24453" target="_blank"><strong>Carpet King &amp; Flooring</strong></a><br />
<em>Carpet-Floor/Coverings</em><br />
Joe Kocsis<br />
532 Broadway St.<br />
Myrtle Beach, SC 29577<br />
843-232-7744</p>

<p><a href="https://web.myrtlebeachareachamber.com/Education/Catalyst-Cubed-LLC-31659" target="_blank"><strong>Catalyst Cubed LLC</strong></a><br />
<em>Education</em><br />
Cedric Scott<br />
2423 Hwy. 17 S.<br />
North Myrtle Beach, SC 29582<br />
412-425-0032</p>

<p><a href="https://web.myrtlebeachareachamber.com/Real-Estate/Chad-Ferguson-Realty-One-Group-Dockside-31721" target="_blank"><strong>Chad Ferguson - Realty One Group Dockside</strong></a><br />
<em>Real Estate</em><br />
Chad Ferguson<br />
2305 N. Oak St.<br />
Myrtle Beach, SC 29577<br />
843-945-0297</p>

<p><a href="https://web.myrtlebeachareachamber.com/Real-EstateSales/Cynthia-Quinn-Real-Estate-at-eXp-Realty-31676" target="_blank"><strong>Cynthia Quinn Real Estate at eXp Realty</strong></a><br />
<em>Real Estate-Sales</em><br />
Cynthia Quinn<br />
1000 2nd Ave. S., Ste. 300 #316<br />
North Myrtle Beach, SC 29579<br />
843-778-8886</p>

<p><a href="https://web.myrtlebeachareachamber.com/FinancialPlanning/Edward-Jones-Taneisha-Gore-31673" target="_blank"><strong>Edward Jones - Taneisha Gore</strong></a><br />
<em>Financial-Planning</em><br />
Taneisha Gore<br />
3940 Hwy. 17 S. Byp.<br />
Murrells Inlet, SC 29576<br />
843-651-9036</p>

<p><a href="https://web.myrtlebeachareachamber.com/Nonprofit/EmpowerLitLiteracy-Beyond-31654" target="_blank"><strong>EmpowerLit-Literacy &amp; Beyond</strong></a><br />
<em>Nonprofit</em><br />
Gina Casazza<br />
PO Box 3023<br />
Myrtle Beach, SC 29578<br />
631-790-2829</p>

<p><a href="https://web.myrtlebeachareachamber.com/Shopping/Everything-Under-the-Sun-Flea-Market-North-31750" target="_blank"><strong>Everything Under the Sun Flea Market North</strong></a><br />
<em>Shopping</em><br />
Thiago Pires<br />
811 Hwy. 17 S.<br />
North Myrtle Beach, SC 29582<br />
843-427-7426</p>

<p><a href="https://web.myrtlebeachareachamber.com/Shopping/Everything-Under-the-Sun-Flea-Market-South-31834" target="_blank"><strong>Everything Under the Sun Flea Market South</strong></a><br />
<em>Shopping</em><br />
Elena Pires<br />
3826 S. Kings Hwy.<br />
Myrtle Beach, SC 29577<br />
843-477-1550</p>

<p><a href="https://web.myrtlebeachareachamber.com/Sports/Grand-Strand-Youth-Connection-31716" target="_blank"><strong>Grand Strand Youth Connection</strong></a><br />
<em>Sports</em><br />
Jatasha Greenway<br />
Myrtle Beach, SC 29577<br />
843-321-7062</p>

<p><a href="https://web.myrtlebeachareachamber.com/Nails/Hannah%e2%80%99s-Nails-31675" target="_blank"><strong>Hannah&rsquo;s Nails</strong></a><br />
<em>Nails</em><br />
Hannah Tran<br />
9261 Hwy. 707, Unit L<br />
Myrtle Beach, SC 29588<br />
843-940-6137</p>

<p><a href="https://web.myrtlebeachareachamber.com/Restaurant-Coffee-House/Hug-a%27-Mug-Cafe-31671" target="_blank"><strong>Hug a&#39; Mug Cafe</strong></a><br />
<em>Restaurant - Coffee House</em><br />
Janice Snyder<br />
1626 Hwy. 17 S., Ste. E<br />
North Myrtle Beach, SC 29582<br />
843-273-5003<br />
<br />
<a href="https://web.myrtlebeachareachamber.com/HotelMotel-ManagementDevelopment/Modus-by-PM-Hotel-Group-31678" target="_blank"><strong>Modus by PM Hotel Group</strong></a><br />
<em>Hotel-Motel Management/Development</em><br />
Jonathan Porcello<br />
5425 Wisconsin Ave., Ste. 700<br />
Chevy Chase, MD 20815<br />
732-299-2058</p>

<p><a href="https://web.myrtlebeachareachamber.com/OrganizationsClubs/Myrtle-Beach-Lions-Club-9872" target="_blank"><strong>Myrtle Beach Lions Club</strong></a><br />
<em>Organizations/Clubs</em><br />
Don Gesick<br />
PO Box 70074<br />
Myrtle Beach, SC 29572<br />
603-674-9607<br />
<br />
<a href="https://web.myrtlebeachareachamber.com/Legal-Services/NeSmith-Bail-Bonds,-LLC-31668" target="_blank"><strong>NeSmith Bail Bonds, LLC</strong></a><br />
<em>Legal Services</em><br />
Antonious NeSmith<br />
800 25th Ave. S., Bldg. #2, Ste. #17<br />
North Myrtle Beach, SC 29582<br />
843-234-1176</p>

<p><a href="https://web.myrtlebeachareachamber.com/Insurance/NeSmith-Insurance-Group-31239" target="_blank"><strong>NeSmith Insurance Group</strong></a><br />
<em>Insurance</em><br />
Antonious NeSmith<br />
2423 Hwy. 17 S., Ste. #B17<br />
North Myrtle Beach, SC 29582<br />
843-701-1775<br />
<br />
<a href="https://web.myrtlebeachareachamber.com/Amusements-Attractions/Out-of-the-Ark-Educational-Animal-Shows-30568" target="_blank"><strong>Out of the Ark Educational Animal Shows</strong></a><br />
<em>Amusements &amp; Attractions</em><br />
Ryan LaPierre<br />
Longs, SC 29568<br />
413-654-0197<br />
<br />
<a href="https://web.myrtlebeachareachamber.com/Restaurant-Bakery/Panera-Bread-Myrtle-Beach-21462" target="_blank"><strong>Panera Bread - Myrtle Beach</strong></a><br />
<em>Restaurant - Bakery</em><br />
Haley McCurry<br />
101 Debo Dr.<br />
Myrtle Beach, SC 29579<br />
843-492-7370</p>

<p><a href="https://web.myrtlebeachareachamber.com/Restaurant-Bakery/Panera-Bread-North-Myrtle-Beach-21467" target="_blank"><strong>Panera Bread - North Myrtle Beach</strong></a><br />
<em>Restaurant - Bakery</em><br />
Haley McCurry<br />
1296 Hwy. 17 N.<br />
North Myrtle Beach, SC 29582<br />
843-663-0221<br />
<br />
<a href="https://web.myrtlebeachareachamber.com/Restaurant-Bakery/Panera-Bread-Surfside-Beach-20529" target="_blank"><strong>Panera Bread - Surfside Beach</strong></a><br />
<em>Restaurant - Bakery</em><br />
Haley McCurry<br />
1370 S. Commons Dr.<br />
Myrtle Beach, SC 29588<br />
843-492-5074<br />
<br />
<a href="https://web.myrtlebeachareachamber.com/Apartments/Parkway-at-31-Apartments-31821" target="_blank"><strong>Parkway at 31 Apartments</strong></a><br />
<em>Apartments</em><br />
Adam Foster<br />
10600 SC-90<br />
Little River, SC 29566<br />
854-600-9704<br />
<br />
<a href="https://web.myrtlebeachareachamber.com/Air-Conditioning-Heating/Patriot-Heating-Cooling-31852" target="_blank"><strong>Patriot Heating &amp; Cooling</strong></a><br />
<em>Air Conditioning &amp; Heating</em><br />
Alex Herman<br />
Murrells Inlet, SC 29576<br />
843-748-1111<br />
<br />
<a href="https://web.myrtlebeachareachamber.com/Pressure-Washing/Rices-Powerwash-31670" target="_blank"><strong>Rices Powerwash</strong></a><br />
<em>Pressure Washing</em><br />
Paul Rice<br />
Conway, SC 29526<br />
843-602-9711<br />
<br />
<a href="https://web.myrtlebeachareachamber.com/Real-EstateApartments/Selene-at-SayeBrook-30601" target="_blank"><strong>Selene at SayeBrook</strong></a><br />
<em>Real Estate-Apartments</em><br />
Iyana Lee<br />
331 Pickwick Dr.<br />
Myrtle Beach, SC 29588<br />
843-887-1813<br />
<br />
<a href="https://web.myrtlebeachareachamber.com/Services/Smokin%27-wit-Grace-Cigars-31674" target="_blank"><strong>Smokin&#39; wit Grace Cigars</strong></a><br />
<em>Services</em><br />
Kenneth Holoman<br />
Myrtle Beach, SC 29577<br />
843-997-7512<br />
<br />
<a href="https://web.myrtlebeachareachamber.com/Restaurant/Smooth-Seas-31717" target="_blank"><strong>Smooth Seas</strong></a><br />
<em>Restaurant</em><br />
Olivia Kirtley<br />
2721 Hwy. 17 Business<br />
Murrells Inlet, SC 29576<br />
843-299-0503<br />
<br />
<a href="https://web.myrtlebeachareachamber.com/Blinds/Strickland%27s-Home-31669" target="_blank"><strong>Strickland&#39;s Home</strong></a><br />
<em>Blinds</em><br />
Carlee Hayes<br />
811 2nd Ave. N.<br />
North Myrtle Beach, SC 29582<br />
843-249-3865<br />
<br />
<a href="https://web.myrtlebeachareachamber.com/Tobacco/Sweet-Life-Tobacco-Dispensary-31842" target="_blank"><strong>Sweet Life Tobacco + Dispensary</strong></a><br />
<em>Tobacco</em><br />
Mark Kortright<br />
Carolina Shores, NC 28467<br />
910-579-8275<br />
<br />
<a href="https://web.myrtlebeachareachamber.com/Ice-CreamFrozen-Desserts/The-Crazy-Mason-Express-31647" target="_blank"><strong>The Crazy Mason Express</strong></a><br />
<em>Ice Cream-Frozen Desserts</em><br />
Sherri Steele<br />
5901 S. Kings Hwy.<br />
Myrtle Beach, SC 29577<br />
843-214-1117<br />
<br />
<a href="https://web.myrtlebeachareachamber.com/Business-Services/Thomas-Brand-Financial-Solutions-31657" target="_blank"><strong>Thomas Brand Financial Solutions</strong></a><br />
<em>Business Services</em><br />
Reginald Thomas<br />
Myrtle Beach, SC 29588<br />
803-413-2099<br />
<br />
<a href="https://web.myrtlebeachareachamber.com/Chiropractic/Wave-of-Light-Chiropractic-31494" target="_blank"><strong>Wave of Light Chiropractic</strong></a><br />
<em>Chiropractic</em><br />
Jessica Parada<br />
1753 Sea Pine Blvd., Unit 501B<br />
Myrtle Beach, SC 29577<br />
678-632-3397<br />
<br />
<a href="https://web.myrtlebeachareachamber.com/Window-Cleaner/Window-Cleaning-Service-31706" target="_blank"><strong>Window Cleaning Service</strong></a><br />
<em>Window Cleaner</em><br />
Reuben Hearn<br />
Little River, SC 29566<br />
843-698-3013<br />
<br />
<a href="https://web.myrtlebeachareachamber.com/Restaurant-Mediterranean/Zeytin-31797" target="_blank"><strong>Zeytin</strong></a><br />
<em>Restaurant - Mediterranean</em><br />
Umut Balkis<br />
224 Fresh Dr., Unit A<br />
Myrtle Beach, SC 29579<br />
843-236-0173</p>

<hr />
<p>Thank you to the following businesses who renewed their chamber membership during the month of June.</p>

<ul>
<li>A Father&#39;s Place</li>
<li>Accuchex</li>
<li>AIM Acupuncture &amp; Integrative Medicine</li>
<li>A-JAX Golf Cart Rentals</li>
<li>All4Paws Animal Rescue</li>
<li>ALZ FOUNDATION</li>
<li>Anderson Insurance Associates</li>
<li>Arcadian Risk Managers</li>
<li>Ashe Law Firm, Inc.</li>
<li>Associated Charities</li>
<li>Atlantic Heating &amp; Cooling</li>
<li>Barnabas Horse Foundation</li>
<li>Beach &amp; Forest Realty</li>
<li>Beach Audiology Hearing &amp; Balance Center</li>
<li>Beach Ball Classic</li>
<li>BeachCHURCH - Myrtle Beach Community Church</li>
<li>Berkshire Hathaway HomeServices Myrtle Beach Real Estate</li>
<li>Berry Financial Group, Inc.</li>
<li>Better Bins Disposal Dumpster Rentals</li>
<li>Blue Ribbon Show Services</li>
<li>Bmore Technology</li>
<li>Brazen Roofing</li>
<li>Burch &amp; Burch Business Consulting</li>
<li>Byrd Palmer Property Management</li>
<li>Callie Wise State Farm</li>
<li>Careteam Plus, Inc.</li>
<li>Carmella Walter Insurance Agency (Allstate)</li>
<li>Carolina Adaptive Golf</li>
<li>Carolina Master Chorale</li>
<li>Carolina Temperature Control</li>
<li>Carolina Trust Federal Credit Union</li>
<li>Carolina Trust Federal Credit Union</li>
<li>Carolinas Staffing Solutions, Inc.</li>
<li>Cavinder Elevator Company</li>
<li>Cellular Sales/Verizon Wireless</li>
<li>Century 21 Boling &amp; Associates, Inc.</li>
<li>Children&#39;s Recovery Center</li>
<li>Claremont Property Company</li>
<li>Clawson and Staubes, LLC</li>
<li>Coastal Carolina Otolaryngology</li>
<li>Coastal Distribution</li>
<li>Coastal Eye Group, PC</li>
<li>Coastal Interiorscapes</li>
<li>Coastal Periodontics LLC</li>
<li>Coastal Vision Center</li>
<li>Coastal Youth Ballet Theatre</li>
<li>Competition Cars Inc.</li>
<li>Convention Makers, Inc.</li>
<li>Conway Air Conditioning</li>
<li>Core Services, LLC</li>
<li>CRM Services</li>
<li>Dawol Homes, Inc.</li>
<li>DeFalco&#39;s Automotive &amp; Towing</li>
<li>Down East Heating and Air Conditioning, Inc.</li>
<li>DRIVE Point of Sale</li>
<li>Eddie &amp; Julie Boyd, The Boyd Team - INNOVATE Real Estate</li>
<li>Edward Jones - Jason Toy</li>
<li>Edward Jones - Bryan Cambra</li>
<li>Family Justice Center of Georgetown and Horry Counties</li>
<li>Feldman &amp; Melton Law Offices</li>
<li>Flossy Pediatric Dentistry</li>
<li>For What It&#39;s Worth Appraisals</li>
<li>Founders Centre I LLC</li>
<li>Franklin G. Burroughs - Simeon B. Chapin Art Museum</li>
<li>Freewoods Farm</li>
<li>Friends of the Chapin Memorial Library</li>
<li>FSIoffice</li>
<li>Golf Tourism Solutions</li>
<li>Grand Anchor Insurance</li>
<li>Grand Strand Angel Network</li>
<li>Grand Strand Business Alliance</li>
<li>Grand Strand Nissan, Inc.</li>
<li>Grand Strand Senior Center</li>
<li>Habitat for Humanity of Horry County, Inc.</li>
<li>Hadwin-White GMC/Buick/Subaru</li>
<li>Heyd &amp; Co.</li>
<li>Hillcrest Cemetery</li>
<li>Horry County Disabilities &amp; Special Needs</li>
<li>Horry Electric Cooperative, Inc.</li>
<li>IMPACT Ministries of Myrtle Beach</li>
<li>InterExchange, Inc.</li>
<li>Invera Wealth Advisors</li>
<li>John T. Cook &amp; Associates</li>
<li>John W. Molony Law Firm, LLC</li>
<li>Kelly O&#39;Brien Insurance Agency Inc.</li>
<li>Kristina Barron Photography</li>
<li>Law Offices of N. David DuRant &amp; Associates, PA</li>
<li>Leader Mentality Business Consulting LLC</li>
<li>Leverage Roofing</li>
<li>The Litchfield Company Real Estate</li>
<li>Little River Medical Center, Inc.</li>
<li>LPGA Amateur Golf Association - Myrtle Beach</li>
<li>LS3P</li>
<li>Maguire Law Firm</li>
<li>Martine Wiliams Coaching</li>
<li>McCutchen, Vaught, Geddie &amp; Hucks, PA</li>
<li>McMillan-Small Funeral Home</li>
<li>Meals on Wheels of Horry County, Inc.</li>
<li>Midtown Vineyard Church</li>
<li>Mikaela Kate Training</li>
<li>Minuteman Press</li>
<li>Mission City Travel LLC</li>
<li>Monarch Roofing</li>
<li>Monteith Construction Corp.</li>
<li>Moore &amp; Associates Insurance of Surfside</li>
<li>Muriel Ward O&#39;Tuel, Ph.D.</li>
<li>Myrtle Beach Golf App</li>
<li>National Shag Dance Championship</li>
<li>New Directions of Horry County</li>
<li>New Horizon Hospitality</li>
<li>Newby, Sartip &amp; Masel, LLC</li>
<li>Olsten Staffing Services</li>
<li>One Source Communications</li>
<li>Palmetto Literacy Council</li>
<li>Palmetto Property Inspections</li>
<li>PAR Physical Therapy</li>
<li>Pawleys Eye Associates</li>
<li>Peoples Underwriters, Inc.</li>
<li>Piedmont Service Group</li>
<li>Pinnacle Financial Partners</li>
<li>Pittsburgh Institute of Aeronautics</li>
<li>Practical Solutions for Public Safety, Inc.</li>
<li>R.L. Causey, Inc.</li>
<li>Radius Financial Group</li>
<li>RE/MAX Southern Shores</li>
<li>Real Hot Yoga</li>
<li>Rebecca Gibson State Farm</li>
<li>Re-Builders, Inc.</li>
<li>River Oaks Animal Hospital</li>
<li>Riverbend Wealth Management</li>
<li>Rivertown Property Inspections</li>
<li>RSM, Inc.</li>
<li>Saltwater Chamber Orchestra</li>
<li>Sansbury Law Firm, LLC</li>
<li>Santee Cooper Credit Union</li>
<li>Senior Helpers</li>
<li>Sexton Dental Clinic</li>
<li>SMITH SAPP CPAs</li>
<li>Socastee Eye Clinic</li>
<li>Sons &amp; Daughters of Italy in America Lodge 2662</li>
<li>SOS Care</li>
<li>South State Bank- Myrtle Beach</li>
<li>SOWW - Special Operations Wounded Warriors</li>
<li>Spann Roofing &amp; Sheet Metal, Inc.</li>
<li>Spherion</li>
<li>St. John Greek Orthodox Church</li>
<li>Stanley Steemer Carpet Cleaner</li>
<li>State Farm Insurance - Wyman Wise</li>
<li>Strand Capital Group LLC</li>
<li>Strand Supply</li>
<li>SunCoast Building Products &amp; Services Inc.</li>
<li>Temple Emanu-El</li>
<li>The Beach Nest, Interiors &amp; Design</li>
<li>The Bellamy Law Firm</li>
<li>The Brave at Heart Foundation</li>
<li>The Brittain Law Firm, P.A.</li>
<li>The Derrick Law Firm</li>
<li>The Earthworks Group, Inc.</li>
<li>The George Agency</li>
<li>The Grove at Coastal Grand</li>
<li>The Humane Society of North Myrtle Beach</li>
<li>The Lovely Law Firm</li>
<li>The Palmettos Garden City</li>
<li>The Salvation Army - Horry County</li>
<li>Thomas &amp; Hutton Engineering Co.</li>
<li>Thomas Gymnastics at the Beach</li>
<li>Thomas Real Estate, Inc.</li>
<li>Tidelands Health</li>
<li>Ann Vaughn Tilley</li>
<li>United Way of Horry County</li>
<li>USA Plumbing II Inc.</li>
<li>Vinings at Carolina Bays</li>
<li>Waccamaw EOC, Inc.</li>
<li>Waccamaw Indian People</li>
<li>Waccamaw Insurance Services, Inc.</li>
<li>Waccamaw Land &amp; Timber Co., Inc.</li>
<li>Watermark Real Estate Group</li>
<li>William H. Miller Studios &amp; Fine Art</li>
<li>Withers Crest</li>
<li>WMBF News</li>
<li>WTS-Waccamaw Telecommunication Systems, Inc.</li>
<li>Yahnis Coastal, Inc.</li>
<li>Young Talkers - Adult &amp; Pediatric Therapy Clinic</li>
<li>Yvonne Salsbury State Farm</li>
<li>1229 Shine</li>
<li>Action Watersportz</li>
<li>Affordable Large Properties</li>
<li>Aloha Mini Golf</li>
<li>Angelo&#39;s Steak &amp; Pasta</li>
<li>Apache Pier</li>
<li>Art Burger Sushi Bar</li>
<li>Aspen Grille</li>
<li>Atlantic Kitchens</li>
<li>Backstage Escape Game</li>
<li>Backstage Mirror Maze</li>
<li>Badd Kitty</li>
<li>Barefoot Queen Riverboat</li>
<li>Barefoot Resort Rentals</li>
<li>Benjamin&#39;s Bakery Cafe &amp; Coffee Roaster</li>
<li>Bistro 217</li>
<li>Blueberry&#39;s Grill - North Myrtle Beach</li>
<li>Booe Realty</li>
<li>Broadway at the Beach</li>
<li>Calabash Fishing Fleet</li>
<li>Carolina Pottery</li>
<li>Carolina RV</li>
<li>Classic Swing Golf School, Inc.</li>
<li>Coastal Engravers, Inc. - MB</li>
<li>Coffee &amp; Cream Cabana</li>
<li>Coral Beach Resort &amp; Suites</li>
<li>Country Club</li>
<li>Country Inn &amp; Suites by Radisson</li>
<li>Croissants Bistro &amp; Bakery</li>
<li>Cypress Room</li>
<li>Dayton House Resort</li>
<li>Drunken Jack&#39;s</li>
<li>Dunes Realty Vacation Rentals</li>
<li>Dunes Village Resort</li>
<li>Duplin Winery</li>
<li>Elko Spas, Billiards &amp; Pools</li>
<li>Elton John Tribute Show - GTS Theatre</li>
<li>Essence Day Spa</li>
<li>Flamingo Grill</li>
<li>Flamingo Rides</li>
<li>Floortech Styles and Design</li>
<li>Garden City Realty, Inc.</li>
<li>Gay Dolphin</li>
<li>Grand Strand Vacations and Rentals</li>
<li>Grayline of Myrtle Beach / Leisure Time Unlimited, Inc.</li>
<li>Great Escapes Kayak Expeditions</li>
<li>Hachiya Express Surfside Beach, Inc</li>
<li>Hawaiian Rumble Miniature Golf</li>
<li>Hawaiian Village Miniature Golf</li>
<li>Holiday Sands North &quot;On the Boardwalk&quot;</li>
<li>Hook &amp; Barrel</li>
<li>Hudson&#39;s Surfside Flea Market</li>
<li>Hungry Howie&#39;s Pizza &amp; Subs</li>
<li>Inlet Affairs Banquet &amp; Catering</li>
<li>Inlet Prohibition Company</li>
<li>International Chili Society</li>
<li>Island Vista</li>
<li>Island Vista</li>
<li>Kirk&#39;s 1890 Ice Cream Parlor</li>
<li>Kozy Getaways</li>
<li>Lakewood Camping Resort</li>
<li>Logan&#39;s Roadhouse</li>
<li>Magic &amp; Comedy Show - GTS Theatre</li>
<li>Marco Polo Pizzeria</li>
<li>Marriott&#39;s OceanWatch Villas @ Grande Dunes</li>
<li>McDonald&#39;s</li>
<li>Milk &amp; Honey Coffee Cafe</li>
<li>Myrtle Beach Timeshare Resales</li>
<li>New Wave Watersports</li>
<li>Ocean Front Bar &amp; Grill</li>
<li>Original Motown Tribute Show at GTS Theatre</li>
<li>Osprey Marina</li>
<li>Perrone&#39;s Restaurant and Bar</li>
<li>Pet Supplies Plus</li>
<li>PirateLand Family Camping Resort</li>
<li>RipTydz Oceanfront Grille &amp; Rooftop Bar</li>
<li>Rose Real Estate</li>
<li>Roxanne Towers</li>
<li>Sea Crest Oceanfront Resort</li>
<li>Sea Racer Dolphin Tours</li>
<li>Se&ntilde;or Frogs</li>
<li>Sheraton Myrtle Beach Convention Center Hotel</li>
<li>Sound Tracks of Soul - GTS Theatre</li>
<li>Southern Shores Island and Dolphin Cruises</li>
<li>Stars and Strikes Family Entertainment Center</li>
<li>Surfmaster By The Sea Oceanfront Rentals-Garden City Realty</li>
<li>Swift Appliance LLC</li>
<li>The Big Red Bus</li>
<li>The Bowery</li>
<li>The Car Store</li>
<li>The Christmas Mouse MB</li>
<li>The Grumpy Monk</li>
<li>The Hangout</li>
<li>Thomas Beach Vacations</li>
<li>Thorny&#39;s Food Sports Fun</li>
<li>Thoroughbreds Chophouse &amp; Seafood Grille</li>
<li>Tomlinsons Warehouse</li>
<li>Tupelo Bay Golf</li>
<li>Voyager Deep Sea Fishing &amp; Dolphin Cruises</li>
<li>Wacca Wache Marina</li>
<li>Wholesale Furniture Gallery</li>
<li>Yogi Bear&#39;s Jellystone Park at Daddy Joe&#39;s</li>
</ul>
]]></content>
    <teaser_image_url><![CDATA[https://www.myrtlebeachareachamber.com/img/cache/blog/BlogPosts/692/teaser_image/34836-590-394f-4d22ac6ad028bf35f2a8ff07772b1b94]]></teaser_image_url>
    <teaser_image_alt_text><![CDATA[Welcome New Members - June 2024]]></teaser_image_alt_text>
    <categories><![CDATA[New Members]]></categories>
    <author/>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Tracy Conner To Serve as MBACC Interim President and CEO]]></title>
    <date><![CDATA[2024-07-02 10:16:00]]></date>
    <content><![CDATA[<p>MYRTLE BEACH, S.C.&mdash;The Myrtle Beach Area Chamber of Commerce (MBACC) and Convention and Visitors Bureau (CVB) announce the immediate appointment of Tracy Conner as the Interim President and CEO following the resignation of Karen Riordan.</p>

<p>Conner will collaborate with the Chamber&rsquo;s board of directors and staff to ensure the seamless continuation of the organization&rsquo;s operations and strategic initiatives during the search for a permanent replacement.</p>

<p>&ldquo;Tracy&rsquo;s extensive experience and commitment to the community, including his dedication to promoting the region as a premier golf destination, make him an ideal choice for this role. His leadership will undoubtedly steer the Chamber and CVB toward continued success and growth while we search for new leadership,&rdquo; said John Rutenberg, Chair of the Board of Directors.</p>

<p>Conner brings more than 35 years of professional experience to the position, including extensive connections within the Grand Strand&rsquo;s business community as well as the national tourism and hospitality industries.</p>

<p>Through his leadership positions with organizations such as the Myrtle Beach Area Golf Course Owners Association and Golf Tourism Solutions, he has played a crucial role in marketing the Grand Strand as the &ldquo;Golf Capital of the World,&rdquo; securing the PGA TOUR&rsquo;s Myrtle Beach Classic and ensuring the success of its inaugural tournament.&nbsp;</p>

<p>Conner has been actively involved with the Chamber and CVB for several years, serving on the Board of Directors and as Chair of the Advocacy Council. He and his wife, Debbie, are long-time residents of Myrtle Beach.</p>

<p>&ldquo;I am honored to step into this role and look forward to working closely with our members, stakeholders and staff to ensure the Chamber&rsquo;s continued success in serving the Myrtle Beach area for which I care for so deeply,&rdquo; Conner said.</p>

<p>The Chamber&rsquo;s board of directors will soon establish a committee and select a firm to conduct a nationwide search for the next leader, with more details to be announced at a later date.</p>
]]></content>
    <teaser_image_url><![CDATA[https://www.myrtlebeachareachamber.com/img/cache/blog/BlogPosts/693/teaser_image/34836-590-394f-4d22ac6ad028bf35f2a8ff07772b1b94]]></teaser_image_url>
    <teaser_image_alt_text/>
    <categories><![CDATA[News]]></categories>
    <author/>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Important Leadership Announcement]]></title>
    <date><![CDATA[2024-06-28 14:28:00]]></date>
    <content><![CDATA[<p>It is with heartfelt appreciation and best wishes that we share with you the announcement of Karen Riordan&rsquo;s resignation as our President and CEO.</p>

<p>Karen, who has served the Chamber and CVB with dedication and distinction since 2018, has decided to step down to pursue new opportunities and spend more time with her family effective June 28, 2024.</p>

<p>Karen shares this message: &ldquo;It has been a great honor to serve as President and CEO of the Myrtle Beach Area Chamber and CVB. I am incredibly proud of what we have accomplished together and grateful for the support of our members, staff, board and community. While I look forward to new challenges ahead, the Myrtle Beach Area Chamber and CVB will always hold a special place in my heart.&rdquo;</p>

<p>John Rutenberg, Chair of the Chamber board of directors, expressed his heartfelt regard for Riordan&rsquo;s leadership over the past six years. &ldquo;Karen&rsquo;s vision for our chamber, CVB and community have been transformative for the Grand Strand&rsquo;s business community by continuing to foster the area as a thriving destination. We are thankful for her service, and we wish her the very best in any of her future endeavors.&rdquo;</p>

<p>During her tenure, Karen has been instrumental in the local business environment, including economic growth and promoting Myrtle Beach as a premier destination for tourism. This includes leading the Chamber and CVB through milestones such as launching community enhancement efforts like the Partnership Grand Strand foundation and Keep Myrtle Beach Beautiful, rebranding the Chamber and Visit Myrtle Beach highlighted by the successful &ldquo;You Belong at the Beach&rdquo; campaign, and participating in notable events such as the Myrtle Beach Bowl and the PGA TOUR&rsquo;s Myrtle Beach Classic.</p>

<p>We appreciate Karen&#39;s contributions and wish her the very best in her future endeavors.&nbsp;</p>

<p>The Chamber&rsquo;s board of directors will soon begin the search for a new president and CEO. Interim leadership plans will be announced in the coming days to ensure a smooth transition.</p>

<p>Thank you for your continued support and involvement in the Myrtle Beach Area Chamber and CVB. Should you have any questions or need further information, please do not hesitate to contact us at <a data-emb-href-display="info@visitmyrtlebeach.com" href="mailto:info@visitmyrtlebeach.com">info@visitmyrtlebeach.com</a>.</p>
]]></content>
    <teaser_image_url><![CDATA[https://www.myrtlebeachareachamber.com/img/cache/blog/BlogPosts/691/teaser_image/34836-590-394f-4d22ac6ad028bf35f2a8ff07772b1b94]]></teaser_image_url>
    <teaser_image_alt_text/>
    <categories><![CDATA[News]]></categories>
    <author/>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Celebrate Christmas in July and Support Substitutes for Santa]]></title>
    <date><![CDATA[2024-06-25 10:36:00]]></date>
    <content><![CDATA[<p>Grand Strand Young Professionals is celebrating Christmas in July with several fundraisers benefiting Substitutes for Santa - an annual event held in partnership with SOS Care that provides a magical Christmas experience to 150 children in Horry County.</p>

<p>During the event, the children are first taken to Fun Warehouse for games and pizza, then they are taken to Walmart to buy presents. Each child also is sent home with a bag of necessary household items and toiletries. Sponsorships and fundraisers make the event possible.</p>

<p>Sponsorships start at $250 and are available now for the 2024 event. View sponsorship benefits and levels by visiting <a href="https://grandstrandyoungprofessionals.com/" rel="noreferrer noopener" target="_blank">GrandStrandYoungProfessionals.com</a>.</p>

<p>The following are Christmas in July events scheduled to support Substitutes for Santa this year.</p>

<p>Brews to Benefit: July 1 at Tidal Creek Brewhouse. $1 from each beer sold between 5 and 7 p.m. on July 1 will be donated to Substitutes for Santa.</p>

<p>Spaghetti Wednesday: Beachfront Kitchen &amp; Bar is donating proceeds from it&rsquo;s Spaghetti Wednesday on July 10 between 11 a.m. and 9 p.m. to Substitutes for Santa. For $12.99, enjoy a salad, garlic bread and plate of spaghetti with meat sauce. $10 from each meal will be donated. Orders are for available dine in, carry out or pick up.</p>

<p>WonderWorks Ticket Offer: WonderWorks is offering tickets at a special rate to support Substitutes for Santa. From July 21 through July 28, you can purchase &ldquo;Buy Now, Use Later&rdquo; tickets for $15 where $5 from each ticket will directly support the charity event. Tickets may only be purchased online during the event dates with code GSYP at checkout. Taxes are not included.</p>

<p>Christmas in July at BurgerFi: Fuel your appetite for giving back at BurgerFi at 106 Sayebrook Pkwy. in Myrtle Beach on July 24 from 4-8 p.m. When you order, tell the staff you&rsquo;re there for GSYP and 20% of your order will be donated to Substitutes for Santa.</p>

<p>For additional information on the fundraisers or Substitutes for Santa, visit GrandStrandYoungProfessionals.com or email <a href="mailto:Isabella.Cenatiempo@VisitMyrtleBeach.com" rel="noreferrer noopener" target="_blank">Isabella.Cenatiempo@VisitMyrtleBeach.com</a>.</p>
]]></content>
    <teaser_image_url><![CDATA[https://www.myrtlebeachareachamber.com/img/cache/blog/BlogPosts/690/teaser_image/34836-590-394f-4d22ac6ad028bf35f2a8ff07772b1b94]]></teaser_image_url>
    <teaser_image_alt_text><![CDATA[Support substitutes for santa and celebrate christmas in july]]></teaser_image_alt_text>
    <categories><![CDATA[News,GSYP]]></categories>
    <author><![CDATA[by Amanda Blomquist, Business Development Marketing Manager]]></author>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Jada Hudson Joins Myrtle Beach Area Chamber as Public Policy Coordinator]]></title>
    <date><![CDATA[2024-06-24 14:11:00]]></date>
    <content><![CDATA[<p>The Myrtle Beach Area Chamber of Commerce (MBACC) is pleased to announce the appointment of Jada Hudson as the new Public Policy Coordinator.</p>

<p>In her role, Hudson will collaborate with Jimmy Gray, MBACC vice president of public policy, to support advocacy-related activities, programs, research and communications, including monitoring legislation that impacts those who live, work and play in Horry and Georgetown counties. &nbsp;</p>

<p>&ldquo;We&rsquo;re thrilled to welcome Jada to our team,&rdquo; said Karen Riordan, MBACC President and CEO. &ldquo;Her passion for public policy will be invaluable as we continue to advocate for the interests of our members and the broader business community.&rdquo;</p>

<p>Hudson graduated from the University of South Carolina&rsquo;s Honors College in May 2024 with a bachelor&rsquo;s degree in political science. During her time at the university, Hudson served as the president of the Association of African American Students, a speaker pro tempore of the Student Senate, a student assistant at the Office of Access and Opportunity, a student ambassador at the Office of Multicultural Student Affairs, a legislative intern at the Department of Alcohol and Other Drug Abuse Services, and a student coordinator for the Multicultural Assistance Peer Program. Hudson is also a member of Phi Beta Kappa, Delta Sigma Theta Sorority Inc., Omicron Delta Kappa and the NAACP.</p>

<p>&ldquo;I&rsquo;m incredibly excited to join the Myrtle Beach Area Chamber of Commerce as the Public Policy Coordinator,&rdquo; Hudson said. &ldquo;This position offers a unique opportunity to effect meaningful change and positively impact the lives of those across the Grand Strand.&rdquo;</p>
]]></content>
    <teaser_image_url><![CDATA[https://www.myrtlebeachareachamber.com/img/cache/blog/BlogPosts/688/teaser_image/34836-590-394f-4d22ac6ad028bf35f2a8ff07772b1b94]]></teaser_image_url>
    <teaser_image_alt_text><![CDATA[jada hudson joins mbacc as public policy coordinator]]></teaser_image_alt_text>
    <categories><![CDATA[News]]></categories>
    <author><![CDATA[by Marlane White, Director of Communications]]></author>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Sandy Haines Receives 2024 Spirit of TAP Award from Travel Alliance Partners]]></title>
    <date><![CDATA[2024-06-21 8:03:00]]></date>
    <content><![CDATA[<p>Myrtle Beach Area Chamber of Commerce and Visit Myrtle Beach are&nbsp;pleased to announce that Sandy Haines, director of group tour sales, has been awarded the 2024 Spirit of TAP Award by Travel Alliance Partners (TAP), a prestigious travel industry organization comprised of group tour operators and suppliers across the U.S. and Canada.</p>

<p>&quot;We&rsquo;re incredibly proud of Sandy for receiving this top industry recognition,&rdquo; said Bob Harris, Visit Myrtle Beach&rsquo;s executive vice president of group sales. &ldquo;Her dedication to fostering strong partnerships with group tour operators across the country is a driving force behind why the Myrtle Beach area continues to grow as a destination for groups, meetings and sports events.&rdquo;</p>

<p>Haines, who has worked for Visit Myrtle Beach for the past 32 years, received the Spirit of TAP Award during the organization&rsquo;s annual conference held June 9-11 in Jeffersonville, Ind.</p>

<p>TAP is renowned for providing resources and programming to North American Tour Operators. Being recognized by such a distinguished organization underscores the high regard in which Haines is held by her peers and colleagues while celebrating the vibrant tourism industry in Myrtle Beach.</p>
]]></content>
    <teaser_image_url><![CDATA[https://www.myrtlebeachareachamber.com/img/cache/blog/BlogPosts/689/teaser_image/34836-590-394f-4d22ac6ad028bf35f2a8ff07772b1b94]]></teaser_image_url>
    <teaser_image_alt_text><![CDATA[Sandy Haines Receives 2024 Spirit of TAP Award from Travel Alliance Partners]]></teaser_image_alt_text>
    <categories><![CDATA[News]]></categories>
    <author><![CDATA[by Marlane White, Director of Communications]]></author>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Ways to Help Myrtle Beach Nonprofits - June 2024]]></title>
    <date><![CDATA[2024-06-18 8:30:00]]></date>
    <content><![CDATA[<div>
<p>In an effort to support the many Grand Strand nonprofits on their missions to supporting the community, Myrtle Beach Area Chamber of Commerce is publishing this monthly roundup of our nonprofit members current needs.</p>

<p>If you&rsquo;re looking to get involved or give back, consider supporting the nonprofits below or in&nbsp;the chamber&rsquo;s&nbsp;<a href="https://web.myrtlebeachareachamber.com/Nonprofit">business directory.</a></p>

<hr /></div>

<p>The&nbsp;<strong><a href="https://web.myrtlebeachareachamber.com/Nonprofit/Boys-Girls-Club-of-the-Grand-Strand-6775">Boys &amp; Girls Club of the Grand Strand</a></strong>&nbsp;seeks 20 Chromebooks and a 3D printer. They also are looking for silent auction donations.</p>

<p><strong><a href="https://web.myrtlebeachareachamber.com/Nonprofit/Eagle-Cold-Case-and-Missing-Persons-Institute-(ECCMPI)-28228">Eagle Cold Case and Missing Persons Institute</a></strong>&nbsp;seeks funding to support their efforts to examine unresolved murders and missing persons cases.</p>

<p><strong><a href="https://web.myrtlebeachareachamber.com/TheatresLive/Long-Bay-Theatre-24030" target="_blank">Long Bay Theatre</a></strong>&nbsp;seeks supplies for their summer camp program including: liquid hand soaps, toilet paper, bathroom cleaning supplies, paper towels, copy paper, snacks, small paper cups, mechanical pencils, lunchables and a water cooler for 5-10 gallon bottles. Long term, they are looking for stackable chairs for rehearsals and recitals.</p>

<p><strong><a href="https://www.silverliningmb.com/">Silver Lining School of the Arts</a></strong>&nbsp;is looking for sponsors to support Slugger Special Needs music students and Silver Lining Dancers who are unable to afford classes. Sponsorships begin at $200.&nbsp;SLSA wants to be the bridge that gives every child quality instruction in the artistic field of their choice, regardless of their emotional struggles, physical disabilities, special needs or their family&#39;s ability to pay. The studio is also in need of classroom mirrors and adapted musical instruments for our uniquely gifted students. For information on how to donate call 843-236-6226.</p>

<p><strong><a href="http://SOSCaresc.org">SOS Care</a></strong>&nbsp;needs mulch for playgrounds and flowers for front flower beds. They also are in need of power washing, and gutter cleaning services and handyman services.</p>

<p><strong><a href="https://web.myrtlebeachareachamber.com/Events-Promotions/The-Arts-Grand-Strand-19305">The Arts Grand Strand</a></strong>&nbsp;is looking for new board members and volunteers. Please contact William H. Miller, executive director, by emailing&nbsp;<a data-linkindex="3" href="mailto:theartsgrandstrand@gmail.com">theartsgrandstrand@gmail.com</a>.</p>

<p><strong><a href="https://wow.uscgaux.info/content.php?unit=070-12-04">United States Coast Guard Auxiliary</a></strong>&nbsp;is seeking donations for the purchase of new life jackets and materials to repair several life jacket stands at Horry County boat launches.</p>
]]></content>
    <teaser_image_url><![CDATA[https://www.myrtlebeachareachamber.com/img/cache/blog/BlogPosts/684/teaser_image/34836-590-394f-4d22ac6ad028bf35f2a8ff07772b1b94]]></teaser_image_url>
    <teaser_image_alt_text><![CDATA[Ways to Help Myrtle Beach Nonprofits - June 2024]]></teaser_image_alt_text>
    <categories><![CDATA[News]]></categories>
    <author/>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Myrtle Beach Area Chamber Holds Community Open House on June 21]]></title>
    <date><![CDATA[2024-06-13 15:55:00]]></date>
    <content><![CDATA[<p>MYRTLE BEACH, S.C.&mdash;The Community Engagement Committee of the Myrtle Beach Area Chamber of Commerce and Convention and Visitors Bureau (CVB) is holding a Community Open House on June 21, 2024, from 1 to 3 p.m. at the Myrtle Beach Area Chamber of Commerce visitors center at 1200 N. Oak Street in Myrtle Beach.</p>

<p>Light refreshments and giveaways will be available as members of the community learn more about the vital role the chamber and CVB play in its mission to promote, protect and improve the Grand Strand through supporting local businesses and nonprofit organizations.</p>

<p>Opportunities will be given to meet with chamber staff and members of the community engagement committee who represent organizations throughout Horry and Georgetown counties.</p>

<p>Plus, the open house will provide information on ways to get involved in the community through various service opportunities and programs such as Keep Myrtle Beach Beautiful.</p>

<p>This event is free and open to all. Pre-register for the event at <a href="https://nam12.safelinks.protection.outlook.com/?url=https%3A%2F%2Fweb.myrtlebeachareachamber.com%2Fevents%2FCommunityOpen%2520House-8586%2Fdetails&amp;data=05%7C02%7Cfaith.schmeizl%40visitmyrtlebeach.com%7C3a6ed82d578747fe949308dc8bdcc5ae%7C81d417a4e3dd45fc965205e902b9d96e%7C0%7C0%7C638539029141422211%7CUnknown%7CTWFpbGZsb3d8eyJWIjoiMC4wLjAwMDAiLCJQIjoiV2luMzIiLCJBTiI6Ik1haWwiLCJXVCI6Mn0%3D%7C0%7C%7C%7C&amp;sdata=%2BaIevrfxcRq%2FHwmlC8jcxU36wlGdvTYbvkPQkzXWCDI%3D&amp;reserved=0">MyrtleBeachAreaChamber.com</a>.</p>

<p>&nbsp;</p>

<p style="text-align: center;"># # #</p>

<p>&nbsp;</p>

<p><a name="x__Hlk78886154">About Myrtle Beach Area Chamber of Commerce and Convention and Visitors Bureau:</a></p>

<p>Since 1938, the Myrtle Beach Area Chamber of Commerce (MBACC) has stood as the unified voice of the Grand Strand&#39;s business community &mdash; serving Myrtle Beach, North Myrtle Beach, Little River, Loris, Atlantic Beach, Carolina Forest, Conway, Aynor, Socastee, Surfside Beach, Garden City Beach, Murrells Inlet, Litchfield Beach and Pawleys Island. The U.S. Chamber of Commerce has awarded MBACC its five-star accreditation &mdash; one of only a few chambers in South Carolina to earn this distinction. The Myrtle Beach Area Convention and Visitors Bureau (CVB) and its destination marketing arm Visit Myrtle Beach promote tourism through various partnerships and initiatives to advance the economic success of the Grand Strand. For more information, visit <a href="file:///C:/Users/marlane.white/Desktop/PRESS%20RELEASES/DRAFT%20RELEASES/MyrtleBeachAreaChamber.com">MyrtleBeachAreaChamber.com</a>, <a href="https://nam12.safelinks.protection.outlook.com/?url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.myrtlebeachareacvb.com%2F&amp;data=05%7C02%7Cfaith.schmeizl%40visitmyrtlebeach.com%7C3a6ed82d578747fe949308dc8bdcc5ae%7C81d417a4e3dd45fc965205e902b9d96e%7C0%7C0%7C638539029141433201%7CUnknown%7CTWFpbGZsb3d8eyJWIjoiMC4wLjAwMDAiLCJQIjoiV2luMzIiLCJBTiI6Ik1haWwiLCJXVCI6Mn0%3D%7C0%7C%7C%7C&amp;sdata=CNjLngU0Byef6KioZIiVII2v3Dj5Ko8QLcJ6k9V2je8%3D&amp;reserved=0">MyrtleBeachAreaCVB.com</a> and <a href="https://nam12.safelinks.protection.outlook.com/?url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.visitmyrtlebeach.com%2F&amp;data=05%7C02%7Cfaith.schmeizl%40visitmyrtlebeach.com%7C3a6ed82d578747fe949308dc8bdcc5ae%7C81d417a4e3dd45fc965205e902b9d96e%7C0%7C0%7C638539029141439750%7CUnknown%7CTWFpbGZsb3d8eyJWIjoiMC4wLjAwMDAiLCJQIjoiV2luMzIiLCJBTiI6Ik1haWwiLCJXVCI6Mn0%3D%7C0%7C%7C%7C&amp;sdata=U%2BMZ%2F3xYZveN8RJ5UvrDsbyvmfBnZJybO47qPGj%2F0Nw%3D&amp;reserved=0">VisitMyrtleBeach.com</a>.</p>
]]></content>
    <teaser_image_url><![CDATA[https://www.myrtlebeachareachamber.com/img/cache/blog/BlogPosts/687/teaser_image/34836-590-394f-4d22ac6ad028bf35f2a8ff07772b1b94]]></teaser_image_url>
    <teaser_image_alt_text/>
    <categories><![CDATA[News]]></categories>
    <author/>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Visit Myrtle Beachs Cyndi Mohr Receives 2024 Associate of the Year Award from South Carolina Society of Association Executives]]></title>
    <date><![CDATA[2024-06-12 15:35:00]]></date>
    <content><![CDATA[<h2>Visit Myrtle Beach&rsquo;s Cyndi Mohr Receives 2024 Associate of the Year Award from South Carolina Society of Association Executives</h2>

<p>MYRTLE BEACH, S.C.&mdash;Visit Myrtle Beach is pleased to announce Cyndi Mohr, senior sales manager, was honored with the prestigious 2024 Associate of the Year Award by the South Carolina Society of Association Executives (SCSAE) during the organization&rsquo;s annual conference, held June 9-11, 2024, in Hilton Head, S.C.</p>

<p>&ldquo;Cyndi has received this award based on her many years of support to SCSAE, and how she represents Myrtle Beach with pride and assists members with all their needs,&rdquo; said Casey Clyburn, SCSAE Executive Director.</p>

<p>The society is dedicated to advancing the professional development of the state&rsquo;s association executives through education, networking and advocacy. Since 1996, the Associate of the Year Award has recognized an outstanding member that demonstrates continuous support of SCSAE programs and involvement in activities.</p>

<p>Mohr joined the Myrtle Beach Area Convention and Visitors Bureau (CVB) group sales department in 2019 and represents Visit Myrtle Beach across the country to implement strategies that welcome meetings and conventions to the destination. According to the CVB, group travel generates a significant benefit to the region, contributing approximately $200 million annually to the local economy.</p>
]]></content>
    <teaser_image_url><![CDATA[https://www.myrtlebeachareachamber.com/img/cache/blog/BlogPosts/686/teaser_image/34836-590-394f-4d22ac6ad028bf35f2a8ff07772b1b94]]></teaser_image_url>
    <teaser_image_alt_text><![CDATA[Cyndi Mohr smiles while holding award.]]></teaser_image_alt_text>
    <categories><![CDATA[News]]></categories>
    <author/>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[2024 Hurricane Forum]]></title>
    <date><![CDATA[2024-06-10 13:12:00]]></date>
    <content><![CDATA[<p style="text-align: center;"><strong>Get Storm Ready at Third Annual Hurricane Connection Forum on June 20</strong></p>

<p style="text-align: center;"><em>Free Event in Myrtle Beach&rsquo;s Market Common to Take Place 10 a.m. &ndash; 1 p.m.</em></p>

<p>MYRTLE BEACH, S.C.&mdash;Hurricane season is upon us and now is the time to get prepared. To help the community know what to expect and how to best deal with a storm, a free forum will be held on Thursday, June 20, 2024. The third annual Hurricane Connection Forum takes place from 10 a.m. to 1 p.m. in Market Common at the Thomas C. Maeser Auditorium on the Horry-Georgetown Technical College - Grand Strand Campus, 950 Crabtree Ln., Myrtle Beach.</p>

<p>The event is presented by Myrtle Beach Area Chamber of Commerce (MBACC), Conway Chamber of Commerce, Little River Chamber of Commerce, Loris Chamber of Commerce and North Myrtle Beah Chamber of Commerce, and is sponsored by Santee Cooper and Southeastern Alliance Underwriters.</p>

<p>&ldquo;The key to facing any storm lies in being prepared,&rdquo; said Karen Riordan, MBACC President and CEO. &ldquo;This open forum is crafted to empower our community members and business stakeholders, guaranteeing they have the necessary information and resources to confront hurricanes effectively. It&rsquo;s crucial for all individuals in the Grand Strand area to develop a well-considered emergency plan, have the necessary supplies and stay informed about available support services ahead of any storm.&rdquo;</p>

<p>The forum&rsquo;s free expo will be open from 10 a.m. to noon. During this time, attendees can meet with representatives from various businesses and organizations that specialize in disaster preparedness and recovery.</p>

<p>Exhibitors include:</p>

<ul>
<li>Advanced Industrial Monitoring (A.I.M)</li>
<li>American Red Cross</li>
<li>At Your Fingertips Organizing</li>
<li>Cape Fear Solar Systems</li>
<li>Carolina Temperature Control</li>
<li>CRM Services</li>
<li>Elite Exteriors</li>
<li>Horry County Emergency Management</li>
<li>US Lawns</li>
<li>Klaus Roofing by Carolina Energy Conservation</li>
<li>Palmetto Protection Films LLC</li>
<li>Paradise Financial Strategies</li>
<li>Restoration 1</li>
<li>Santee Cooper</li>
<li>Southeastern Alliance Underwriters</li>
<li>Spann Roofing &amp; Sheet Metal Inc.</li>
</ul>

<p>From noon to 1 p.m., panel experts will share their insight about this year&rsquo;s hurricane season, which runs June through Nov. 1, and answer audience questions. This year&rsquo;s panelists are WPDE Meteorologist Ed Piotrowski, Sam Hodge, director of Horry County Emergency Management, and Michael Hesbach, executive director with Eastern South Carolina Chapter of the American Red Cross.</p>

<p>Complimentary box lunches will be served. For more information, visit <a href="https://nam12.safelinks.protection.outlook.com/?url=https%3A%2F%2Fweb.myrtlebeachareachamber.com%2Fevents%2FHurricaneConnection%2520Forum-8439%2Fdetails&amp;data=05%7C02%7Cfaith.schmeizl%40visitmyrtlebeach.com%7Cb8d8e2ec82c94189e60408dc8970557e%7C81d417a4e3dd45fc965205e902b9d96e%7C0%7C0%7C638536362872220055%7CUnknown%7CTWFpbGZsb3d8eyJWIjoiMC4wLjAwMDAiLCJQIjoiV2luMzIiLCJBTiI6Ik1haWwiLCJXVCI6Mn0%3D%7C0%7C%7C%7C&amp;sdata=JVTuiyvMI%2FT%2FB1NGBQ0apFrQS7b%2F%2BpA7vDspcJaS8ls%3D&amp;reserved=0">MyrtleBeachAreaChamber.com</a>.</p>

<p style="text-align: center;"># # #</p>

<p><a name="x__Hlk78886154">About Myrtle Beach Area Chamber of Commerce and Convention and Visitors Bureau:</a></p>

<p>Since 1938, the Myrtle Beach Area Chamber of Commerce (MBACC) has stood as the unified voice of the Grand Strand&#39;s business community &mdash; serving Myrtle Beach, North Myrtle Beach, Little River, Loris, Atlantic Beach, Carolina Forest, Conway, Aynor, Socastee, Surfside Beach, Garden City Beach, Murrells Inlet, Litchfield Beach and Pawleys Island. The U.S. Chamber of Commerce has awarded MBACC its five-star accreditation &mdash; one of only a few chambers in South Carolina to earn this distinction. The Myrtle Beach Area Convention and Visitors Bureau (CVB) and its destination marketing arm Visit Myrtle Beach promote tourism through various partnerships and initiatives to advance the economic success of the Grand Strand. For more information, visit <a href="file:///C:/Users/marlane.white/Desktop/PRESS%20RELEASES/DRAFT%20RELEASES/MyrtleBeachAreaChamber.com">MyrtleBeachAreaChamber.com</a>, <a href="https://nam12.safelinks.protection.outlook.com/?url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.myrtlebeachareacvb.com%2F&amp;data=05%7C02%7Cfaith.schmeizl%40visitmyrtlebeach.com%7Cb8d8e2ec82c94189e60408dc8970557e%7C81d417a4e3dd45fc965205e902b9d96e%7C0%7C0%7C638536362872237486%7CUnknown%7CTWFpbGZsb3d8eyJWIjoiMC4wLjAwMDAiLCJQIjoiV2luMzIiLCJBTiI6Ik1haWwiLCJXVCI6Mn0%3D%7C0%7C%7C%7C&amp;sdata=yYzIxN80t1Txo5GGmoneS%2BDNDfYNycvSNpLYpBT473Q%3D&amp;reserved=0">MyrtleBeachAreaCVB.com</a> and <a href="https://nam12.safelinks.protection.outlook.com/?url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.visitmyrtlebeach.com%2F&amp;data=05%7C02%7Cfaith.schmeizl%40visitmyrtlebeach.com%7Cb8d8e2ec82c94189e60408dc8970557e%7C81d417a4e3dd45fc965205e902b9d96e%7C0%7C0%7C638536362872253747%7CUnknown%7CTWFpbGZsb3d8eyJWIjoiMC4wLjAwMDAiLCJQIjoiV2luMzIiLCJBTiI6Ik1haWwiLCJXVCI6Mn0%3D%7C0%7C%7C%7C&amp;sdata=LtvNmV2%2FzRK8VeVuP%2B9NRA6IBWoQPlKPIzhxxHkuryE%3D&amp;reserved=0">VisitMyrtleBeach.com</a>.</p>
]]></content>
    <teaser_image_url><![CDATA[https://www.myrtlebeachareachamber.com/img/cache/blog/BlogPosts/685/teaser_image/34836-590-394f-4d22ac6ad028bf35f2a8ff07772b1b94]]></teaser_image_url>
    <teaser_image_alt_text/>
    <categories><![CDATA[News]]></categories>
    <author/>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Myrtle Beach Area Chamber of Commerce Partners with MUZIKA!]]></title>
    <date><![CDATA[2024-06-07 13:06:00]]></date>
    <content><![CDATA[<p>MYRTLE BEACH, S.C.&mdash;The Myrtle Beach Area Chamber of Commerce is partnering with Varna International&rsquo;s MUZIKA! 2024 Festival to offer free tickets to Broadway Revue, a magical evening of songs from beloved musicals on June 20, 2024, at 7 p.m.</p>

<p>&ldquo;We&rsquo;re thrilled to partner with MUZIKA! once again, as the festival provides our residents and visitors with a unique chance to enjoy world-class performances by students and professional trainers. As a way to experience the festival at no cost, we invite the public to join us on June 20 for a celebration of some of Broadway&rsquo;s greatest hits,&rdquo; said Karen Riordan, MBACC President and CEO.</p>

<p>MUZIKA!&rsquo;s Broadway Revue features Broadway Pianist Alex Lefevre and vocalists from Varna International&rsquo;s opera productions, performing popular songs from top musicals like &ldquo;Phantom of the Opera&rdquo; and &ldquo;Les Mis&eacute;rables.&rdquo;</p>

<p>The performance takes place at Beach Church, 557 George Bishop Pkwy, Myrtle Beach. Doors open at 6:15 p.m. and the show starts at 7 p.m., running 90 minutes with no intermission. Although admission is free, advance seat reservations are required due to the limited space.</p>

<p>MUZIKA!, the 23rd annual Varna International Music Festival in South Carolina, runs June 13-29 and features over a dozen performances across the state, including fully-staged operas, choral and orchestral performances, voice recitals, and chamber music. This is the third year the festival has come to the Grand Strand.</p>

<p><a class="readon" href="https://muzika.ticketspice.com/broadway-revue-muzika---june-20-2024" target="_blank">Get Tickets</a></p>
]]></content>
    <teaser_image_url><![CDATA[https://www.myrtlebeachareachamber.com/img/cache/blog/BlogPosts/683/teaser_image/34836-590-394f-4d22ac6ad028bf35f2a8ff07772b1b94]]></teaser_image_url>
    <teaser_image_alt_text/>
    <categories><![CDATA[News]]></categories>
    <author/>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Leadership Grand Strand Welcomes Shannon Furtick as New Executive Director]]></title>
    <date><![CDATA[2024-05-31 8:50:00]]></date>
    <content><![CDATA[<h2>Leadership Grand Strand Welcomes Shannon Furtick as New Executive Director</h2>

<h3>Diana Greene&rsquo;s Two Decades of Impactful Leadership Commended</h3>

<p>MYRTLE BEACH, S.C.&mdash;Leadership Grand Strand (LGS), a premier leadership development program of the Myrtle Beach Area Chamber of Commerce (MBACC), is pleased to announce Shannon Furtick, IOM, as its new executive director. Furtick succeeds Diana Greene, who is retiring after 19 years of dedicated service to the organization.</p>

<p>Furtick started her career with the chamber in 2008 and currently serves as the business development director of member engagement. She&rsquo;ll continue in that position while starting her duties overseeing LGS on June 3.</p>

<p>&ldquo;We&rsquo;re very excited to see Shannon expand her role at the chamber by carrying on the remarkable legacy that Diana has cultivated over the past two decades at Leadership Grand Strand. Shannon brings a wealth of organizational experience and passion for the community that will carry the program into this new chapter,&rdquo; said Karen Riordan, MBACC President and CEO.</p>

<p>Among Furtick&rsquo;s notable achievements, she graduated from LGS&rsquo;s Class 31 in 2011, completed the U.S. Chamber of Commerce&rsquo;s Institute for Organization Management (IOM) in 2016, was recognized by the Association of Chamber of Commerce Executives&rsquo; 40 Under 40 in 2020, and received Multiplying Good&rsquo;s Jefferson Award in 2022.</p>

<p>&ldquo;I&rsquo;m honored to step into the role of LGS executive director and build upon the foundation laid by Diana and those before her. I look forward to collaborating with our board of regents, alumni, future classes and community partners to advance the LGS mission and make a lasting impact in our community,&rdquo; Furtick said.</p>

<p>Now in its 45th year, LGS has become one of the region&rsquo;s preeminent leadership programs, graduating hundreds of community leaders who have made substantial contributions to the Myrtle Beach area.</p>

<p>&ldquo;It has been a privilege to lead LGS for the past 19 years,&rdquo; Greene said. &ldquo;I&rsquo;m immensely humbled by what the program has achieved and confident that Shannon is the right person to take the helm. Her passion for enhancing the Grand Strand is inspiring, and I&rsquo;m excited to see how she&rsquo;ll elevate the program to new heights,&rdquo; Greene said.</p>

<p>Applications are now being accepted through June 30 for LGS Class 45, which will begin in August. The cost of the program is $1,499 per person and scholarship opportunities are available.</p>

<p>For more information and to apply for the program, visit <a href="https://www.myrtlebeachareachamber.com/leadershipgrandstrand/?utm_source=domain&amp;utm_medium=redirect&amp;utm_campaign=leadershipgrandstrand-com">LeadershipGrandStrand.com</a>.</p>

<p style="text-align: center;"># # #</p>

<p><strong>About Leadership Grand Strand:</strong></p>

<p>The goal of Leadership Grand Strand, a program of the Myrtle Beach Area Chamber of Commerce, is to develop a corps of informed, committed and qualified individuals capable of providing dynamic leadership for the Grand Strand. Over the years, Leadership Grand Strand has created a cadre of leaders who guide the direction of change throughout the Grand Strand. For more information about the program, visit <a href="https://www.myrtlebeachareachamber.com/leadershipgrandstrand">LeadershipGrandStrand.com</a>.</p>
]]></content>
    <teaser_image_url><![CDATA[https://www.myrtlebeachareachamber.com/img/cache/blog/BlogPosts/682/teaser_image/34836-590-394f-4d22ac6ad028bf35f2a8ff07772b1b94]]></teaser_image_url>
    <teaser_image_alt_text><![CDATA[Shannon Furtick Named executive director of leadership grand strand]]></teaser_image_alt_text>
    <categories><![CDATA[MBACC News Release,LGS News]]></categories>
    <author><![CDATA[by Marlane White, Director of Communications]]></author>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Welcome New Members - May 2024]]></title>
    <date><![CDATA[2024-05-30 10:00:00]]></date>
    <content><![CDATA[<p>Myrtle Beach Area Chamber of Commerce encourages investors to do business with other chamber members. Please consider these new stakeholders the next time you have a need for products/services. New member&nbsp;referral? Contact&nbsp;<a href="mailto:Pam.Wright@%20VisitMyrtleBeach.com">Pam Wright</a>, business development manager, 843-916-7220. Need to make changes to business information? Contact&nbsp;<a href="mailto:Amanda.Bailey@VisitMyrtleBeach.com">Amanda Bailey</a>, business development coordinator, 843-916-7205.</p>

<hr />
<p><a href="https://web.myrtlebeachareachamber.com/JanitorialServices/360Clean-31485" target="_blank"><strong>360Clean</strong></a><br />
<em>Janitorial-Services</em><br />
Broderick Dillon<br />
Little River, SC 29566<br />
540-427-8127</p>

<p><a href="https://web.myrtlebeachareachamber.com/Convenience-Stores/7Eleven-31573" target="_blank"><strong>7-Eleven</strong></a><br />
<em>Convenience Stores</em><br />
Brian Mulcahy<br />
8201 N. Kings Hwy.<br />
Myrtle Beach, SC 29572<br />
843-340-1579</p>

<p><a href="https://web.myrtlebeachareachamber.com/Consultants/Alliance-Consulting-Group,-LLC-31486" target="_blank"><strong>Alliance Consulting Group, LLC</strong></a><br />
<em>Consultants</em><br />
Chip Russell<br />
PO Box 30931<br />
Myrtle Beach, SC 29588<br />
843-421-6008</p>

<p><a href="https://web.myrtlebeachareachamber.com/Consultants/Ayres-Advisory-Partners,-LLC-31574" target="_blank"><strong>Ayres Advisory Partners, LLC</strong></a><br />
<em>Consultants</em><br />
Caleb Mancuso<br />
Fayetteville, NC 28303<br />
423-341-0571</p>

<p><a href="https://web.myrtlebeachareachamber.com/Bar-Restaurant/Bar-Louie-23165" target="_blank"><strong>Bar Louie</strong></a><br />
<em>Bar &amp; Restaurant</em><br />
Lucinda Wipf<br />
1318 Celebrity Cir., #183<br />
Myrtle Beach, SC 29577<br />
843-854-8544</p>

<p><a href="https://web.myrtlebeachareachamber.com/Fitness/Beach-Babes-Ladies-Fitness-Center-31483" target="_blank"><strong>Beach Babes Ladies Fitness Center</strong></a><br />
<em>Fitness</em><br />
Valerie Reyes<br />
607 N. Kings Hwy.<br />
Myrtle Beach, SC 29577<br />
832-282-9881<br />
<br />
<a href="https://web.myrtlebeachareachamber.com/Disaster-RestorationFireWaterMold/Blue-Kangaroo-Packoutz-Coastal-Carolinas-31477" target="_blank"><strong>Blue Kangaroo Packoutz Coastal Carolinas</strong></a><br />
<em>Disaster Restoration/Fire/Water/Mold</em><br />
Rachel Hodges<br />
201 East Cox Ferry, Bldg. C<br />
Conway, SC 29526<br />
919-800-7876</p>

<p><a href="https://web.myrtlebeachareachamber.com/HealthWellness/Body-Revolution-Aesthetics-and-Wellness-31575" target="_blank"><strong>Body Revolution Aesthetics and Wellness</strong></a><br />
<em>Health-Wellness</em><br />
Morgan Farrah<br />
1211 48th Ave. N.<br />
Myrtle Beach, SC 29577<br />
843-213-1633</p>

<p><a href="https://web.myrtlebeachareachamber.com/ClothingFamily/Born-United-31495" target="_blank"><strong>Born United</strong></a><br />
<em>Clothing-Family</em><br />
Ashley Sovilla<br />
10835 Kings Rd., Ste. 770<br />
Myrtle Beach, SC 29572<br />
843-804-0644</p>

<p><a href="https://web.myrtlebeachareachamber.com/Restaurant-Italian/Crave-Italian-Oven-Bar-Myrtle-Beach-19615" target="_blank"><strong>Crave Italian Oven &amp; Bar - Myrtle Beach</strong></a><br />
<em>Restaurant - Italian</em><br />
Jill Vaugh<br />
5900 N. Kings Hwy., Ste. B&amp;C<br />
Myrtle Beach, SC 29577<br />
843-213-0500</p>

<p><a href="https://web.myrtlebeachareachamber.com/Restaurant-Italian/Crave-Italian-Oven-Bar-North-Myrtle-Beach-31637" target="_blank"><strong>Crave Italian Oven &amp; Bar - North Myrtle Beach</strong></a><br />
<em>Restaurant - Italian</em><br />
Mike Brinkley<br />
202 Hwy. 17 N.<br />
North Myrtle Beach, SC 29582<br />
843-258-9633</p>

<p><a href="https://web.myrtlebeachareachamber.com/FurnitureOutdoors/Custom-Outdoor-Furniture-Restrapping,-Inc-12164" target="_blank"><strong>Custom Outdoor Furniture &amp; Restrapping, Inc.</strong></a><br />
<em>Furniture-Outdoors-Furniture-Patio Umbrellas</em><br />
Sarah Cox<br />
2415 Hwy. 17 S.<br />
Garden City, SC 29576<br />
843-651-9633</p>

<p><a href="https://web.myrtlebeachareachamber.com/GolfMiniature/Dinosaur-Adventure-Mini-Golf-31590" target="_blank"><strong>Dinosaur Adventure Mini Golf</strong></a><br />
<em>Golf-Miniature</em><br />
Marj Gumapac<br />
701 Hwy. 17 S.<br />
North Myrtle Beach, SC 29582<br />
843-272-8041</p>

<p><a href="https://web.myrtlebeachareachamber.com/WeightLoss/East-Carolina-Weight-Loss-31539" target="_blank"><strong>East Carolina Weight Loss</strong></a><br />
<em>Weight-Loss</em><br />
Karyn Dauwer<br />
2798-D Howard Ave.<br />
Myrtle Beach, SC 29577<br />
339-832-1643</p>

<p><a href="https://web.myrtlebeachareachamber.com/Transportation/Flamingo-Rides-31479" target="_blank"><strong>Flamingo Rides</strong></a><br />
<em>Transportation</em><br />
Terrell Clough<br />
Myrtle Beach, SC 29579<br />
843-274-7250</p>

<p><a href="https://web.myrtlebeachareachamber.com/Senior-Services/Grand-Strand-Comfort-Care-LLC-26815" target="_blank"><strong>Grand Strand Comfort Care LLC</strong></a><br />
<em>Senior Services</em><br />
Asher Rosenberg<br />
2411 N. Oak St., Ste. 104<br />
Myrtle Beach, SC 29577<br />
843-626-2613</p>

<p><a href="https://web.myrtlebeachareachamber.com/Consultants/Hop2it-Consulting-31576" target="_blank"><strong>Hop2it Consulting</strong></a><br />
<em>Consultants</em><br />
Dan Hoppe<br />
304 Maximus Ct.<br />
Myrtle Beach, SC 29588<br />
419-205-1659<br />
<br />
<a href="https://web.myrtlebeachareachamber.com/Services/HOTELhelp,-Inc-31489" target="_blank"><strong>HOTELhelp, Inc.</strong></a><br />
<em>Services</em><br />
Nancy Lee<br />
Charlotte, NC 28209<br />
843-957-8628</p>

<p><a href="https://web.myrtlebeachareachamber.com/Restaurant-Coffee-House/Island-Vibez-Cafe-and-Coffeehouse-31451" target="_blank"><strong>Island Vibez Cafe and Coffeehouse</strong></a><br />
<em>Restaurant - Coffee House</em><br />
Dr. Rechel&nbsp; Anderson<br />
533 Broadway St.<br />
Myrtle Beach, SC 29577<br />
704-779-5727<br />
<br />
<a href="https://web.myrtlebeachareachamber.com/Restaurant-Italian/Little-Italy-Myrtle-Beach-Italian-Restaurant-and-Pizzeria-31472" target="_blank"><strong>Little Italy Myrtle Beach - Italian Restaurant and Pizzeria</strong></a><br />
<em>Restaurant - Italian</em><br />
Alina Zyma<br />
3001 N. Kings Hwy., Unit G<br />
Myrtle Beach, SC 29577<br />
843-213-1403</p>

<p><a href="https://web.myrtlebeachareachamber.com/GolfMiniature/Lost-Treasure-Mini-Golf-31589" target="_blank"><strong>Lost Treasure Mini Golf</strong></a><br />
<em>Golf-Miniature</em><br />
Austin Green<br />
1705 Hwy. 17 S.<br />
North Myrtle Beach, SC 29582<br />
843-272-5467</p>

<p><a href="https://web.myrtlebeachareachamber.com/GolfMiniature/Mayday-Golf-31591" target="_blank"><strong>Mayday Golf</strong></a><br />
<em>Golf-Miniature</em><br />
Rodney Milliken<br />
715 Hwy. 17 N.<br />
North Myrtle Beach, SC 29582<br />
843-280-3535<br />
<br />
<a href="https://web.myrtlebeachareachamber.com/DeliveryServices/Mountain-Logistics-LLC-31476" target="_blank"><strong>Mountain Logistics LLC</strong></a><br />
<em>Delivery-Services</em><br />
Brandon Shockley<br />
Myrtle Beach, SC 29577<br />
843-948-0039</p>

<p><a href="https://web.myrtlebeachareachamber.com/EngineersConsulting/Providence-Engineering-(South-Carolina-Office)-31567" target="_blank"><strong>Providence Engineering South Carolina Office-</strong></a><br />
<em>Engineers-Consulting</em><br />
Jessel Elliott<br />
Myrtle Beach, SC 29579<br />
843-220-0990</p>

<p><a href="https://web.myrtlebeachareachamber.com/LandscapeServices/PureGreen-Land-Group-31561" target="_blank"><strong>PureGreen Land Group</strong></a><br />
<em>Landscape-Services</em><br />
Kate Kapshuck<br />
Longs, SC 29568<br />
843-816-3287</p>

<p><a href="https://web.myrtlebeachareachamber.com/BeachAccessories-and-Supplies/Seaside-Mobility-31492" target="_blank"><strong>Seaside Mobility</strong></a><br />
<em>Beach-Accessories and Supplies</em><br />
Kevin Higgins<br />
Conway, SC 29526<br />
843-251-8688</p>

<p><a href="https://web.myrtlebeachareachamber.com/Ice-CreamFrozen-Desserts/The-Dolly-Llama-31566" target="_blank"><strong>The Dolly Llama</strong></a><br />
<em>Ice Cream-Frozen Desserts</em><br />
Liliana Vasquez<br />
505 9th Ave. N.<br />
Myrtle Beach, SC 29577<br />
610-428-6460</p>

<p><a href="https://web.myrtlebeachareachamber.com/MedicalServices/Trial-Management-Associates-31497" target="_blank"><strong>Trial Management Associates</strong></a><br />
<em>Medical-Services</em><br />
Philip Dattilo<br />
945 82nd Pkwy., 2nd Floor<br />
Myrtle Beach, SC 29572<br />
843-994-7655</p>

<p><a href="https://web.myrtlebeachareachamber.com/Restaurant-Mexican/Tu-Taco-Conway-31624" target="_blank"><strong>Tu Taco - Conway</strong></a><br />
<em>Restaurant - Mexican</em><br />
Eddie Vizcarra<br />
201 Graduate Rd., #107<br />
Conway, SC 29526<br />
843-331-1263<br />
<br />
<a href="https://web.myrtlebeachareachamber.com/Department-Stores/Walmart-Supercenter-Surfside-Beach-13904" target="_blank"><strong>Walmart Supercenter - Surfside Beach</strong></a><br />
<em>Department Stores</em><br />
Mike Lombardi<br />
2751 Beaver Run Blvd.<br />
Surfside Beach, SC 29575<br />
843-650-4800</p>

<p><a href="https://web.myrtlebeachareachamber.com/HealthWellness/Yoga-In-Common-31478" target="_blank"><strong>Yoga In Common</strong></a><br />
<em>Health-Wellness</em><br />
Solange Cheng<br />
3062 Deville St.<br />
Myrtle Beach, SC 29577<br />
843-839-9636</p>
]]></content>
    <teaser_image_url><![CDATA[https://www.myrtlebeachareachamber.com/img/cache/blog/BlogPosts/681/teaser_image/34836-590-394f-4d22ac6ad028bf35f2a8ff07772b1b94]]></teaser_image_url>
    <teaser_image_alt_text><![CDATA[Welcome New Members- May 2024]]></teaser_image_alt_text>
    <categories><![CDATA[New Members]]></categories>
    <author/>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Ways to Help Myrtle Beach Nonprofits - May 2024]]></title>
    <date><![CDATA[2024-05-22 9:43:00]]></date>
    <content><![CDATA[<p>In an effort to support the many Grand Strand nonprofits on their missions to supporting the community, Myrtle Beach Area Chamber of Commerce is publishing this monthly roundup of our nonprofit members current needs.</p>

<p>If you&rsquo;re looking to get involved or give back, consider supporting the nonprofits below or in&nbsp;the chamber&rsquo;s&nbsp;<a href="https://web.myrtlebeachareachamber.com/Nonprofit" target="_blank">business directory.</a></p>

<hr />
<p><a href="https://web.myrtlebeachareachamber.com/Nonprofit/Eagle-Cold-Case-and-Missing-Persons-Institute-(ECCMPI)-28228" target="_blank"><strong>Eagle Cold Case</strong></a> seeks donations to support their work assisting families of unsolved death/missing persons cases.</p>

<p><a href="https://web.myrtlebeachareachamber.com/Nonprofit/Gifts-From-the-Heart-23067" target="_blank"><strong>Gifts from the Heart</strong></a> is looking for items to fill baskets for seniors in the Myrtle Beach area. Items needed include: shampoo, conditioner, toothbrushes, toothpaste, blankets, hand soap, tissues, socks, soft baby dolls or stuffed animals, soft candy/chocolate, puzzles with large pieces.</p>

<p><a href="https://web.myrtlebeachareachamber.com/Nonprofit/Palmetto-Literacy-Council-23209" target="_blank"><strong>Palmetto Literacy Council</strong></a> seeks sponsors and raffle donations for their golf scramble on June 8. The nonprofit also is looking for volunteers to tutor students two hours per week at the library. Learn more by calling 843-945-9278.</p>

<p><a href="https://web.myrtlebeachareachamber.com/Nonprofit/SOS-Care-4032" target="_blank"><strong>SOS Care</strong></a> seeks items for summer programs including pool noodles and floats, diving toys, water toys, water blasters and a volleyball net.</p>

<p><strong><a href="https://web.myrtlebeachareachamber.com/Nonprofit/South-Carolina-Mental-Health-for-Heroes-30226" target="_blank">South Carolina Mental Health for Heroes</a></strong>&nbsp;is looking for sponsors who want to support the mental health veterans, first responders, healthcare professionals and their families. Sponsorships begin at $2,500.</p>

<p>&nbsp;</p>

<p><a href="https://web.myrtlebeachareachamber.com/Nonprofit/Go-Get-Your-You-Foundation-27566"><strong>The Go Get Your You Foundation</strong></a> is looking for sponsors&nbsp;to help pay speaker fees for their Juneteenth festival in Conway. People also can shop their <a href="https://www.walmart.com/registry/RR/d6228f46-b5ce-4703-83e0-98f2037b915a" target="_blank">festival registry</a>.</p>

<p><a href="https://web.myrtlebeachareachamber.com/Nonprofit/The-Humane-Society-of-North-Myrtle-Beach-23483" target="_blank"><strong>The Humane Society of North Myrtle Beach</strong></a> needs foster families for medium to large dogs (over 40 lbs). Fostering gives&nbsp;these dogs a chance to decompress and thrive and frees&nbsp;up space in the shelter for other animals in need. Learn more and <a href="https://humanesocietynmb.org/be-a-foster-caregiver/">submit a foster application</a>. Additionally their wish list of donations includes:&nbsp;Purina Cat Chow,&nbsp;cat litter, hard chew toys for dogs, Pup-Peroni dog treats, paper towels, cardboard cat scratcher pads, multipurpose copy paper, Churu lickable cat treats.</p>

<p><a href="https://web.myrtlebeachareachamber.com/Nonprofit/The-Period-Project-26714" target="_blank"><strong>The Period Project</strong></a> is celebrating Period Poverty Awareness Week May 20-28 with a donation drive. Donations of menstrual products will be accepted at Lucid Coast Candle Bar. Donated supplies will be given to Horry County students for their summer needs.</p>

<hr />
<p><a href="https://web.myrtlebeachareachamber.com/events?ce=true" target="_blank">VIEW NONPROFIT &amp; COMMUNITY EVENTS</a></p>

<p>Want to be on this list? <a href="https://www.myrtlebeachareachamber.com/nonprofit-organizations">Learn</a> how nonprofits can share their current needs.</p>
]]></content>
    <teaser_image_url><![CDATA[https://www.myrtlebeachareachamber.com/img/cache/blog/BlogPosts/680/teaser_image/34836-590-394f-4d22ac6ad028bf35f2a8ff07772b1b94]]></teaser_image_url>
    <teaser_image_alt_text><![CDATA[Ways to Help Myrtle Beach Nonprofits - May 2024]]></teaser_image_alt_text>
    <categories><![CDATA[News]]></categories>
    <author><![CDATA[by Amanda Blomquist, Business Development Marketing Manager]]></author>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Hop2it Consulting to Provide Leadership Training for Leadership Grand Strand]]></title>
    <date><![CDATA[2024-05-17 11:07:00]]></date>
    <content><![CDATA[<h1>Hop2it Consulting to Provide Leadership Training for Leadership Grand Strand</h1>

<p>MYRTLE BEACH, S.C.&mdash;Leadership Grand Strand (LGS), a program of the Myrtle Beach Area Chamber of Commerce, is pleased to announce Dr.&rsquo;s Dan and Heather Hoppe of Hop2it Consulting have been selected to provide leadership training for the program&rsquo;s upcoming classes.<a href="https://www.myrtlebeachareachamber.com/leadershiptrainer" target="_blank"><img alt="Leadership Trainer Hop2it Consulting" src="/img/cache/lib24watch/Lib24watchFiles/1954/lib24watch_file/0-291e661adb04d1d1b6ff5b57f85faf16" style="width: 300px; height: 300px; margin: 10px; float: left;" /></a></p>

<p>Together, the Hoppe&rsquo;s have more than 40 years of combined experience in higher education, nonprofit management and business. Dan holds a Doctor of Education in Leadership Studies and has spent the last 24 years in higher education leadership, nonprofit management and business entrepreneurship. Heather earned her Doctor of Philosophy in Educational Leadership and has spent the last 25 years working as a leader and consultant in higher education.</p>

<p>&ldquo;We&rsquo;re truly honored and excited to have been chosen to serve as the leadership trainers for Leadership Grand Strand. As alumni&nbsp;of this beloved program, we look forward to sharing our wisdom and mentoring the amazing leaders we have here in the Grand Strand,&rdquo; said Dan Hoppe, president, Hop2it Consulting.</p>

<p>LGS provides transformative leadership training activities and exclusive behind-the-scenes tours of Grand Strand institutions in order to cultivate a dynamic corps of individuals who are well informed, committed and exceptionally qualified.</p>

<p><a href="https://www.myrtlebeachareachamber.com/applicationprocess" target="_blank">Applications are now being accepted</a> through June 30 for Class 45, which will begin in August. The cost of the program is $1,499 per person and scholarship opportunities are available.</p>

<p>For more information and to apply for the program, visit LeadershipGrandStrand.com.</p>

<p style="text-align: center;"># # #</p>

<p><strong>About Leadership Grand Strand:</strong></p>

<p>The goal of Leadership Grand Strand, a program of the Myrtle Beach Area Chamber of Commerce, is to develop a corps of informed, committed and qualified individuals capable of providing dynamic leadership for the Grand Strand. Over the years, Leadership Grand Strand has created a cadre of leaders who guide the direction of change throughout the Grand Strand. For more information about the program, visit LeadershipGrandStrand.com.</p>

<p><strong>About Hop2it Consulting:</strong></p>

<p>Hop2it Consulting is a small professional consulting firm, focused on meeting the individualized needs of business and educational organizations. Dr.&rsquo;s Dan and Heather Hoppe started Hop2it Consulting with one thing in mind, offering customized professional consulting and training services to companies, educational institutions, and nonprofit organizations. Together, the Hoppe&rsquo;s have over 40 years of experience in higher education, non-profit management, and business. Dan completed his Ed.D. in Leadership Studies and has spent the last 24 years in higher education leadership, non-profit management, and business entrepreneurship. Heather received her Ph.D. in Education Leadership and has spent the last 25 years working as a leader and consultant in higher education.</p>
]]></content>
    <teaser_image_url><![CDATA[https://www.myrtlebeachareachamber.com/img/cache/blog/BlogPosts/679/teaser_image/34836-590-394f-4d22ac6ad028bf35f2a8ff07772b1b94]]></teaser_image_url>
    <teaser_image_alt_text><![CDATA[Hop2it Consulting to Provide Leadership Training for Leadership Grand Strand]]></teaser_image_alt_text>
    <categories><![CDATA[LGS News]]></categories>
    <author/>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[TD Bank to Provide Chamber Memberships to Five Minority-Owned Businesses]]></title>
    <date><![CDATA[2024-05-15 9:08:00]]></date>
    <content><![CDATA[<h1>TD Bank to Provide Free Chamber Memberships to Five Minority-Owned Businesses</h1>

<h3>Deadline To Apply Is May 31, 2024</h3>

<p>MYRTLE BEACH, S.C.&mdash;The Myrtle Beach Area Chamber of Commerce (MBACC) is partnering with TD Bank, America&rsquo;s Most Convenient Bank, to award complimentary chamber memberships to five minority-owned businesses.</p>

<p>In a continuing effort to engage and support minority businesses, TD Bank is sponsoring the cost of one year&rsquo;s membership dues for five Myrtle Beach area businesses that are at least 51 percent owned by a minority. The selected business owners and their employees will have full access to all benefits of chamber membership, including a listing in the business directory, online job postings, discounts through money-saving programs, and access to networking events and education classes.</p>

<p>&ldquo;We&rsquo;re thrilled to partner with TD Bank to offer these membership opportunities and provide the selected businesses with the advantages of being a Myrtle Beach Area Chamber member, including networking and educational events,&rdquo; said Karen Riordan, MBACC President and CEO.</p>

<p>To qualify, the business must be 51 percent or more owned by a minority, marginalized or underrepresented demographic such as: Black or African American, Hispanic, Native American, Asian-Pacific, Subcontinent Asian, woman, veteran or disabled person. In addition, the business must be located in Horry or Georgetown counties, legally operating for at least one month and cannot be a current investor with the chamber.</p>

<p>Businesses that meet the parameters will be entered into a drawing and selected at random. The deadline to enter is May 31, 2024, and the selected businesses will be notified no later than June 15.</p>

<p>The entry form and more information can be found online at <a href="https://www.myrtlebeachareachamber.com/membership-contest" target="_blank">MyrtleBeachAreaChamber.com/membership-contest</a>.</p>

<p style="text-align: center;"># # #</p>

<p><strong>About Myrtle Beach Area Chamber of Commerce and Convention and Visitors Bureau:</strong></p>

<p>Since 1938, the Myrtle Beach Area Chamber of Commerce (MBACC) has stood as the unified voice of the Grand Strand&#39;s business community &mdash; serving Myrtle Beach, North Myrtle Beach, Little River, Loris, Atlantic Beach, Carolina Forest, Conway, Aynor, Socastee, Surfside Beach, Garden City Beach, Murrells Inlet, Litchfield Beach and Pawleys Island. The U.S. Chamber of Commerce has awarded MBACC its five-star accreditation &mdash; one of only a few chambers in South Carolina to earn this distinction. The Myrtle Beach Area Convention and Visitors Bureau (CVB) and its destination marketing arm Visit Myrtle Beach promote tourism through various partnerships and initiatives to advance the economic success of the Grand Strand. For more information, visit MyrtleBeachAreaChamber.com, MyrtleBeachAreaCVB.com and VisitMyrtleBeach.com.</p>

<p><strong>About TD Bank, America&#39;s Most Convenient Bank&reg;</strong></p>

<p>TD Bank, America&#39;s Most Convenient Bank, is one of the 10 largest banks in the U.S., providing more than 9.7 million customers with a full range of retail, small business and commercial banking products and services at more than 1,100 convenient locations throughout the Northeast, Mid-Atlantic, Metro D.C., the Carolinas and Florida. In addition, TD Bank and its subsidiaries offer customized private banking and wealth management services through TD Wealth&reg;, and vehicle financing and dealer commercial services through TD Auto Finance. TD Bank is headquartered in Cherry Hill, N.J. To learn more, visit www.td.com/us. Find TD Bank on Facebook at&nbsp;facebook.com/TDBank and on Twitter at twitter.com/TDBank_US and twitter.com/TDNews_US.</p>

<p>TD Bank, America&#39;s Most Convenient Bank, is a member of TD Bank Group and a subsidiary of The Toronto-Dominion Bank of Toronto, Canada, a top 10 financial services company in North America. The Toronto-Dominion Bank trades on the New York and Toronto stock exchanges under the ticker symbol &quot;TD.&quot;&nbsp;To learn more, visit www.td.com/us.</p>
]]></content>
    <teaser_image_url><![CDATA[https://www.myrtlebeachareachamber.com/img/cache/blog/BlogPosts/678/teaser_image/34836-590-394f-4d22ac6ad028bf35f2a8ff07772b1b94]]></teaser_image_url>
    <teaser_image_alt_text/>
    <categories><![CDATA[News]]></categories>
    <author><![CDATA[by Marlane White, Director of Communications]]></author>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Welcome New Members - April 2024]]></title>
    <date><![CDATA[2024-04-30 8:56:00]]></date>
    <content><![CDATA[<p>Myrtle Beach Area Chamber of Commerce encourages investors to do business with other chamber members. Please consider these new stakeholders the next time you have a need for products/services. New member&nbsp;referral? Contact&nbsp;<a href="mailto:Pam.Wright@%20VisitMyrtleBeach.com">Pam Wright</a>, business development manager, 843-916-7220. Need to make changes to business information? Contact&nbsp;<a href="mailto:Amanda.Bailey@VisitMyrtleBeach.com">Amanda Bailey</a>, business development coordinator, 843-916-7205.</p>

<hr />
<p><a href="https://web.myrtlebeachareachamber.com/Restaurant-Family/Anchor-Bar-of-Myrtle-Beach-31291" target="_blank"><strong>Anchor Bar of Myrtle Beach</strong></a><br />
<em>Restaurant - Family</em><br />
Bob Kroon<br />
6401 N. Kings Hwy.<br />
Myrtle Beach, SC 29572<br />
716-932-7228</p>

<p><a href="https://web.myrtlebeachareachamber.com/Financial/Carolinas-Wealth-Management-31339" target="_blank"><strong>Carolinas Wealth Management</strong></a><br />
<em>Financial</em><br />
Lauryn Harbour<br />
4481 Oleander Dr., Ste. 1B<br />
Myrtle Beach, SC 29577<br />
843-497-8505</p>

<p><a href="https://web.myrtlebeachareachamber.com/Fishing-BoatsCharterHeadboats/Coastal-Marsh-Adventures-31330" target="_blank"><strong>Coastal Marsh Adventures</strong></a><br />
<em>Fishing Boats-Charter/Headboats</em><br />
Chris Bowden<br />
4495 Baker St.<br />
Little River, SC 29566<br />
304-807-7577</p>

<p><a href="https://web.myrtlebeachareachamber.com/Flooring/Floors-and-More,-LLC-31408" target="_blank"><strong>Floors and More, LLC</strong></a><br />
<em>Flooring</em><br />
Tyler Bischoff<br />
Myrtle Beach, SC 29577<br />
843-213-1861</p>

<p><a href="https://web.myrtlebeachareachamber.com/HotelMotel/Hampton-Inn-Northwood-1196" target="_blank"><strong>Hampton Inn Northwood</strong></a><br />
<em>Hotel-Motel</em><br />
Erik Reis<br />
620 75th Ave. N.<br />
Myrtle Beach, SC 29572<br />
843-497-0077</p>

<p><a href="https://web.myrtlebeachareachamber.com/LandscapeServices/Hardhat-Landscaping-31324" target="_blank"><strong>Hardhat Landscaping</strong></a><br />
<em>Landscape-Services</em><br />
Cody Schilawski<br />
5180 Hwy. 17 S., Ste. D<br />
Murrells Inlet, SC 29576<br />
843-421-3590</p>

<p><a href="https://web.myrtlebeachareachamber.com/Jewelry/Jewelers-at-Saint-James-31321" target="_blank"><strong>Jewelers at Saint James</strong></a><br />
<em>Jewelry</em><br />
Carlos El Cid<br />
3542 St. James Ave.<br />
Myrtle Beach, SC 29577<br />
843-848-4688</p>

<p><a href="https://web.myrtlebeachareachamber.com/Nonprofit/Kiwanis-Club-of-Myrtle-Beach-31310" target="_blank"><strong>Kiwanis Club of Myrtle Beach</strong></a><br />
<em>Nonprofit</em><br />
Don Gesick<br />
1169 Seaboard St.<br />
Myrtle Beach, SC 29577<br />
843-450-8393</p>

<p><a href="https://web.myrtlebeachareachamber.com/CoachingBusinessPersonal/Kris-Cala-Coaching-31359" target="_blank"><strong>Kris Cala Coaching</strong></a><br />
<em>Coaching-Business/Personal</em><br />
Kris Cala<br />
PO Box 50984<br />
Myrtle Beach, SC 29579<br />
843-242-7028</p>

<p><a href="https://web.myrtlebeachareachamber.com/Restaurant-Mexican/Los-Cabos-Mexican-Grill-and-Cantina-31322" target="_blank"><strong>Los Cabos Mexican Grill and Cantina</strong></a><br />
<em>Restaurant - Mexican</em><br />
Mario Ruiz<br />
670 Hwy. 17 Business<br />
Surfside Beach, SC 29575<br />
843-213-1401</p>

<p><a href="https://web.myrtlebeachareachamber.com/Nonprofit/LPGA-Amateur-Golf-Association-Myrtle-Beach-31300" target="_blank"><strong>LPGA Amateur Golf Association - Myrtle Beach</strong></a><br />
<em>Nonprofit</em><br />
Jaime Costanzo<br />
Conway, SC 29526<br />
732-904-6854</p>

<p><a href="https://web.myrtlebeachareachamber.com/Roofing-Services/Maverick-Metal-Roof-Supply-31329" target="_blank"><strong>Maverick Metal Roof Supply</strong></a><br />
<em>Roofing Services</em><br />
Darius Gordyk<br />
6285 Dick Pond Rd.<br />
Myrtle Beach, SC 29588<br />
843-902-6287</p>

<p><a href="https://web.myrtlebeachareachamber.com/Painter/McRae-Painting-Carpentry-31103" target="_blank"><strong>McRae Painting Carpentry</strong></a><br />
<em>Painter</em><br />
David McRae<br />
Conway, SC 29526<br />
843-655-6206</p>

<p><a href="https://web.myrtlebeachareachamber.com/Property-Management/Ohana%27s-Oasis-31323" target="_blank"><strong>Ohana&#39;s Oasis</strong></a><br />
<em>Property Management</em><br />
Cody Schilawski<br />
5180 Hwy. 17 S., Ste. D<br />
Murrells Inlet, SC 29576<br />
843-947-0062</p>

<p><a href="https://web.myrtlebeachareachamber.com/Apartments/Pegasus-Residential-Encore-Luxury-Residences-31320" target="_blank"><strong>Pegasus Residential- Encore Luxury Residences</strong></a><br />
<em>Apartments</em><br />
Johna Hill<br />
111 Teal Cir.<br />
Little River, SC 29566<br />
843-798-7819</p>

<p><a href="https://web.myrtlebeachareachamber.com/Nonprofit/PFLAG-Pawleys-Island-31309" target="_blank"><strong>PFLAG Pawleys Island</strong></a><br />
<em>Nonprofit</em><br />
Mark Bayer<br />
Pawleys Island, SC 29585<br />
843-999-0177</p>

<p><a href="https://web.myrtlebeachareachamber.com/Senior-Living-Services/Prime-Carolina-Coast-31326" target="_blank"><strong>Prime Carolina Coast</strong></a><br />
<em>Senior Living Services</em><br />
Alice Roberts<br />
209 Wild Wing Blvd.<br />
Conway, SC 29526<br />
843-279-5617</p>

<p><a href="https://web.myrtlebeachareachamber.com/AdvertisingRadio/Radio-El-Gallo-31314" target="_blank"><strong>Radio El Gallo</strong></a><br />
<em>Advertising-Radio</em><br />
Alberto Torres<br />
4337 Big Barn Dr.<br />
Little River, SC 29566<br />
843-900-1288</p>

<p><a href="https://web.myrtlebeachareachamber.com/Rental-Equipment/Sand-Savvy-Rentals-31301" target="_blank"><strong>Sand Savvy Rentals</strong></a><br />
<em>Rental Equipment</em><br />
Wrenn Smith<br />
Wake Forest, NC 27587<br />
919-796-3225</p>

<p><a href="https://web.myrtlebeachareachamber.com/CarpetRugUpholstery-Cleaner/Shelby-Restoration-and-Carpet-Care-31095" target="_blank"><strong>Shelby Restoration and Carpet Care</strong></a><br />
<em>Carpet-Rug/Upholstery Cleaner</em><br />
Laura Mullaney<br />
Myrtle Beach, SC 29579<br />
843-360-1169</p>

<p><a href="https://web.myrtlebeachareachamber.com/Nonprofit/Softtoe-Entertainment-and-Dance-Production,-Inc-25421" target="_blank"><strong>Softtoe Entertainment and Dance Production, Inc.</strong></a><br />
<em>Nonprofit</em><br />
Curtis Platt<br />
Lorton, VA 22079<br />
443-655-6599</p>

<p><a href="https://web.myrtlebeachareachamber.com/Nonprofit/Sons-and-Daughters-of-Italy-Murrells-Inlet-Lodge-3006-31308" target="_blank"><strong>Sons and Daughters of Italy Murrells Inlet Lodge #3006</strong></a><br />
<em>Nonprofit</em><br />
Robert Paniccia<br />
PO Box 2143<br />
Murrells Inlet, SC 29576<br />
843-299-1813</p>

<p><a href="https://web.myrtlebeachareachamber.com/Transportation/Southern-Charm-Limousine-30543" target="_blank"><strong>Southern Charm Limousine</strong></a><br />
<em>Transportation</em><br />
Amanda Barnes<br />
PO Box 1411<br />
Murrells Inlet, SC 29576<br />
405-979-0131</p>

<p><a href="https://web.myrtlebeachareachamber.com/HomeDecor/The-Vision-You-31333" target="_blank"><strong>The Vision You</strong></a><br />
<em>Home-Decor</em><br />
Kamila Reichelt<br />
Myrtle Beach, SC 29588<br />
843-999-2131</p>

<p><a href="https://web.myrtlebeachareachamber.com/LandscapeServices/US-Lawns-31303" target="_blank"><strong>U.S. Lawns</strong></a><br />
<em>Landscape-Services</em><br />
Jennifer Reed<br />
7887 Moss Creek Rd.<br />
Myrtle Beach, SC 29588<br />
843-650-8875</p>
]]></content>
    <teaser_image_url><![CDATA[https://www.myrtlebeachareachamber.com/img/cache/blog/BlogPosts/676/teaser_image/34836-590-394f-4d22ac6ad028bf35f2a8ff07772b1b94]]></teaser_image_url>
    <teaser_image_alt_text><![CDATA[Welcome New Members - April 2024]]></teaser_image_alt_text>
    <categories><![CDATA[New Members]]></categories>
    <author/>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Myrtle Beach Area Chamber of Commerce and CVB Celebrates Achievements, Recognizes Award Winners During 85th Annual Meeting]]></title>
    <date><![CDATA[2024-04-26 14:57:00]]></date>
    <content><![CDATA[<p>MYRTLE BEACH, S.C.&mdash;The Myrtle Beach Area Chamber of Commerce (MBACC) and Convention and Visitors Bureau (CVB) held its 85<sup>th</sup>&nbsp;annual meeting on April 25, 2024, at the Hilton Myrtle Beach Resort. The event was an opportunity for the chamber&rsquo;s members, board of directors and staff to celebrate achievements from last year as well as honor those who worked to make their community stronger.</p>

<p>&ldquo;This year, the chamber celebrates 86 years of serving the Grand Strand and our annual meeting provided the prime opportunity to mark the occasion and affirm our commitment to promoting, protecting and improving the business community at The Beach. We are very proud of the accomplishments and pleased to honor the distinguished local businesses and individuals who exemplify the chamber&rsquo;s mission,&rdquo; said Karen Riordan, MBACC and CVB President and CEO.</p>

<p>In 2023, the chamber and CVB surpassed its membership goals by holding a 94 percent member retention rate and welcoming 401 new members. In addition, Grand Strand Young Professionals increased its membership by 26 percent.</p>

<p>Additional accomplishments for 2023 included:</p>

<ul type="disc">
<li>Committing to member development by holding 290 events, including 144 ribbon-cutting ceremonies and 46 networking events;</li>
<li>Improving community sustainability by adding an EV charging station through a Santee Cooper grant, hosting 11 Keep Myrtle Beach Beautiful cleanups and being recognized by Keep America Beautiful with a President&rsquo;s Circle Recognition Award;</li>
<li>Debuting the first season of the hit &ldquo;Cooking Channel&rdquo; show &ldquo;Chef Swap at The Beach,&rdquo; which was viewed in more than 600,000 homes, and</li>
<li>Receiving a Chamber of the Year award from the Carolinas Association of Chamber Executives.</li>
</ul>

<p>The following professionals and businesses were honored:</p>

<ul type="disc">
<li>Mark and Jennifer Kiskunas, Citizens of the Year, presented by A&amp;I Fire and Water Restoration</li>
<li>Diane DeVaughn Stokes, Ashby Ward Pioneer of the Year, presented by Carolina Cool</li>
<li>The Lovely Law Firm, Small Business of the Year, presented by Carolina Limousine &amp; Coach</li>
<li>Barnabas Horse Foundation, Nonprofit of the Year, presented by United Bank</li>
<li>Tom Narducci, Chamber Ambassador of the Year, presented by Four Star Plumbing &amp; Air Conditioning</li>
<li>Michelle Griffin, Volunteer of the Year, presented by The Lovely Law Firm</li>
<li>Akeem Hemingway, Champion of Diversity</li>
<li>Project Golf, Business Innovation Award, presented by CRM Services</li>
<li>Weston Dowell of Palmetto Hospitality Services, Entrepreneur of the Year, presented by Truist</li>
<li>Pet Wants South Myrtle, Community Service Award, presented by The Soto Sawyer Crosby Group of Merrill Lynch</li>
<li>Hager Vaught of the Dayton House Resort, Hospitality Employee of the Year, presented by Best Western Ocean Sands and myBeach Vacations.</li>
<li>Shanon Detzler, Leadership Grand Strand&rsquo;s Ann DeBock Leadership Award</li>
<li>Stephanie Warren, Grand Strand Young Professional&rsquo;s Ambassador of the Year</li>
<li>Olivia Elswick, Grand Strand Young Professional&rsquo;s Young Professional of the Year</li>
</ul>

<p>In addition, 18 local high school seniors from 14 area schools were recognized for their leadership and accomplishments through the chamber&rsquo;s Educational Scholarship Foundation and contributions from local business, including Ron Jon Surf Shop. A total of $29,000 in scholarships was awarded to the following recipients:</p>

<p>&nbsp;</p>

<ul type="disc">
<li>Academy for Arts, Science and Technology: Lindsey Beam</li>
<li>Academy for Technology &amp; Academics: Peyton Basso</li>
<li>Aynor High School: Kinley Jones</li>
<li>Carolina Forest High School: Alexa Halling</li>
<li>Conway High School: Derek Grant</li>
<li>Early College High School: Faith Mercer</li>
<li>Green Sea Floyds High School: Eric Crawford, Jr.</li>
<li>HCS Scholars Academy: Jacob Mijalli</li>
<li>Loris High School: Aubrey Anderson</li>
<li>Myrtle Beach High School: Macie McMillan, Amari Rhodes &amp; Maura Wilson</li>
<li>North Myrtle Beach High School: Shaw Ashley, Jessica Nguyen &amp; Gracelyn Tester</li>
<li>Socastee High School: Ava LiVigni</li>
<li>St. James High School: Justin Williams</li>
<li>Waccamaw High School: Grace Gibson</li>
</ul>

<p>The annual meeting was made possible through the following sponsors: BlueCross BlueShield of South Carolina, Santee Cooper, A&amp;I Fire &amp; Water Restoration, Carolina Cool, HTC, The Lovely Law Firm, myBeach Vacation Rentals, Best Western Ocean Sands, Carolina Limousine and Coach, CRM Services, Four Star Plumbing &amp; Air Conditioning, The Soto Sawyer Crosby Group at Merrill Lynch, Truist, United Bank, Boys &amp; Girls Club of the Grand Strand, Brookgreen Gardens, Carolina Trust Federal Credit Union, Dayton House Resort, Golf Tourism Solutions, Hickey&rsquo;s Interactive Adventures, Horry-Georgetown Technical College Foundation Inc., KingOne Properties International, Marriot Resort Myrtle Beach Grande Dunes, ProjectGolf.org Myrtle Beach, Synovus, Tidelands Health with MUSC Health, Waccamaw Community Foundation, MyHorryNews.com, and Coastal Engravers.</p>
]]></content>
    <teaser_image_url><![CDATA[https://www.myrtlebeachareachamber.com/img/cache/blog/BlogPosts/677/teaser_image/34836-590-394f-4d22ac6ad028bf35f2a8ff07772b1b94]]></teaser_image_url>
    <teaser_image_alt_text/>
    <categories><![CDATA[News]]></categories>
    <author/>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[31 Local Professionals Graduate Leadership Grand Strand on May 3]]></title>
    <date><![CDATA[2024-04-20 11:38:00]]></date>
    <content><![CDATA[<h2>31 Local Professionals Graduate Leadership Grand Strand on May 3</h2>

<p>MYRTLE BEACH, S.C.&mdash;Leadership Grand Strand (LGS), a program of the Myrtle Beach Area Chamber of Commerce, will hold a graduation ceremony on Friday, May 3, 2024, for its 44th program class. During the ceremony, 31 professionals from across the Grand Strand will be awarded the coveted LGS diploma after completing the nine-month program.</p>

<p>The curriculum provided each graduate with broad-based leadership perspectives and first-hand experiences aimed at familiarizing them with the Grand Strand&rsquo;s resources and service opportunities. The program, which began in August 2023, covered a variety of topics, including professional development, regional history, tourism and economic development, education, law enforcement, human services, government and politics, and the arts.</p>

<p>Each graduate completed 75 community project hours, including specific hours dedicated to Habitat for Humanity of the Grand Strand, youth services, community enhancement and team projects recognizing local citizens for the Ann DeBock Leadership Award.</p>

<p>The graduates of LGS Class 44 are:</p>

<ul>
<li>Cameron W. Armstrong, City of Myrtle Beach</li>
<li>Briana C. Brandon, Maynard Nexsen PC</li>
<li>Robert Branton, Santee Cooper</li>
<li>Dawn S. Bryant, Tidelands Health</li>
<li>Kenneth L Chapman, Jr., Myrtle Beach Fire Department</li>
<li>Chris R. Chockley, Bolton &amp; Menk Inc.</li>
<li>Shaquasia P. Coleman, Juice Crush, LLC</li>
<li>Jacob J. Duesing, City of Myrtle Beach Police Department</li>
<li>David Ethridge, HTC</li>
<li>April Formo, Coldwell Banker Sea Coast Advantage - The Sollecito Advantage Group</li>
<li>Christie Foxworth, Coastal Carolina National Bank</li>
<li>Dr. Casey Garavito, PAR Physical Therapy</li>
<li>Christopher M. Gentile, Prestwick Country Club</li>
<li>Emily B. Griffin, TD Bank</li>
<li>Michelle R. Griffin, Winslow Law Firm</li>
<li>Dr. Tiffany Hollis, Coastal Carolina University</li>
<li>John R. Howenstine, South Atlantic Bank</li>
<li>Kelly Hughes, McLeod Health</li>
<li>Sherry Katzenberger, Pinnacle Financial Partners</li>
<li>Shawn S. Kelley, Practical Solutions for Public Safety, Inc.</li>
<li>Samantha Norris, Loris Chamber of Commerce</li>
<li>Emily Otto, Otto Realty LLC - RE/MAX Southern Shores</li>
<li>Eric R. Rivenbark, Coastal Carolina University</li>
<li>Kim Rodgers-Clora, Jacqueline Rodgers Foundation Inc.</li>
<li>Stephanie Sebring-Wilson, Ground Zero</li>
<li>Emily Smith, Insurance Resource Group LLC</li>
<li>Victoria Tobin, Myrtle Beach Area Hospitality Association</li>
<li>Stephanie Warren, Grand Strand Miracle League</li>
<li>Marlane White, Myrtle Beach Area Chamber of Commerce</li>
<li>Jenny Williams, SkyWheel Myrtle Beach</li>
<li>Karl A. Yachulke, Broadway at the Beach</li>
</ul>

<p>&ldquo;It&rsquo;s a true honor to graduate this year&rsquo;s class of Leadership Grand Strand as each participant excelled at the program and now possess enhanced skills to be more effective leaders in our community,&rdquo; said LGS Executive Director Diana Greene.</p>

<p>Those interested in learning more about LGS can visit LeadershipGrandStrand.com. The deadline to submit an application to participate in the 45th LGS class is June 30, 2024.</p>
]]></content>
    <teaser_image_url><![CDATA[https://www.myrtlebeachareachamber.com/img/cache/blog/BlogPosts/674/teaser_image/34836-590-394f-4d22ac6ad028bf35f2a8ff07772b1b94]]></teaser_image_url>
    <teaser_image_alt_text/>
    <categories><![CDATA[LGS News]]></categories>
    <author><![CDATA[by Marlane White, Director of Communications]]></author>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Celebrate Earth Day 2024 by Volunteering with Keep Myrtle Beach Beautiful]]></title>
    <date><![CDATA[2024-04-17 11:41:00]]></date>
    <content><![CDATA[<h2>Celebrate Earth Day 2024 by Volunteering with Keep Myrtle Beach Beautiful</h2>

<h3>Litter Removal and Beautification Activities to be Held at Withers Swash Park on April 22</h3>

<p>MYRTLE BEACH, S.C.&mdash;Keep Myrtle Beach Beautiful (KMMB) is calling on volunteers to help clean up and beautify Myrtle Beach&rsquo;s Withers Swash Park on Earth Day, Monday, April 22, 2024, from 9 to 11 a.m.</p>

<p>Volunteers can check in at the registration booth located at the Withers Swash Park pavilion, 314 Withers Swash Drive in Myrtle Beach.</p>

<p>Keep Myrtle Beach Beautiful will provide trash bags, safety vests, easy-reach grabbers, refreshments and complimentary t-shirts while supplies last.</p>

<p>Withers Swash is a tidal creek estuary where saltwater from the ocean and stormwater from impervious areas mix. The swash runs from the Atlantic Ocean to U.S. Highway 501, running along 3rd Ave. South and includes several small inland tributaries and a small lake just north of Kings Highway.</p>

<p>This unique natural habitat includes several city parks and recreational areas, a boardwalk, open spaces and road easements&mdash;all of which will be swept for litter on Earth Day.</p>

<p>Anyone interested in volunteering can learn more and register in advance at&nbsp;<a data-auth="Verified" data-linkindex="1" href="https://www.myrtlebeachareachamber.com/keepmyrtlebeachbeautiful" originalsrc="https://www.myrtlebeachareachamber.com/keepmyrtlebeachbeautiful" shash="S62auAMQUINOmpCh+D9Rri6fyBBleaTTd2bss8pHg+xfNt3jZ4icpARrt2jIsEUpcleGzubleyhY03V8Rdgs6TAp9AOIIVLnKP6pEfCPpDnjH5p/ojBqcYyxlns1WPUReMub3ApeVdqsh09gao1vB4D0T2XhlI9RbPpJdp18/TU=" title="Original URL: https://www.myrtlebeachareachamber.com/keepmyrtlebeachbeautiful. Click or tap if you trust this link.">KeepMyrtleBeachBeautiful.com</a>.</p>
]]></content>
    <teaser_image_url><![CDATA[https://www.myrtlebeachareachamber.com/img/cache/blog/BlogPosts/675/teaser_image/34836-590-394f-4d22ac6ad028bf35f2a8ff07772b1b94]]></teaser_image_url>
    <teaser_image_alt_text/>
    <categories><![CDATA[News,Keep Myrtle Beach Beautiful]]></categories>
    <author><![CDATA[by Marlane White, Director of Communications]]></author>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Ways to Help Myrtle Beach Nonprofits - April 2024]]></title>
    <date><![CDATA[2024-04-16 10:22:00]]></date>
    <content><![CDATA[<p>In an effort to support the many Grand Strand nonprofits on their missions to supporting the community, Myrtle Beach Area Chamber of Commerce is publishing this monthly roundup of our nonprofit members current needs.</p>

<p>If you&rsquo;re looking to get involved or give back, consider supporting the nonprofits below or in&nbsp;the chamber&rsquo;s&nbsp;<a href="https://web.myrtlebeachareachamber.com/Nonprofit" target="_blank">business directory.</a></p>

<hr />
<p><strong><img alt="Neighbor to Neighbor Volunteer Flyer" src="/img/cache/lib24watch/Lib24watchFiles/1948/lib24watch_file/0-291e661adb04d1d1b6ff5b57f85faf16" style="width: 300px; height: 200px; margin-left: 10px; margin-right: 10px; float: right;" /></strong></p>

<p><strong>Neighbor to Neighbor of South Carolina</strong> is seeking volunteer drivers to assist seniors, disabled adults and veterans with transportation to and from medial appointments. Learn more at <a href="https://www.n2ncarolinas.org/" target="_blank">n2ncarolinas.org</a>.</p>

<p><strong><a href="https://helpnewdirections.org/" target="_blank">New Directions of Horry County</a></strong>&nbsp;is seeking donations of wishlist items including fitted food prep gloves in size large or extra large, 9&rdquo; foam plates, toilet tissue, laundry detergent pods and Pine Sol. You can shop their <a href="https://helpnewdirections.org/current-needs" target="_blank">online wishlist</a> to help.</p>

<p><strong>Saltwater Chamber Orchestra</strong> is looking for experienced adult string players, specifically double bass or viola players.&nbsp;Rehearsals are&nbsp;Fridays&nbsp;from 1-3 p.m.&nbsp;at Faith Presbyterian Church at 805&nbsp;79th Ave. N in Myrtle Beach. Learn more by calling 843-240-0400.</p>

<p><a href="https://soscaresc.org/" target="_blank"><strong>SOS Care</strong></a> is participating in Palmetto Giving Day, a 36-hour online giving marathon that serves as one of their top fundraising initiatives for the year. They are raising funds to support programs including ABA therapy, Project Lifesaver, independent living skills development, job coach training, Oak Tree Farms and more. You can make donations online May 7-8 at <a href="https://www.palmettogivingday.org/organizations/soscare" target="_blank">PalmettoGivingDay.org</a>.</p>

<p><a href="https://www.score.org/grandstrand/our-sponsors-partners" target="_blank"><strong>SCORE Grand Strand</strong></a> is looking for a replacement TV/monitor for their conference room to replace one that was damaged during the move to their new location. They are looking for a 43&rdquo; TV, either this <a href="https://www.bestbuy.com/site/toshiba-43-class-c350-series-led-4k-uhd-smart-fire-tv/6532119.p?skuId=6532119" target="_blank">Toshiba model</a> or this <a href="https://www.bestbuy.com/site/samsung-43-class-cu7000-crystal-uhd-4k-smart-tizen-tv/6537422.p?skuId=6537422" target="_blank">Samsung model</a>. A used model in good condition would be considered. Contact <a href="mailto:ron.opher@scorevolunteer.org">Ron Opher</a> for more information.</p>

<p><img alt="HSNMB Wishlist" src="/img/cache/lib24watch/Lib24watchFiles/1947/lib24watch_file/0-291e661adb04d1d1b6ff5b57f85faf16" style="width: 240px; height: 300px; margin-left: 10px; margin-right: 10px; float: right;" />The <strong><a href="https://humanesocietynmb.org/" target="_blank">Humane Society of North Myrtle Beach</a></strong> is seeking people to <a href="https://humanesocietynmb.org/be-a-foster-caregiver/" target="_blank">foster kittens</a>&nbsp;as well as help purchase supplies for the animals they serve. Top wishlist items include Pedigree dry puppy food, paper towels, 13 gallon kitchen trash bags, silicone snuffle mats, Hill&rsquo;s I/D Digestive Care cat and dog food.</p>

<p><a href="https://periodproject.org/" target="_blank"><strong>The Period Project</strong></a> is looking for volunteers to support the nonprofits mission of providing free and accessible menstrual health supplies to local schools, shelters, food pantries and other relief organizations. Volunteers are needed to assist at donation drives and packing parties. Email <a href="mailto:myrtlebeach@periodproject.org">myrtlebeach@periodproject.org</a> for additional information.</p>

<p>&nbsp;</p>

<hr />
<p><a href="https://web.myrtlebeachareachamber.com/events?ce=true" target="_blank">VIEW NONPROFIT &amp; COMMUNITY EVENTS</a></p>

<p>Want to be on this list? <a href="https://www.myrtlebeachareachamber.com/nonprofit-organizations">Learn</a> how nonprofits can share their current needs.</p>

<p>&nbsp;</p>
]]></content>
    <teaser_image_url><![CDATA[https://www.myrtlebeachareachamber.com/img/cache/blog/BlogPosts/673/teaser_image/34836-590-394f-4d22ac6ad028bf35f2a8ff07772b1b94]]></teaser_image_url>
    <teaser_image_alt_text><![CDATA[ways to help myrtle beach nonprofits]]></teaser_image_alt_text>
    <categories><![CDATA[News]]></categories>
    <author><![CDATA[by Amanda Blomquist, Business Development Marketing Manager]]></author>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Volunteer with KMBB at the Myrtle Beach Classic]]></title>
    <date><![CDATA[2024-04-10 8:02:00]]></date>
    <content><![CDATA[<h1>Volunteer Opportunity at the Myrtle Beach Classic</h1>

<p>Keep Myrtle Beach Beautiful (KMBB), a program of Myrtle Beach Area Chamber of Commerce, will lead the Ecology Volunteer Committee for the 2024 Myrtle Beach Classic.&nbsp;</p>

<p>Join our Ecology Team at the Myrtle Beach Classic!</p>

<p><strong>The following volunteer opportunities are available:</strong></p>

<ul>
<li>Sunday, May 5: volunteers will be needed to place approximately 75 trash irons and trash boxes around the golf course.&nbsp;</li>
<li>Monday, May 6 &ndash; Sunday, May 12:&nbsp;Two shift opportunities. Shifts will run approximately 7 a.m. to 1 p.m. and 1-7 p.m. (Times may differ a little each day, especially early in the week)</li>
</ul>

<p><u><strong>Volunteer Responsibilities:</strong></u></p>

<ul>
<li>Volunteers will be removing all trash from hospitality areas, concession stands and other public areas on the golf course.&nbsp;</li>
<li>Volunteers will be moving all day and circulating through all areas that have a trash receptacle to gauge the level and if it needs to be removed.&nbsp;</li>
<li>Monday and Tuesday are expected to be lighter trash days, with Wednesday to Sunday being heavier days.&nbsp;</li>
<li>Prefer if volunteers can work multiple days.</li>
<li>Volunteers must be able to lift at least 40 pounds.</li>
</ul>

<p><u><strong>Volunteer uniforms:</strong></u></p>

<ul>
<li>Keep Myrtle Beach Beautiful T-shirts (provided by KMBB)</li>
<li>Khaki shorts</li>
<li>Tennis shoes</li>
<li>Keep Myrtle Beach Beautiful hats (provided by KMBB)</li>
<li>Sunscreen will be provided</li>
<li>All volunteers will have a home base in the climate-controlled volunteer headquarters tent near the Dunes Club tennis courts. There are restrooms there where volunteers can change if needed.</li>
</ul>

<p>Breakfast, lunch, snacks and beverages will be provided throughout the day.</p>

<p>Volunteers will be given a parking pass for Lot B, a volunteer credential for entry to all days of the tournament and the opportunity to purchase up to four (4) daily grounds tickets at 50% off. Volunteers who work at least 18 hours will receive a discounted round of golf at The Dunes Club on one of the two dates (dates to be determined following the tournament.)</p>

<p><a class="readon" href="http://marketing.visitmyrtlebeach.com/t/y-i-xkhutjk-l-t/" target="_blank">Sign Up!</a></p>

<p><em>To register, choose the ecology volunteer type then enter code&nbsp;<strong>ecology24 .&nbsp;</strong>Click continue and fill in fields as requested. When you reach the screen listing prices of volunteer packages, please ignore these options and instead click to complete the registration.&nbsp;</em></p>
]]></content>
    <teaser_image_url><![CDATA[https://www.myrtlebeachareachamber.com/img/cache/blog/BlogPosts/671/teaser_image/34836-590-394f-4d22ac6ad028bf35f2a8ff07772b1b94]]></teaser_image_url>
    <teaser_image_alt_text><![CDATA[Volunteer Opportunity at the Myrtle Beach Classic]]></teaser_image_alt_text>
    <categories><![CDATA[Keep Myrtle Beach Beautiful]]></categories>
    <author/>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Welcome New Members - March 2024]]></title>
    <date><![CDATA[2024-04-02 8:18:00]]></date>
    <content><![CDATA[<p>Myrtle Beach Area Chamber of Commerce encourages investors to do business with other chamber members. Please consider these new stakeholders the next time you have a need for products/services. New member&nbsp;referral? Contact&nbsp;<a href="mailto:Pam.Wright@%20VisitMyrtleBeach.com">Pam Wright</a>, business development manager, 843-916-7220. Need to make changes to business information? Contact&nbsp;<a href="mailto:Amanda.Bailey@VisitMyrtleBeach.com">Amanda Bailey</a>, business development coordinator, 843-916-7205.</p>

<hr />
<p><a href="https://web.myrtlebeachareachamber.com/Transportation/Absolute-Taxi-LLC-31259" target="_blank"><strong>Absolute Taxi LLC</strong></a><br />
<em>Transportation</em><br />
Paul Corpodean<br />
1900 Mr. Joe White Ave., Ste. 7<br />
Myrtle Beach, SC 29577<br />
843-333-3333<br />
<br />
<a href="https://web.myrtlebeachareachamber.com/HealthFitness-ConsultantsTrainers/Anytime-Fitness-Murrells-Inlet-31093" target="_blank"><strong>Anytime Fitness Murrells Inlet</strong></a><br />
<em>Health-Fitness Consultants/Trainers</em><br />
Benjamin Furtwengler<br />
736 Mink Ave.<br />
Murrells Inlet, SC 29576<br />
843-459-2270<br />
<br />
<a href="https://web.myrtlebeachareachamber.com/ClothingFamily/Boho-Tique-LLC-31112" target="_blank"><strong>Boho Tique LLC</strong></a><br />
<em>Clothing-Family</em><br />
Angela Carnes<br />
640 Hwy. 17 Business, Unit D<br />
Surfside Beach, SC 29585<br />
843-446-2814</p>

<p><a href="https://web.myrtlebeachareachamber.com/Restaurant-Seafood/Cackalacky-Fish-Co-24403" target="_blank"><strong>Cackalacky Fish Co.</strong></a><br />
<em>Restaurant - Seafood</em><br />
William Benfield<br />
400 S. Kings Hwy.<br />
Myrtle Beach, SC 29577<br />
843-945-5040<br />
<br />
<a href="https://web.myrtlebeachareachamber.com/Cleaning/CORE-Clean-LLC-31081" target="_blank"><strong>CORE Clean LLC</strong></a><br />
<em>Cleaning</em><br />
Kevin Radford<br />
Myrtle Beach, SC 29526<br />
888-830-2673<br />
<br />
<a href="https://web.myrtlebeachareachamber.com/MarketingConsultants/Directly-Alex-LLC-31125" target="_blank"><strong>Directly Alex LLC</strong></a><br />
<em>Marketing-Consultants</em><br />
Alex Husner<br />
Myrtle Beach, SC 29577<br />
843-251-6623</p>

<p><a href="https://web.myrtlebeachareachamber.com/Real-EstateDevelopment/DRB-Homes-31085" target="_blank"><strong>DRB Homes</strong></a><br />
<em>Real Estate-Development</em><br />
Jillian Kearney<br />
524 Sun Colony Blvd.<br />
Little River, SC 29566<br />
586-651-1637<br />
<br />
<a href="https://web.myrtlebeachareachamber.com/Merchant-Services/DRIVE-Point-of-Sale-31131" target="_blank"><strong>DRIVE Point of Sale</strong></a><br />
<em>Merchant Services</em><br />
Chris Laforge<br />
Conway, SC 29526<br />
854-236-7459<br />
<br />
<a href="https://web.myrtlebeachareachamber.com/Furniture/Ethan-Allen-Myrtle-Beach-31129" target="_blank"><strong>Ethan Allen Myrtle Beach</strong></a><br />
<em>Furniture</em><br />
Karen Milligan<br />
575 Market Ct.<br />
Myrtle Beach, SC 29577<br />
843-916-8440<br />
<br />
<strong>FIRE TO TABLE by Fat Boys</strong><br />
<em>Restaurant - Barbeque</em><br />
Raymond Clark<br />
3415 Hwy. 17 Business<br />
Murrells Inlet, SC 29576<br />
843-357-1515<br />
<br />
<a href="https://web.myrtlebeachareachamber.com/Travel-Agencies/First-Response-Travel-31091" target="_blank"><strong>First Response Travel</strong></a><br />
<em>Travel Agencies</em><br />
Andrew Dillon<br />
Myrtle Beach, SC 29579<br />
843-965-3225<br />
<br />
<a href="https://web.myrtlebeachareachamber.com/Consultants/Franchise-Recon-31083" target="_blank"><strong>Franchise Recon</strong></a><br />
<em>Consultants</em><br />
Kenneth Walker<br />
Myrtle Beach, SC 29579<br />
843-994-3690<br />
<br />
<a href="https://web.myrtlebeachareachamber.com/Technology/Grand-Strand-Angel-Network-31111" target="_blank"><strong>Grand Strand Angel Network</strong></a><br />
<em>Technology</em><br />
Mckean Nowlin<br />
509 9th Ave. N.<br />
Myrtle Beach, SC 29577<br />
573-268-7874<br />
<br />
<a href="https://web.myrtlebeachareachamber.com/Painter/Grand-Strand-Custom-Painting-31211" target="_blank"><strong>Grand Strand Custom Painting</strong></a><br />
<em>Painter</em><br />
Doina Mazzola<br />
4201 Carolina Exchange Dr., Ste. 202<br />
Myrtle Beach, SC 29579<br />
843-315-8714<br />
<br />
<a href="https://web.myrtlebeachareachamber.com/Nonprofit/I-AM-Metamorphosis-31289" target="_blank"><strong>&quot;I AM&quot; Metamorphosis</strong></a><br />
<em>Nonprofit</em><br />
Angela Graves-Bellamy<br />
Myrtle Beach, SC 29588<br />
862-281-9583<br />
<br />
<a href="https://web.myrtlebeachareachamber.com/Restaurant-Seafood/Joe%27s-Crab-Shack-Broadway-at-the-Beach-18970" target="_blank"><strong>Joe&#39;s Crab Shack - Broadway at the Beach</strong></a><br />
<em>Restaurant - Seafood</em><br />
Shannon Holland<br />
1219 Celebrity Cir.<br />
Myrtle Beach, SC 29577<br />
843-626-4490<br />
<br />
<a href="https://web.myrtlebeachareachamber.com/Art-Galleries/Kaleidoscope-Artisan-Collective-31223" target="_blank"><strong>Kaleidoscope Artisan Collective</strong></a><br />
<em>Art Galleries</em><br />
Joe Kohler<br />
519 Broadway St.<br />
Myrtle Beach, SC 29577<br />
843-232-7642<br />
<br />
<a href="https://web.myrtlebeachareachamber.com/Water-Sports/Kokopelli-Surf-Camp-Paddleboard-Kayak-Tours-and-Rentals-20857" target="_blank"><strong>Kokopelli Surf Camp Paddleboard Kayak Tours and Rentals</strong></a><br />
<em>Water Sports</em><br />
Wyatt Todd<br />
North Myrtle Beach, SC 29582<br />
843-340-9565<br />
<br />
<a href="https://web.myrtlebeachareachamber.com/Photography/KPhoto-Media-LLC-31222" target="_blank"><strong>KPhoto Media LLC</strong></a><br />
<em>Photography</em><br />
Karla Pulido<br />
Loris, SC 29569<br />
713-540-8768<br />
<br />
<a href="https://web.myrtlebeachareachamber.com/AirlinesAir-Freight/LIFT-Academy-31232" target="_blank"><strong>LIFT Academy</strong></a><br />
<em>Airlines-Air Freight</em><br />
Jim Borgaard<br />
3085 Howard Ave.<br />
Myrtle Beach, SC 29577<br />
854-600-1953<br />
<br />
<a href="https://web.myrtlebeachareachamber.com/Real-EstateSales/Living-in-South-Carolina-31167" target="_blank"><strong>Living in South Carolina</strong></a><br />
<em>Real Estate-Sales</em><br />
Samantha Marksberry<br />
Longs, SC 29568<br />
443-740-0832<br />
livinginsc.com<br />
<br />
<a href="https://web.myrtlebeachareachamber.com/Cleaning/MaidThis-Cleaning-Myrtle-Beach-30792" target="_blank"><strong>MaidThis Cleaning Myrtle Beach</strong></a><br />
<em>Cleaning</em><br />
Daniel Blaker<br />
Myrtle Beach, SC 29577<br />
843-588-7184<br />
<br />
<a href="https://web.myrtlebeachareachamber.com/Entertainment/Mermaid-Wishes-31130" target="_blank"><strong>Mermaid Wishes</strong></a><br />
<em>Entertainment</em><br />
Paul Caple<br />
Myrtle Beach, SC 29579<br />
843-957-1174<br />
<br />
<a href="https://web.myrtlebeachareachamber.com/Attorneys/Nelson-Galbreath-31090" target="_blank"><strong>Nelson &amp; Galbreath</strong></a><br />
<em>Attorneys</em><br />
Julie Stubblefield<br />
4701 Oleander Dr.<br />
Myrtle Beach, SC 29577<br />
843-913-8694<br />
<br />
<a href="https://web.myrtlebeachareachamber.com/Restaurant-Bakery/Nothing-Bundt-Cakes-25521" target="_blank"><strong>Nothing Bundt Cakes</strong></a><br />
<em>Restaurant - Bakery</em><br />
Chevon Bacot<br />
112 Loyola Dr., Ste. 103<br />
Myrtle Beach, SC 29588<br />
843-898-8044<br />
<br />
<a href="https://web.myrtlebeachareachamber.com/Vacation-Rentals-Beach-Homes-/Ocean-Breeze-Townhomes-31123" target="_blank"><strong>Ocean Breeze Townhomes</strong></a><br />
<em>Vacation Rentals &amp; Beach Homes</em><br />
James Hinkle<br />
Myrtle Beach, SC 29577<br />
843-685-4587<br />
<br />
<a href="https://web.myrtlebeachareachamber.com/TheatresDinner-Attractions/Polynesian-Fire-Productions-20421" target="_blank"><strong>Polynesian Fire Productions</strong></a><br />
<em>Theatres-Dinner Attractions</em><br />
Jason Wright<br />
Myrtle Beach, SC 29572<br />
843-424-1978<br />
<br />
<a href="https://web.myrtlebeachareachamber.com/FinancialServices/Riverbend-Wealth-Management-31118" target="_blank"><strong>Riverbend Wealth Management</strong></a><br />
<em>Financial-Services</em><br />
Jeremy Finger<br />
1341 44th Ave. N., Ste. 102<br />
Myrtle Beach, SC 29577<br />
843-970-1049</p>

<p><a href="https://web.myrtlebeachareachamber.com/BreweryDistillery/Southern-Hops-Brewing-Company-Murrells-Inlet-31138" target="_blank"><strong>Southern Hops Brewing Company - Murrells Inlet</strong></a><br />
<em>Brewery/Distillery</em><br />
Jolie Deaton<br />
5148 Hwy. 17 Business<br />
Murrells Inlet, SC 29576<br />
843-299-1254</p>

<p><a href="https://web.myrtlebeachareachamber.com/HealthFitness-ConsultantsTrainers/StrongSelves-31230" target="_blank"><strong>StrongSelves</strong></a><br />
<em>Health-Fitness Consultants/Trainers</em><br />
Viktoriia Voronina<br />
4377 N. Kings Hwy., Ste. 109<br />
Myrtle Beach, SC 29577<br />
843-957-2295<br />
<br />
<a href="https://web.myrtlebeachareachamber.com/ClothingWomen/Style-Encore-18108" target="_blank"><strong>Style Encore</strong></a><br />
<em>Clothing-Women</em><br />
Nicki Welch<br />
10792 Kings Rd.<br />
Myrtle Beach, SC 29572<br />
843-232-7163<br />
<br />
<a href="https://web.myrtlebeachareachamber.com/InteriorDesigners/Ten-08-Interiors-LLC-31114" target="_blank"><strong>Ten 08 Interiors LLC</strong></a><br />
<em>Interior-Designers</em><br />
Amy Helander-Roberts<br />
Myrtle Beach, SC 29577<br />
843-685-0988<br />
<br />
<a href="https://web.myrtlebeachareachamber.com/Restaurant-Breakfast/Toasted-Yolk-Cafe-31234" target="_blank"><strong>Toasted Yolk Cafe</strong></a><br />
<em>Restaurant - Breakfast</em><br />
Adam Thornton<br />
1004 Glenforest Rd.<br />
Myrtle Beach, SC 29579<br />
843-903-4100<br />
<br />
<a href="https://web.myrtlebeachareachamber.com/BreweryDistillery/Voodoo-Brewing-Company-Myrtle-Beach-31240" target="_blank"><strong>Voodoo Brewing Company Myrtle Beach</strong></a><br />
<em>Brewery/Distillery</em><br />
Todd Pinkler<br />
1318 Celebrity Cir.<br />
Myrtle Beach, SC 29577<br />
910-381-7498<br />
<br />
<a href="https://web.myrtlebeachareachamber.com/Attorneys/Wright-Injury-Law-LLC-31115" target="_blank"><strong>Wright Injury Law LLC</strong></a><br />
<em>Attorneys</em><br />
Brooke Wright<br />
4214 Mayfair St., Unit A<br />
Myrtle Beach, SC 29577<br />
843-457-0637</p>
]]></content>
    <teaser_image_url><![CDATA[https://www.myrtlebeachareachamber.com/img/cache/blog/BlogPosts/670/teaser_image/34836-590-394f-4d22ac6ad028bf35f2a8ff07772b1b94]]></teaser_image_url>
    <teaser_image_alt_text/>
    <categories><![CDATA[New Members]]></categories>
    <author/>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Ways to Help Local Nonprofits - March 2024]]></title>
    <date><![CDATA[2024-03-12 10:12:00]]></date>
    <content><![CDATA[<p>In an effort to support the many Grand Strand nonprofits on their missions to supporting the community, Myrtle Beach Area Chamber of Commerce is publishing this monthly roundup of our nonprofit members current needs.</p>

<p>If you&rsquo;re looking to get involved or give back, consider supporting the nonprofits below or in&nbsp;the chamber&rsquo;s&nbsp;<a href="https://web.myrtlebeachareachamber.com/Nonprofit" target="_blank">business directory.</a></p>

<hr />
<p><strong>Children&rsquo;s Recovery Center</strong> is seeking donations of snacks, small blankets and toys for the children they serve. <a href="https://childrensrecoverycenter.org/" target="_blank">Learn more</a></p>

<p><strong>Eagle Cold Case and Missing Persons</strong> is looking for donations to support their efforts investigating unsolved homicides and missing persons cases. <a href="https://www.eccmpi.org" target="_blank">Learn more</a></p>

<p>The <strong>Go Get Your You Foundation</strong> is <a href="/lib24watch/files/pdf/1912" rel="external">seeking donations</a>&nbsp;of raffle items or financial contributions for their <a href="https://bit.ly/43avlW5" target="_blank">Juneteenth&nbsp;Festival</a>.</p>

<p><strong>Help4Kids</strong> is collecting Easter baskets and basket items (decorative grass, candy, eggs, etc.) to provide to children in their program. <a href="https://www.help4kidssc.org/" target="_blank">Learn more</a></p>

<p>The <strong>Myrtle Beach Area Hospitality Association</strong> is seeking donations for the 15th Annual&nbsp;Trio&nbsp;Dinner&rsquo;s Silent Auction to be held April 15, 2024, at the Myrtle Beach Convention Center.&nbsp;The dinner features local chefs paired with student chefs to compete for the best dish and this year they&#39;re adding a new twist by featuring top bartenders from the Grand Strand. The auction raises&nbsp;money for hospitality programs at Horry-Georgetown Technical College, the International Culinary Institute of Myrtle Beach and Coastal Carolina University. <a data-emb-href-display="mbhospitality.org" href="https://mbhospitality.org/trio-silent-auction">Submit donation form</a>.</p>

<p><strong>Palmetto Literacy Council</strong> is looking for volunteers to help children and adults who struggle with basic reading, writing and math. The nonprofit provides all materials and training and is looking for volunteers to provide one hour twice weekly tutoring at local libraries. Currently, volunteers are needed at the following locations:</p>

<ul>
<li>1 at Carolina Forest Library</li>
<li>1 at&nbsp;Chapin Memorial Library</li>
<li>7 volunteers at&nbsp;Conway Library</li>
<li>10 at Socastee Library</li>
<li>4 at&nbsp;Surfside Beach Library</li>
</ul>

<p>The next volunteer orientation is March 19. You can call 843-945-9278 for more information.</p>

<hr />
<p><a href="https://web.myrtlebeachareachamber.com/events?ce=true" target="_blank">VIEW NONPROFIT &amp; COMMUNITY EVENTS</a></p>

<p>Want to be on this list? <a href="https://www.myrtlebeachareachamber.com/nonprofit-organizations">Learn</a> how nonprofits can share their current needs.</p>
]]></content>
    <teaser_image_url><![CDATA[https://www.myrtlebeachareachamber.com/img/cache/blog/BlogPosts/669/teaser_image/34836-590-394f-4d22ac6ad028bf35f2a8ff07772b1b94]]></teaser_image_url>
    <teaser_image_alt_text><![CDATA[Ways to Help Local Nonprofits - January 2024]]></teaser_image_alt_text>
    <categories><![CDATA[News]]></categories>
    <author/>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Nine Local Charities to Benefit from 2024 Myrtle Beach Classic]]></title>
    <date><![CDATA[2024-02-29 14:19:00]]></date>
    <content><![CDATA[<h2>Nine Local Charities to Benefit from 2024 Myrtle Beach Classic</h2>

<h3>A total of $225,000 to be allocated</h3>

<p>Myrtle Beach, S.C. (February 26, 2024) &ndash; Nine local social service charities have been selected to receive a grant from revenue generated by the inaugural Myrtle Beach Classic, scheduled May 6-12 at the Dunes Golf and Beach Club, meaning the event will not only showcase the Grand Strand, but also benefit the area. A total of $225,000 will be allocated for 2024.</p>

<p>&ldquo;The charities selected are all doing impactful and meaningful work, and we are proud to provide assistance to further promote these programs that are making such a huge difference on the Grand Strand,&rdquo; said Darren Nelson, tournament director. &ldquo;The PGA TOUR has a time-honored tradition of supporting charities and giving back to each community where events are hosted.&rdquo;</p>

<p>Tournaments under the PGA TOUR umbrella donate their net proceeds each year to support local philanthropic organizations, totaling close to $4 billion to date, which is more than all other major sports leagues combined.</p>

<p>&quot;We are extremely grateful,&rdquo; said Barb Mains, who founded the Help 4 Kids charity in 1989 and has been leading the organization for 35 years. &ldquo;Oh Lord, that money will go a long way. It will help us feed the kids for two months. Our kids won&rsquo;t have to go home from school for the weekends without food.&rdquo;</p>

<p>A fully volunteer organization where 100 percent of every donation goes to the charity, Help 4 Kids currently delivers food to 40 Horry County schools and feeds more than 3,000 children each week. Teachers discreetly place food sacks into the students&rsquo; backpacks on Friday afternoon so they have something to eat on the weekend. In addition, Help 4 Kids provides school supplies, blankets, clothing and coats.</p>

<p>Additional charities selected are Blue Star Mothers of Coastal Carolina, Boys and Girls Clubs of the Grand Strand, Champion Autism Network, Children&rsquo;s Recovery Center, Classy Smiles, Helping Hand of Myrtle Beach, Project Golf, and SOS Care. All of the benefitting charities have 501c3 status, meaning they are non-profit, tax-exempt groups with a dedicated mission.</p>

<p>&ldquo;This is a game-changer for us,&rdquo; said Becky Large, executive director of Champion Autism Network, a program that helps to create judgment-free experiences for people living with autism. &ldquo;We support more than 900 families in Horry and Georgetown counties who have someone on the autism spectrum. We can use these funds to create awareness and serve even more people.&rdquo;</p>

<p>The Myrtle Beach Classic is a dual-field PGA TOUR event sponsored by Visit Myrtle Beach and managed by Sportfive, a global event management company. The local event will be one of two stops in the Palmetto State for the PGA TOUR in 2024, joining with the RBC Heritage in April at Harbour Town Golf Links.</p>

<p>A Robert Trent Jones-designed course, the Dunes Club was incorporated in 1948. It was host to the season-ending Charles Schwab Cup Championship on PGA TOUR Champions from 1994 to 1999, with notables Raymond Floyd, Jim Colbert, Jay Sigel, Gil Morgan, Hale Irwin and Gary McCord claiming titles. Twenty-one years earlier, the Dunes Club was the site of PGA TOUR Q-School Finals in 1973, with Ben Crenshaw taking medalist honors.</p>

<p style="text-align: center;">###</p>

<p><strong>About Myrtle Beach Classic</strong></p>

<p>The Myrtle Beach Classic, a dual-field PGA TOUR event hosting 120 players, takes place May 9-12, 2024, at Dunes Golf and Beach Club in Myrtle Beach, S.C., commonly known as the &ldquo;Golf Capital of the World.&rdquo; Daily and weekly general admission tickets, and Club 18 Shared Hospitality options are available for purchase online at MyrtleBeachClassic.com. Children aged 15 and younger are admitted free with an adult ticketholder.</p>

<p><strong>About PGA TOUR</strong></p>

<p>By showcasing golf&rsquo;s greatest players, the PGA TOUR engages, inspires and positively impacts our fans, partners and communities worldwide. The PGA TOUR, headquartered in Ponte Vedra Beach, Florida, co-sanctions tournaments on the PGA TOUR, PGA TOUR Champions, Korn Ferry Tour, PGA TOUR Americas and administers PGA TOUR Q-School presented by Korn Ferry and PGA TOUR University. TOUR members represent the world&rsquo;s best players, hailing from 28 countries and territories. Showcasing the biggest moments in the sport with history and legacy on the line, the PGA TOUR has long-term domestic distribution partnerships for broadcast coverage on CBS, NBC and Golf Channel and video streaming service on ESPN+. Internationally, PGA TOUR coverage is available across 200+ countries and territories in 28 languages via 44 broadcast and digital partners. Virtually all tournaments are organized as non-profit organizations to maximize charitable giving, and to date, tournaments across all Tours have generated more than $3.64 billion. Fans can follow the PGA TOUR on the new PGA TOUR app and PGATOUR.COM, and on social media channels, including Facebook, Instagram (in Spanish, Korean and Japanese), LinkedIn, TikTok, X (in English and Spanish), WhatsApp (in English and Spanish), WeChat, Weibo, Toutiao, Douyin and LINE.</p>

<p><strong>About SPORTFIVE</strong></p>

<p>SPORTFIVE is a global sports marketing agency that delivers customer-centric solutions based on trust and transparency, deep industry experience and global relationships, digital intelligence, and innovation. SPORTFIVE strategically and creatively connects brands, rightsholders, media platforms and fans to create and enable contemporary partnerships in sports.</p>

<p>While creating and growing long-term value for all, SPORTFIVE often leads the sports business into the future through innovative digital solutions and strives to be the most progressive and respected partner in sports.</p>

<p>Being at the center of professional sports, SPORTFIVE will use its unique position to make a positive contribution to sustainability and to live up to the social and economic duty and responsibility, which sport and consequently all parties involved, also have. SPORTFIVE operates with a global mindset and network of over 1,200 local experts based in 15 countries around the world, active in soccer, golf, Esports, motorsport, handball, tennis, football, basketball, ice hockey, rugby, Olympics, multi-sport events, and many more.</p>
]]></content>
    <teaser_image_url><![CDATA[https://www.myrtlebeachareachamber.com/img/cache/blog/BlogPosts/667/teaser_image/34836-590-394f-4d22ac6ad028bf35f2a8ff07772b1b94]]></teaser_image_url>
    <teaser_image_alt_text><![CDATA[Nine Local Charities to Benefit from 2024 Myrtle Beach Classic]]></teaser_image_alt_text>
    <categories><![CDATA[MBACC News Release]]></categories>
    <author/>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Welcome New Members - February 2024]]></title>
    <date><![CDATA[2024-02-26 17:25:00]]></date>
    <content><![CDATA[<p>Myrtle Beach Area Chamber of Commerce encourages investors to do business with other chamber members. Please consider these new stakeholders the next time you have a need for products/services. New member&nbsp;referral? Contact&nbsp;<a href="mailto:Pam.Wright@%20VisitMyrtleBeach.com">Pam Wright</a>, business development manager, 843-916-7220. Need to make changes to business information? Contact&nbsp;<a href="mailto:Amanda.Bailey@VisitMyrtleBeach.com">Amanda Bailey</a>, business development coordinator, 843-916-7205.</p>

<hr />
<p><a href="https://web.myrtlebeachareachamber.com/Restaurant-Seafood/1229-Shine-30823" target="_blank"><strong>1229 Shine</strong></a><br />
<em>Restaurant - Seafood</em><br />
Mary Pappas<br />
1229 Shine Ave.<br />
Myrtle Beach, SC 29577<br />
704-604-5720</p>

<p><a href="https://web.myrtlebeachareachamber.com/MortgageLenders/Anchor-Mortgage-LLC-30640" target="_blank"><strong>Anchor Mortgage LLC</strong></a><br />
<em>Mortgage-Lenders</em><br />
Andrea Campanelli<br />
5180 Horry Dr., Unit A<br />
Murrells Inlet, SC 29576<br />
843-367-9900</p>

<p><a href="https://web.myrtlebeachareachamber.com/Apartments/Bell%27s-Lake-Townes-30888" target="_blank"><strong>Bell&#39;s Lake Townes</strong></a><br />
<em>Apartments</em><br />
Patrick Ard<br />
100 Lyman Ct.<br />
Longs, SC 29568<br />
843-790-9383</p>

<p><a href="https://web.myrtlebeachareachamber.com/Restaurant-Seafood/Big-Chill-Island-House-30980" target="_blank"><strong>Big Chill Island House</strong></a><br />
<em>Restaurant</em><br />
Danielle Merritts<br />
4736 Hwy. 17 S.<br />
North Myrtle Beach, SC 29582<br />
843-360-0159</p>

<p><a href="https://web.myrtlebeachareachamber.com/Waste-Hauling/Bin-There-Dump-That-30917" target="_blank"><strong>Bin There Dump That</strong></a><br />
<em>Waste Hauling</em><br />
Macy Lee<br />
Conway, SC 29526<br />
843-360-5844</p>

<p><a href="https://web.myrtlebeachareachamber.com/Vacation-Rentals-Beach-Homes-/BlueWater-Resort-and-Banquet-Room-30434"><strong>BlueWater Resort and Banquet Room</strong></a><br />
<em>Vacation Rentals &amp; Beach Homes</em><br />
Anthony Monte Carlo<br />
2001 S. Ocean Blvd.<br />
Myrtle Beach, SC 29577<br />
856-693-8558</p>

<p><a href="https://web.myrtlebeachareachamber.com/Waste-Hauling/Cardinal-Waste-Services-30916"><strong>Cardinal Waste Services</strong></a><br />
<em>Waste Hauling</em><br />
Rachael Hurst<br />
Conway, SC 29526<br />
843-957-5823</p>

<p><a href="https://web.myrtlebeachareachamber.com/Vacation-Rentals-Beach-Homes-/Casago-Myrtle-Beach-30826"><strong>Casago Myrtle Beach</strong></a><br />
<em>Vacation Rentals &amp; Beach Homes</em><br />
Ashley Larrowe<br />
516 Broadway St.<br />
Myrtle Beach, SC 29577<br />
843-999-2837</p>

<p><a href="https://web.myrtlebeachareachamber.com/Nonprofit/Chicora-Rotary-Club-of-Myrtle-Beach-30920"><strong>Chicora Rotary Club of Myrtle Beach</strong></a><br />
<em>Nonprofit</em><br />
Holly Lusk<br />
PO Box 70101<br />
Myrtle Beach, SC 29572<br />
843-340-5728</p>

<p><a href="https://web.myrtlebeachareachamber.com/SchoolsPublic/Coastal-High-School-30825"><strong>Coastal High School</strong></a><br />
<em>Schools-Public</em><br />
Jacquie Roddy<br />
3710 Palmetto Pointe Blvd.<br />
Myrtle Beach, SC 29588<br />
843-788-9898</p>

<p><a href="https://web.myrtlebeachareachamber.com/ClothingWomen/Cultured-Boutique-31071"><strong>Cultured Boutique</strong></a><br />
<em>Clothing-Women</em><br />
Marlena Locklear<br />
Laurinburg, NC 28352<br />
910-303-9830</p>

<p><a href="https://web.myrtlebeachareachamber.com/ToursOperators-Promoters/DIRECTIONS-Tours-30769"><strong>DIRECTIONS Tours</strong></a><br />
<em>Tours-Operators &amp; Promoters</em><br />
Frances Manzitto<br />
Little River, SC 29566<br />
931-801-9900</p>

<p><a href="https://web.myrtlebeachareachamber.com/Water-Sports/Fish-Finder-Fishing-Charters-30773"><strong>Fish Finder Fishing Charters</strong></a><br />
<em>Water Sports</em><br />
Robert Orr<br />
4123 US-17 Business<br />
Murrells Inlet, SC 29576<br />
843-347-4464</p>

<p><a href="https://web.myrtlebeachareachamber.com/Nonprofit/Foundation-Fighting-Blindness-South-Carolina-Chapter-30914"><strong>Foundation Fighting Blindness - South Carolina Chapter</strong></a><br />
<em>Nonprofit</em><br />
Heather Edwards<br />
Columbia, MD 21045<br />
800-683-5555</p>

<p><a href="https://web.myrtlebeachareachamber.com/Travel-Agencies/Great-Vacations-Myrtle-Beach-30820"><strong>Great Vacations Myrtle Beach</strong></a><br />
<em>Travel Agencies</em><br />
Kym Wiley<br />
4214 Mayfair St., Ste. B<br />
Myrtle Beach, SC 29577<br />
608-219-7047</p>

<p><a href="https://web.myrtlebeachareachamber.com/Nonprofit/Gussie-Wortham-Foundation-Inc-30885"><strong>Gussie Wortham Foundation Inc.</strong></a><br />
<em>Nonprofit</em><br />
Kenneth Thompson<br />
Myrtle Beach, SC 29579<br />
860-888-9945</p>

<p><a href="https://web.myrtlebeachareachamber.com/Pest-Control/Harris-Pest-Control-Inc-30879"><strong>Harris Pest Control Inc.</strong></a><br />
<em>Pest Control</em><br />
Chris Muti<br />
3041 Ricks Industrial Park Dr.<br />
Myrtle Beach, SC 29588<br />
843-702-9730</p>

<p><a href="https://web.myrtlebeachareachamber.com/Amusements-Attractions/Hickey%27s-InterActive-Adventures-30919"><strong>Hickey&#39;s InterActive Adventures</strong></a><br />
<em>Amusements &amp; Attractions</em><br />
Robert Sheahan<br />
7621 N. Kings Hwy.<br />
Myrtle Beach, SC 29572<br />
703-785-2545</p>

<p><a href="https://web.myrtlebeachareachamber.com/HotelMotel/Holiday-Inn-Club-Vacations-Myrtle-Beach-Oceanfront-Resort-10302"><strong>Holiday Inn Club Vacations Myrtle Beach Oceanfront Resort</strong></a><br />
<em>Hotel-Motel</em><br />
Katie Gallagher<br />
2917 S. Ocean Blvd.<br />
Myrtle Beach, SC 29577<br />
407-395-6182</p>

<p><a href="https://web.myrtlebeachareachamber.com/Nonprofit/Human-Trafficking-Institute-30884"><strong>Human Trafficking Institute</strong></a><br />
<em>Nonprofit</em><br />
Donna Hamilton<br />
712 H St. NE, Ste. 1651<br />
Washington, DC 20002<br />
607-389-2972</p>

<p><a href="https://web.myrtlebeachareachamber.com/Real-EstateRentals/JP-Property-Management-30794"><strong>J&amp;P Property Management</strong></a><br />
<em>Real Estate-Rentals</em><br />
Devon Marx<br />
3330 S. Hwy. 17<br />
Murrells Inlet, SC 29576<br />
843-651-6616</p>

<p><a href="https://web.myrtlebeachareachamber.com/Transportation/MBFCharters-LLC-30763"><strong>MBFCharters LLC</strong></a><br />
<em>Transportation</em><br />
Sharon Carr<br />
Pawleys Island, SC 29585<br />
843-446-0035</p>

<p><a href="https://web.myrtlebeachareachamber.com/Travel-Agencies/Mission-City-Travel-LLC-30902"><strong>Mission City Travel LLC</strong></a><br />
<em>Travel Agencies</em><br />
Kevin Cabe<br />
Little River, SC 29566<br />
828-273-1536</p>

<p><a href="https://web.myrtlebeachareachamber.com/HotelMotel/Ocean-Escape-30790"><strong>Ocean Escape</strong></a><br />
<em>Hotel-Motel</em><br />
Matt Klugman<br />
1400 S. Ocean Blvd.<br />
Myrtle Beach, SC 29577<br />
843-310-3425</p>

<p><a href="https://web.myrtlebeachareachamber.com/Contractors/Otto-Construction-30822"><strong>Otto Construction</strong></a><br />
<em>Contractors</em><br />
Emily Otto<br />
Myrtle Beach, SC 29577<br />
843-655-4102</p>

<p><a href="https://web.myrtlebeachareachamber.com/HealthWellness/Palmetto-OBGYN-30319"><strong>Palmetto OB/GYN</strong></a><br />
<em>Health-Wellness</em><br />
Sharon Partridge<br />
3864 Renee Dr.<br />
Myrtle Beach, SC 29579<br />
843-353-2111</p>

<p><strong>Pat&#39;s Pampering Petsitting</strong><br />
<em>Pet</em><br />
Pat Antal<br />
Myrtle Beach, SC 29588<br />
607-759-6079</p>

<p><a href="https://web.myrtlebeachareachamber.com/GolfMiniature/PopStroke-30887"><strong>PopStroke</strong></a><br />
<em>Golf-Miniature</em><br />
Dylana Silver O&#39;Brien<br />
1187 Celebrity Cir.<br />
Myrtle Beach, SC 29577<br />
843-932-9520</p>

<p><a href="https://web.myrtlebeachareachamber.com/Environmental-Consultants/Rhino-Demolition-Environmental-Services,-Corp-31034"><strong>Rhino Demolition &amp; Environmental Services, Corp.</strong></a><br />
<em>Environmental Consultants</em><br />
Jake Smith<br />
1664 American Way<br />
Myrtle Beach, SC 29577<br />
843-839-1380</p>

<p><a href="https://web.myrtlebeachareachamber.com/FishingGuides/Salty-Hooker-Fishing-Charters-30833"><strong>Salty Hooker Fishing Charters</strong></a><br />
<em>Fishing-Guides</em><br />
Austin O Luken<br />
1508 S. Waccamaw Dr.<br />
Murrells Inlet, SC 29576<br />
843-504-9667</p>

<p><a href="https://web.myrtlebeachareachamber.com/Water-Sports/Shoreline-Watersports-30768"><strong>Shoreline Watersports</strong></a><br />
<em>Water Sports</em><br />
Garrett Todd<br />
Surfside Beach, SC 29575<br />
843-602-0665</p>

<p><a href="https://web.myrtlebeachareachamber.com/Nonprofit/South-Carolina-Women-in-Leadership-30913"><strong>South Carolina Women in Leadership</strong></a><br />
<em>Nonprofit</em><br />
Kristina Burch<br />
PO Box 11974<br />
Columbia, SC 29211<br />
843-241-3524</p>

<p><a href="https://web.myrtlebeachareachamber.com/Nonprofit/Submarine-Veteran%27s-Group-USSVI-Grand-Strand-Base-30915"><strong>Submarine Veteran&#39;s Group - USSVI Grand Strand Base</strong></a><br />
<em>Nonprofit</em><br />
Ronald Bixby<br />
Myrtle Beach, SC 29588<br />
203-240-6740</p>

<p><a href="https://web.myrtlebeachareachamber.com/Restaurant-Barbeque/Swig-and-Swine-30937"><strong>Swig and Swine</strong></a><br />
<em>Restaurant - Barbeque</em><br />
Anthony Dibernardo<br />
500 Broadway St.<br />
Myrtle Beach, SC 29577<br />
843-460-5146</p>

<p><a href="https://web.myrtlebeachareachamber.com/Security-Services/Task-Force-Protection-30824"><strong>Task Force Protection</strong></a><br />
<em>Security Services</em><br />
Steven Corbin<br />
607 Briarwood Dr., Ste. 2<br />
Myrtle Beach, SC 29572<br />
844-364-8273</p>

<p><a href="https://web.myrtlebeachareachamber.com/Cosmetics/Teeth-Whitening-by-Nicole-31065"><strong>Teeth Whitening by Nicole</strong></a><br />
<em>Cosmetics</em><br />
Nicole Hassinger<br />
4683 Dick Pond Rd.<br />
Myrtle Beach, SC 29588<br />
203-560-1897</p>

<p><a href="https://web.myrtlebeachareachamber.com/Apartments/The-Brixley-at-Carolina-Forest-30828"><strong>The Brixley at Carolina Forest</strong></a><br />
<em>Apartments</em><br />
Jennifer Dixon<br />
110 Chanticleer Village Dr.<br />
Myrtle Beach, SC 29579<br />
843-349-3000</p>

<p><a href="https://web.myrtlebeachareachamber.com/Gymnastics/The-Little-Gym-of-Myrtle-Beach-30878"><strong>The Little Gym of Myrtle Beach</strong></a><br />
<em>Gymnastics</em><br />
Henry Lewandowski<br />
1390 Farrow Pkwy., Unit 4<br />
Myrtle Beach, SC 29577<br />
843-348-2679</p>

<p><a href="https://web.myrtlebeachareachamber.com/PublicRelations/The-Merchant-Strategy,-Inc-30834"><strong>The Merchant Strategy, Inc.</strong></a><br />
<em>Public-Relations</em><br />
Cheryl Scott<br />
Little River, SC 29566<br />
843-254-4764</p>

<p><a href="https://web.myrtlebeachareachamber.com/Insurance/The-Robert-Taylor-Group-30932"><strong>The Robert Taylor Group</strong></a><br />
<em>Insurance</em><br />
David Turbeville<br />
710 Cromwell Dr., Ste. C<br />
Greenville, NC 27858<br />
252-353-7262</p>

<p><a href="https://web.myrtlebeachareachamber.com/Restaurant/The-Tasting-Room,-Inc-30886"><strong>The Tasting Room, Inc</strong></a><br />
<em>Restaurant</em><br />
Lisa Lee<br />
505 9th Ave. N., Unit A<br />
Myrtle Beach, SC 29577<br />
252-503-3569</p>

<p><a href="https://web.myrtlebeachareachamber.com/Restaurant-Breakfast/Theo%27s-Pancake-House-30946"><strong>Theo&#39;s Pancake House</strong></a><br />
<em>Restaurant</em><br />
Maria Kartsaklis<br />
9924 N. Kings Hwy.<br />
Myrtle Beach, SC 29572<br />
843-232-7761</p>

<p><a href="https://web.myrtlebeachareachamber.com/Furniture/Two-Brothers-Woodworks-30785"><strong>Two Brothers Woodworks</strong></a><br />
<em>Furniture</em><br />
Marta Landry<br />
3026 Nevers St.<br />
Myrtle Beach, SC 29577<br />
843-400-3014</p>

<p><a href="https://web.myrtlebeachareachamber.com/ContractorsConcrete-Supplier-/Waccamaw-Concrete-31059"><strong>Waccamaw Concrete</strong></a><br />
<em>Contractors-Concrete Supplier</em><br />
Brian Cobb<br />
5491 Buck Hill Rd.<br />
Myrtle Beach, SC 29588<br />
843-267-6243</p>

<p><a href="https://web.myrtlebeachareachamber.com/MedicalClinics/Waccamaw-Oral-Surgery-and-Medical-Spa-30957"><strong>Waccamaw Oral Surgery and Medical Spa</strong></a><br />
<em>Medical-Clinics</em><br />
Laura Rice<br />
3635 Old Kings Hwy.<br />
Murrells Inlet, SC 29576<br />
843-947-0017</p>

<p style="margin-bottom:11px"><span style="font-size:11pt"><span style="line-height:107%"><span style="font-family:Calibri,sans-serif"></span></span></span></p>
]]></content>
    <teaser_image_url><![CDATA[https://www.myrtlebeachareachamber.com/img/cache/blog/BlogPosts/666/teaser_image/34836-590-394f-4d22ac6ad028bf35f2a8ff07772b1b94]]></teaser_image_url>
    <teaser_image_alt_text><![CDATA[welcome new members]]></teaser_image_alt_text>
    <categories><![CDATA[New Members]]></categories>
    <author/>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[63rd Annual Can-Am Days to Welcomes Canadian Visitors March 9-17]]></title>
    <date><![CDATA[2024-02-23 11:50:00]]></date>
    <content><![CDATA[<p>The Myrtle Beach Area Chamber of Commerce (MBACC) and Convention and Visitors Bureau (CVB), and the City of Myrtle Beach, are pleased to roll out the red carpet again for Canadian visitors during 63<sup>rd</sup>&nbsp;Annual Can-Am Days, happening March 9-17, 2024.</p>

<p>&ldquo;Myrtle Beach has long been a beloved getaway for countless Canadians who seek a warm-weather retreat where they can easily explore our 60-miles of beaches, over 90 golf courses, 2,200-plus restaurants and year-round attractions &ndash; all while enjoying special rates. We look forward to carrying on the tradition of Can-Am Days and showering them with our Southern hospitality once again,&rdquo; said Karen Riordan, MBACC and CVB President and CEO.</p>

<p>Among the special events occurring over Can-Am Days, the chamber and TD Bank will host a Welcome Reception on Monday, March 11, from 1 to 3 p.m. within the lobby of its visitors center at 1200 N. Oak Street in Myrtle Beach. Refreshments will be served.</p>

<p>On March 12, the chamber and Ripley&rsquo;s Aquarium will host the Can-Am Plaza Party outside of Ripley&rsquo;s Aquarium at Broadway at the Beach with music and entertainment for the entire family from 11 a.m. to 1 p.m. Canadians can request the CAA (Canadian Automobile Association) discount on tickets to Ripley&rsquo;s Aquarium for a $2 savings.</p>

<p>In addition, various resorts and attractions are offering specials deals and discounts for Canadians. Visit&nbsp;<a data-auth="Verified" data-linkindex="1" href="https://nam12.safelinks.protection.outlook.com/?url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.canamdays.com%2F&amp;data=05%7C02%7Camanda.blomquist%40visitmyrtlebeach.com%7C95ce36670ac94d06135d08dc33d127bf%7C81d417a4e3dd45fc965205e902b9d96e%7C0%7C0%7C638442222714175807%7CUnknown%7CTWFpbGZsb3d8eyJWIjoiMC4wLjAwMDAiLCJQIjoiV2luMzIiLCJBTiI6Ik1haWwiLCJXVCI6Mn0%3D%7C0%7C%7C%7C&amp;sdata=SBebqkLY5ZIqZ%2B7PuWkBEXyZ8GDdUDlDuUMJ5xNic9I%3D&amp;reserved=0" originalsrc="http://www.canamdays.com/" shash="UyYhOzFJCVIHnoHc/7cA9NAGPCFj/3oRf+QFGT/iWPdL4Q/8r7tbgGuq6OleN1ZnAd5nHxS4ON7XJWSV0088F9tilX1ziyZngN3hSBoXBePZbPf4MVx3MxckrUfiKOVLkxX8HcfNkz3Lv89Ew4+Zui21HikKqk2eXpStbsF7uuY=" title="Original URL: http://www.canamdays.com/. Click or tap if you trust this link.">CanAmDays.com</a>&nbsp;for more details.</p>
]]></content>
    <teaser_image_url><![CDATA[https://www.myrtlebeachareachamber.com/img/cache/blog/BlogPosts/665/teaser_image/34836-590-394f-4d22ac6ad028bf35f2a8ff07772b1b94]]></teaser_image_url>
    <teaser_image_alt_text><![CDATA[63rd annual can-am days march 9-17 2024]]></teaser_image_alt_text>
    <categories><![CDATA[MBACC News Release]]></categories>
    <author><![CDATA[by Marlane White, Director of Communications]]></author>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Leadership Grand Strand Accepting Applications for Class 45]]></title>
    <date><![CDATA[2024-02-07 9:44:00]]></date>
    <content><![CDATA[<p>Leadership Grand Strand (LGS) is pleased to announce applications are now being accepted for participation in Class 45, a 10-month leadership development program beginning in August.</p>

<p>LGS is an initiative of the Myrtle Beach Area Chamber of Commerce that provides transformative leadership training activities and exclusive behind-the-scenes tours of Grand Strand institutions in order to cultivate a dynamic corps of individuals who are well informed, committed and exceptionally qualified.</p>

<p>&ldquo;For more than four decades, LGS has stood as the preeminent program for developing future leaders and we&rsquo;re eager to welcome prospective applicants for our next, highly coveted class,&rdquo; said Diana Greene, LGS executive director. &ldquo;Joining Leadership Grand Strand isn&#39;t just an investment in personal development; it&rsquo;s a commitment to becoming a catalyst for positive change within the community.&quot;</p>

<p>LGS is open to residents of Horry or Georgetown counties. Candidates may self-nominate or be nominated by an organization. Participation is limited and reflects the demographic, geographic and professional diversity of the Myrtle Beach area.</p>

<p>Criteria for selection include evidence of leadership abilities, potential to provide leadership to the Grand Strand, interest in community affairs, desire to volunteer and commitment to become a more involved member of the community. Participants and their sponsoring organizations must be willing to invest the time required to participate, which includes a two-day retreat in September, a full day of classes the first Thursday of each month and 75 hours of community service.</p>

<p>The cost of the program is $1,499 per person. Applications, along with three letters of reference, are due by June 30, 2024.</p>

<p>Scholarship opportunities are available through the William F. Pritchard Scholarship Fund and Bennie J. Swans Jr. Scholarship Fund. The William F. Pritchard Scholarship Fund awards tuition assistance to qualified applicants as determined by the LGS Board of Regents. The Bennie J. Swans Jr. Scholarship Fund provides full tuition to one applicant from an underrepresented or marginalized group, and the recipient is selected by the chamber&rsquo;s Diversity, Equity and Inclusion Council.</p>

<p>For more information and to apply for the program, visit <a href="https://www.myrtlebeachareachamber.com/leadershipgrandstrand">LeadershipGrandStrand.com</a>.</p>
]]></content>
    <teaser_image_url><![CDATA[https://www.myrtlebeachareachamber.com/img/cache/blog/BlogPosts/664/teaser_image/34836-590-394f-4d22ac6ad028bf35f2a8ff07772b1b94]]></teaser_image_url>
    <teaser_image_alt_text><![CDATA[Leadership Grand Strand Accepting Applications for Class 45]]></teaser_image_alt_text>
    <categories><![CDATA[LGS News]]></categories>
    <author/>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Keep Myrtle Beach Beautiful Receives Grant from PalmettoPride]]></title>
    <date><![CDATA[2024-02-06 8:41:00]]></date>
    <content><![CDATA[<h2>Keep Myrtle Beach Beautiful Receives Grant from PalmettoPride</h2>

<p>MYRTLE BEACH, S.C.&mdash;Keep Myrtle Beach Beautiful is pleased to announce PalmettoPride awarded the organization a Keep South Carolina Beautiful Support Grant in the amount of $6,690.</p>

<p>&ldquo;Our grant programs provide resources that directly impact our communities at the local level,&rdquo; said Sarah Lyles, Executive Director of PalmettoPride. &ldquo;It is exciting to see the growth of litter prevention programs across the state, particularly in our rural counties.&rdquo;</p>

<p>Included in the grant is $800 for lawn and garden tools and $600 for flowers to assist with beautification projects throughout the City of Myrtle Beach.</p>

<p>Keep Myrtle Beach Beautiful is holding several cleanup events this year, including a beach cleanup at Hurl Rocks Park on Feb. 26, their annual Cleanin&rsquo; for the Season Citywide Cleanup on March 30, and a beautification of Wither&rsquo;s Swash Park on Earth Day, April 22.</p>

<p>Additional grant money will be used for attending the national Keep America Beautiful educational conference, national dues as well as t-shirts for volunteers.</p>

<p>Keep Myrtle Beach Beautiful is a program of the Myrtle Beach Area Chamber of Commerce and an official affiliate of Keep America Beautiful.</p>

<p>For more information and to volunteer, visit&nbsp;<a data-auth="Verified" data-linkindex="1" href="https://nam12.safelinks.protection.outlook.com/?url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.keepmyrtlebeachbeautiful.com%2F&amp;data=05%7C02%7Camanda.blomquist%40visitmyrtlebeach.com%7C8a504896a9624b569a0608dc267dfbfc%7C81d417a4e3dd45fc965205e902b9d96e%7C0%7C0%7C638427572050673681%7CUnknown%7CTWFpbGZsb3d8eyJWIjoiMC4wLjAwMDAiLCJQIjoiV2luMzIiLCJBTiI6Ik1haWwiLCJXVCI6Mn0%3D%7C0%7C%7C%7C&amp;sdata=CDNlv8jzQoGgeg4x9jbWBC%2B5%2BjrMsHe740tOeLNuMTo%3D&amp;reserved=0" originalsrc="http://www.keepmyrtlebeachbeautiful.com/" shash="SK5l2D3vgFs3kFhY7kmEBBL+WJXr85kqbAZulXGRHZYL9tOcEHyNpSy30ARXAS5fiM36AMmg4I3qEWf6XNdRoa5O4GgnEymbXBCzCZSVf5iLx8izUSkbuLaTuOjIO/CcbrGHYH4ZNR7zH/l5VBO9kBh8CRTOU79zeITb5aN6j9c=" title="Original URL: http://www.keepmyrtlebeachbeautiful.com/. Click or tap if you trust this link.">www.KeepMyrtleBeachBeautiful.com</a>.</p>
]]></content>
    <teaser_image_url><![CDATA[https://www.myrtlebeachareachamber.com/img/cache/blog/BlogPosts/663/teaser_image/34836-590-394f-4d22ac6ad028bf35f2a8ff07772b1b94]]></teaser_image_url>
    <teaser_image_alt_text><![CDATA[Keep Myrtle Beach Beautiful Receives Grant from PalmettoPride]]></teaser_image_alt_text>
    <categories><![CDATA[MBACC News Release,Keep Myrtle Beach Beautiful]]></categories>
    <author><![CDATA[by Marlane White, Director of Communications]]></author>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Visit Myrtle Beach Group Sales Team Members Earn Designation as Certified Faith-Based Meeting Professionals]]></title>
    <date><![CDATA[2024-02-05 9:33:00]]></date>
    <content><![CDATA[<h2>Visit Myrtle Beach Group Sales Team Members Earn Designation as Certified Faith-Based Meeting Professionals</h2>

<p>The Myrtle Beach Area Chamber of Commerce (MBACC) and Convention and Visitors Bureau (CVB) is pleased to announce that three Visit Myrtle Beach group sales staff members have achieved a Certified Faith-Based Meeting Professional (CFMP) designation from the Religious Conference Management Association (RCMA).</p>

<p>Bob Harris, executive vice president of group sales; Cyndi Mohr, senior sales manager; and Lori Lampo, group sales manager, were bestowed the CFMP designation during RCMA&rsquo;s Emerge Conference held in San Antonio, Jan. 9-11, 2024.</p>

<p>The CFMP program requires participants to partake in 12 hours of basic meeting planning education to have a consistent level of professional knowledge with other RCMA members. Certification is valid for five years, at which time, verification of continued involvement in the faith-based event industry is required.</p>

<p>&ldquo;This accomplishment not only reflects the commitment to professional excellence by our group sales team, but their knowledge of the industry enhances our capability to host meaningful and diverse religious events in the Myrtle Beach area.&nbsp;We welcome these meetings, recognizing their economic benefits as well as their contributions through charitable giving and&nbsp;volunteerism, community engagement, and fostering cultural diversity,&rdquo; said Karen Riordan, MBACC and CVB President and CEO.</p>

<p>On Sept. 30 &ndash; Oct. 2, 2024, Myrtle Beach will host the RCMA Planner Experience&nbsp;where an estimated 40 religious conference planners are set to convene within the Grand Strand to tour the destination&rsquo;s event venues.</p>
]]></content>
    <teaser_image_url><![CDATA[https://www.myrtlebeachareachamber.com/img/cache/blog/BlogPosts/661/teaser_image/34836-590-394f-4d22ac6ad028bf35f2a8ff07772b1b94]]></teaser_image_url>
    <teaser_image_alt_text><![CDATA[Members of the Visit Myrtle Beach group sales team stand with those recognized for receiving their C]]></teaser_image_alt_text>
    <categories><![CDATA[MBACC News Release]]></categories>
    <author/>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Nominations Open for 2024 Annual Meeting Awards]]></title>
    <date><![CDATA[2024-02-02 13:35:00]]></date>
    <content><![CDATA[<h2>Myrtle Beach Area Chamber Seeks Community Nominations for &lsquo;Entrepreneur of the Year&rsquo; and &lsquo;Champion of Diversity&rsquo; Award</h2>

<p>MYRTLE BEACH, S.C.&mdash;The Myrtle Beach Area Chamber of Commerce (MBACC) is pleased to announce that community nominations are now being accepted through March 11, 2024, for two distinguished accolades: Entrepreneur of the Year and Champion of Diversity. For these awards, the chamber is seeking to honor individuals or businesses located within Horry or Georgetown County, and membership is not required.</p>

<p>The Entrepreneur of the Year award commends an individual who exhibits innovation and entrepreneurial spirit in developing processes, products or technologies. The Champion of Diversity award recognizes a business or individual who has demonstrated a sustained commitment to fostering diversity in their workplace and community.</p>

<p>&ldquo;By inviting community input, we amplify the diverse voices shaping our region&rsquo;s success, while celebrating those who embody innovation and commitment to inclusivity,&rdquo; said Karen Riordan, MBACC President and CEO.</p>

<p>Recipients are honored during the Annual Meeting scheduled for April 25, 2024. In addition, seven other awards are presented to chamber members, including Small Business of the Year, Nonprofit of the Year, Hospitality Employee of the Year, Chamber Volunteer of the Year, Ambassador of the Year, Business Innovation Award and Community Service Award.</p>

<p>Riordan added, &ldquo;Our annual award categories recognize individuals, businesses and organizations that are stellar reflections of the chamber&rsquo;s mission to promote, protect, and improve civic and economic progress throughout the Grand Strand.&rdquo;</p>

<p>To submit a nomination for the Entrepreneur of the Year or the Champion of Diversity award, fill out the online form at&nbsp;<a data-auth="Verified" data-linkindex="3" href="https://nam12.safelinks.protection.outlook.com/?url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.myrtlebeachareachamber.com%2Fannualmeeting&amp;data=05%7C02%7Camanda.blomquist%40visitmyrtlebeach.com%7Cddaad0ea2bd4471112bc08dc23fe4b78%7C81d417a4e3dd45fc965205e902b9d96e%7C0%7C0%7C638424822330518646%7CUnknown%7CTWFpbGZsb3d8eyJWIjoiMC4wLjAwMDAiLCJQIjoiV2luMzIiLCJBTiI6Ik1haWwiLCJXVCI6Mn0%3D%7C0%7C%7C%7C&amp;sdata=LszTV%2B%2FQae6JEMx3i3BinddI6QxUL1Iq6NRtlTV1baQ%3D&amp;reserved=0" originalsrc="https://www.myrtlebeachareachamber.com/annualmeeting" shash="uiign3d6GfgIxUgWbHZ+ZXxpRkI7ttOcsjSinHdDKQNgP2n50wK3VgrKFYUrLYuVqnERY9O5f9+OSmix1c9KJvCySYlYTgaJRBZ2QpOjtwcn3bVevqXE9giVFb18sWZU9surknW7JUVSEyHtDAJgGDZ82EPpWQb5XGceEWc3myQ=" title="Original URL: https://www.myrtlebeachareachamber.com/annualmeeting. Click or tap if you trust this link.">MyrtleBeachAreaChamber.com/AnnualMeeting</a>&nbsp;no later than March 11.</p>

<hr />
<h2>C&aacute;mara de Comercio del &Aacute;rea de Myrtle Beach busca Nominaciones de la Comunidad para el Premio &#39;Empresario del A&ntilde;o&#39; y &#39;Campe&oacute;n de la Diversidad&#39;</h2>

<p>MYRTLE BEACH, S.C.&mdash; La C&aacute;mara de Comercio del &Aacute;rea de Myrtle Beach (MBACC) se complace en anunciar que se est&aacute;n aceptando nominaciones de la comunidad hasta el 11 de marzo de 2024, para dos distinguidos reconocimientos: &ldquo;Empresario del A&ntilde;o&rdquo; y &ldquo;Campe&oacute;n de la Diversidad&rdquo;. Para estos premios, la c&aacute;mara busca honrar a individuos o negocios ubicados dentro de los condados de Horry o Georgetown, y la membres&iacute;a no es obligatoria.</p>

<p>El premio &ldquo;Empresario del A&ntilde;o&rdquo; elogia a un individuo que demuestra innovaci&oacute;n y esp&iacute;ritu emprendedor en el desarrollo de procesos, productos o tecnolog&iacute;as. El premio &ldquo;Campe&oacute;n de la Diversidad&rdquo; reconoce a un negocio o individuo que ha demostrado un compromiso duradero con fomentar la diversidad en su lugar de trabajo y comunidad.</p>

<p>&quot;Al invitar a la participaci&oacute;n de la comunidad, amplificamos las diversas voces que dan forma al &eacute;xito de nuestra regi&oacute;n, al tiempo que celebramos a aquellos que encarnan la innovaci&oacute;n y el compromiso con la inclusividad&quot;, dijo Karen Riordan, Presidenta y Directora Ejecutiva de MBACC.</p>

<p>Los galardonados ser&aacute;n homenajeados durante la Reuni&oacute;n Anual programada para el 25 de abril de 2024. Adem&aacute;s, se entregan nueve premios adicionales a miembros de la c&aacute;mara: Peque&ntilde;o Negocio del A&ntilde;o, Organizaci&oacute;n sin Fines de Lucro del A&ntilde;o, Empleado de Hospitalidad del A&ntilde;o, Voluntario de la C&aacute;mara del A&ntilde;o, Embajador del A&ntilde;o, Premio a la Innovaci&oacute;n Empresarial, Premio al Servicio a la Comunidad, Premio al Pionero del A&ntilde;o y Premio al Ciudadano del A&ntilde;o.</p>

<p>Riordan agreg&oacute;: &quot;Nuestras categor&iacute;as anuales de premios reconocen a individuos, negocios y organizaciones que son reflejos excepcionales de la misi&oacute;n de la c&aacute;mara de promover, proteger y mejorar el progreso c&iacute;vico y econ&oacute;mico en todo Grand Strand&quot;.</p>

<p>Para enviar una nominaci&oacute;n para el Empresario del A&ntilde;o o el Premio Campe&oacute;n de la Diversidad, complete el formulario en l&iacute;nea en MyrtleBeachAreaChamber.com/AnnualMeeting a m&aacute;s tardar el 11 de marzo.</p>
]]></content>
    <teaser_image_url><![CDATA[https://www.myrtlebeachareachamber.com/img/cache/blog/BlogPosts/662/teaser_image/34836-590-394f-4d22ac6ad028bf35f2a8ff07772b1b94]]></teaser_image_url>
    <teaser_image_alt_text><![CDATA[Nominations Open for 2024 Annual Meeting Awards]]></teaser_image_alt_text>
    <categories><![CDATA[MBACC News Release]]></categories>
    <author/>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Stuart Butler Honored for Contributions to Travel Accessibility]]></title>
    <date><![CDATA[2024-01-30 14:13:00]]></date>
    <content><![CDATA[<h2>Stuart Butler Honored for Contributions to Travel Accessibility</h2>

<h3>Both Champion Autism Network &amp; TravelAbility recognize Butler for his leadership</h3>

<p><img alt="Stuart Butler smiles with award from CAN." src="/img/cache/lib24watch/Lib24watchFiles/1911/lib24watch_file/0-291e661adb04d1d1b6ff5b57f85faf16" style="width: 300px; height: 398px; margin-left: 10px; margin-right: 10px; float: left;" />MYRTLE BEACH, S.C.&mdash;The Myrtle Beach Area Chamber of Commerce (MBACC) and Convention and Visitors Bureau (CVB) is pleased to announce Visit Myrtle Beach&rsquo;s Chief Marketing Officer Stuart Butler has earned recognition from two organizations within the travel accessibility industry.</p>

<p><a data-auth="Verified" data-linkindex="1" href="https://nam12.safelinks.protection.outlook.com/?url=http%3A%2F%2Fchampionautismnetwork.com%2F&amp;data=05%7C02%7Camanda.blomquist%40visitmyrtlebeach.com%7Cb4aa596def9b4356b8e108dc21d9330b%7C81d417a4e3dd45fc965205e902b9d96e%7C0%7C0%7C638422464052776550%7CUnknown%7CTWFpbGZsb3d8eyJWIjoiMC4wLjAwMDAiLCJQIjoiV2luMzIiLCJBTiI6Ik1haWwiLCJXVCI6Mn0%3D%7C0%7C%7C%7C&amp;sdata=OZvjlQyQlkAreBu6toHhMCbqncoNr%2F%2FmnKIZ4JzvjPU%3D&amp;reserved=0" originalsrc="http://championautismnetwork.com/" shash="EfV2/5YaQC9c3g6y2lGClDl72289SUXiuIU3NnNgVE1vNaK7B3pslbQmQoSb40Gn9/CPtr5iEDwlnPoXw3jm3wlDT5wtdx7J1j9S5KccsIRJsrftTTCzMwojNcc7eTzNOXF7vbjY8Bd2tVIamgvF1F6uvEhnrBxEX/S/aysacQg=" title="Original URL: http://championautismnetwork.com/. Click or tap if you trust this link.">Champion Autism Network</a>&nbsp;(CAN) presented Butler with their Champion Award during the organization&rsquo;s annual fundraiser on Jan. 25, 2024, for his effort to expand the Myrtle Beach area as a destination that welcomes Autism families.</p>

<p>&ldquo;Stuart&rsquo;s efforts at Visit Myrtle Beach and the Myrtle Beach Area Chamber of Commerce are at the forefront of destinations across the world supporting families with Autism,&rdquo; said CAN Founder and Executive Director Becky Large.&nbsp;</p>

<p>CAN operates the&nbsp;<a data-auth="Verified" data-linkindex="2" href="https://nam12.safelinks.protection.outlook.com/?url=https%3A%2F%2Fautismtravel.club%2F&amp;data=05%7C02%7Camanda.blomquist%40visitmyrtlebeach.com%7Cb4aa596def9b4356b8e108dc21d9330b%7C81d417a4e3dd45fc965205e902b9d96e%7C0%7C0%7C638422464052792789%7CUnknown%7CTWFpbGZsb3d8eyJWIjoiMC4wLjAwMDAiLCJQIjoiV2luMzIiLCJBTiI6Ik1haWwiLCJXVCI6Mn0%3D%7C0%7C%7C%7C&amp;sdata=wUSmYUPNwU71o3pp%2Fp%2FNw4YSlsUXjPYmMtsbbls8cOk%3D&amp;reserved=0" originalsrc="https://autismtravel.club/" shash="f7xpK/oHK82PvRGH6/lzqfFHfzSmJArspoh3v8ic/bhE66kOLLad8hn+XYp7knhZeQwooA79WabKa6S+f1QLaK0j0W7u+rNIO5eyZ7V6/OE7rfMZqE7x4+ukzIct5o7s26J9VMfKW1GBDWyDOJlpo1hoSmIQL+QPsSk9uqCtNFI=" title="Original URL: https://autismtravel.club/. Click or tap if you trust this link.">Autism Travel Club</a>&nbsp;program, which offers families tailored travel experiences to explore places while accommodating their unique needs. Likewise, CAN provides educational certifications for businesses and organizations, such as hotels and restaurants, to create Autism-friendly environments and services.</p>

<p>Moreover, Butler&rsquo;s commitment to inclusivity in travel has been lauded by&nbsp;<a data-auth="Verified" data-linkindex="3" href="https://nam12.safelinks.protection.outlook.com/?url=https%3A%2F%2Ftravelability.net%2F2024-accessibility-champions%2F&amp;data=05%7C02%7Camanda.blomquist%40visitmyrtlebeach.com%7Cb4aa596def9b4356b8e108dc21d9330b%7C81d417a4e3dd45fc965205e902b9d96e%7C0%7C0%7C638422464052801454%7CUnknown%7CTWFpbGZsb3d8eyJWIjoiMC4wLjAwMDAiLCJQIjoiV2luMzIiLCJBTiI6Ik1haWwiLCJXVCI6Mn0%3D%7C0%7C%7C%7C&amp;sdata=w4QmRmMhRKN3rzhZvNtVT53WNPVIzDU3%2BndTzW4pqJU%3D&amp;reserved=0" originalsrc="https://travelability.net/2024-accessibility-champions/" shash="B4qnmppJOykgD8ngKUjy8ArgBybCCWyWm3XvIBaIveta36zJcrypRuCK5Ug7/TIKlueGYG/TUXV9zH4p8bm5PKAa/JsmO92yAA0oQvirpvv850qneJaw2a+qQtdvNuPB4p31fO/Wfx4hH2nSR5+M+Jl4C56cCwdf4LIhKyqGrYo=" title="Original URL: https://travelability.net/2024-accessibility-champions/. Click or tap if you trust this link.">TravelAbility</a>, naming him one of their &ldquo;24 Accessibility Champions to Watch in 2024.&rdquo; The recognition highlights professionals with &ldquo;empathy and understanding of the diverse needs of travelers with disabilities.&rdquo;</p>

<p>TravelAbility, known for its advocacy, education and technological innovations, annually hosts the TravelAbility Summit, uniting industry leaders and accessibility advocates to share pioneering accessible travel solutions.</p>

<p>Under Butler&rsquo;s visionary leadership, Visit Myrtle Beach has launched several initiatives catering to travelers with special needs and their families, including&nbsp;<a data-auth="Verified" data-linkindex="4" href="https://nam12.safelinks.protection.outlook.com/?url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.visitmyrtlebeach.com%2Fthe-beach-is-for-everybody&amp;data=05%7C02%7Camanda.blomquist%40visitmyrtlebeach.com%7Cb4aa596def9b4356b8e108dc21d9330b%7C81d417a4e3dd45fc965205e902b9d96e%7C0%7C0%7C638422464052809054%7CUnknown%7CTWFpbGZsb3d8eyJWIjoiMC4wLjAwMDAiLCJQIjoiV2luMzIiLCJBTiI6Ik1haWwiLCJXVCI6Mn0%3D%7C0%7C%7C%7C&amp;sdata=Jq07gWMMnudr5Yeis0NzXv8rzFgLz3IYuRbUt5nl828%3D&amp;reserved=0" originalsrc="https://www.visitmyrtlebeach.com/the-beach-is-for-everybody" shash="kyeVn8TaPqjengJHSiZ+iLsWjWCMwzR2A4YxxPsrglJqKLch+Gm1212zJP/jO5vLM0xsk6VV6jx48qwUz1j0G5hAV7NxrzW6Zi31bh0S/m0mhNuWr1WM+kAlqLg2yb5VXWbg89aahdGfP6eqJZ5MR2Upz6hcfiCMvvvYxjdMowA=" title="Original URL: https://www.visitmyrtlebeach.com/the-beach-is-for-everybody. Click or tap if you trust this link.">The Beach is for everyBODY</a>&nbsp;sensory-friendly pledge for hospitality businesses and the&nbsp;<a data-auth="Verified" data-linkindex="5" href="https://nam12.safelinks.protection.outlook.com/?url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.visitmyrtlebeach.com%2Fplan%2Fautism-friendly-vacations&amp;data=05%7C02%7Camanda.blomquist%40visitmyrtlebeach.com%7Cb4aa596def9b4356b8e108dc21d9330b%7C81d417a4e3dd45fc965205e902b9d96e%7C0%7C0%7C638422464052815568%7CUnknown%7CTWFpbGZsb3d8eyJWIjoiMC4wLjAwMDAiLCJQIjoiV2luMzIiLCJBTiI6Ik1haWwiLCJXVCI6Mn0%3D%7C0%7C%7C%7C&amp;sdata=HmqkhZKFsoCTEGWYvqpMTLFo6g5Q619LwcwWwfCoM%2BM%3D&amp;reserved=0" originalsrc="https://www.visitmyrtlebeach.com/plan/autism-friendly-vacations" shash="wY5fV3+m5RsWdwFs4V66ZvxZHxYnBQu6WF9acsM2YdD5yV8Fdfk8Y5EdQ6l0A3/0FLYFClyE3MmUQb8bP02njDWNzVEYU1N0dHJdtqMhAs4aLKJ3Y5M3KW68/VCykkGH23AoI/IqGoqzrbbsomb6Aphu69hfMnEQC92VcJbwvzI=" title="Original URL: https://www.visitmyrtlebeach.com/plan/autism-friendly-vacations. Click or tap if you trust this link.">Autism-Friendly Vacation Guide</a>.</p>

<p>Looking ahead, Visit Myrtle Beach is set to unveil further inclusive projects, including a children&rsquo;s book and streaming TV show, both showcasing how persons with Autism can enjoy the Myrtle Beach area.&nbsp;</p>

<p>&ldquo;I&rsquo;m deeply honored by the acknowledgements from CAN and TravelAbility,&rdquo; Butler said. &ldquo;Creating inclusive experiences is not just about removing barriers, but about fostering a culture of understanding and acceptance. This is a collective effort that takes more than just one individual, and I look forward to continuing these collaborative efforts throughout our community to further enrich the lives of those affected by neurodevelopmental disorders and other disabilities.&rdquo;</p>

<p align="center">###</p>

<p><b>&nbsp;About Myrtle Beach Area Chamber of Commerce and Convention and Visitors Bureau:</b></p>

<p>Since 1938, the Myrtle Beach Area Chamber of Commerce (MBACC) has stood as the unified voice of the Grand Strand&rsquo;s business community &mdash; serving Myrtle Beach, North Myrtle Beach, Little River, Loris, Atlantic Beach, Carolina Forest, Conway, Aynor, Socastee, Surfside Beach, Garden City Beach, Murrells Inlet, Litchfield Beach and Pawleys Island. The U.S. Chamber of Commerce has awarded MBACC its five-star accreditation &mdash; one of only a few chambers in South Carolina to earn this distinction. The Myrtle Beach Area Convention and Visitors Bureau (CVB) and its destination marketing arm Visit Myrtle Beach promote tourism through various partnerships and initiatives to advance the economic success of the Grand Strand. For more information, visit&nbsp;<a data-auth="Verified" data-linkindex="6" href="https://nam12.safelinks.protection.outlook.com/?url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.myrtlebeachareachamber.com%2F&amp;data=05%7C02%7Camanda.blomquist%40visitmyrtlebeach.com%7Cb4aa596def9b4356b8e108dc21d9330b%7C81d417a4e3dd45fc965205e902b9d96e%7C0%7C0%7C638422464052822038%7CUnknown%7CTWFpbGZsb3d8eyJWIjoiMC4wLjAwMDAiLCJQIjoiV2luMzIiLCJBTiI6Ik1haWwiLCJXVCI6Mn0%3D%7C0%7C%7C%7C&amp;sdata=4DHV6TksZW7luWrunLGevsT6OcKZVPr4WsTcTMz%2FIUA%3D&amp;reserved=0" originalsrc="https://www.myrtlebeachareachamber.com/" shash="HQoofirCKvl+n2NV/PS1XCjnxBk3MWbpiWJG+0JqBoqCI9465R6a8PBdyPhoMPXkJHFsKmM7mhGbLIIXGDp23np4SnQK7906asunXaECVZCd3d5Qr63iUtigV/oeWt4Dpp1Zd1lYcLUl2f9SEEABrAM9DqOtVtnE57UBQYdW+1I=" title="Original URL: https://www.myrtlebeachareachamber.com/. Click or tap if you trust this link.">MyrtleBeachAreaChamber.com</a>,&nbsp;<a data-auth="Verified" data-linkindex="7" href="https://nam12.safelinks.protection.outlook.com/?url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.myrtlebeachareacvb.com%2Flodging-dashboard&amp;data=05%7C02%7Camanda.blomquist%40visitmyrtlebeach.com%7Cb4aa596def9b4356b8e108dc21d9330b%7C81d417a4e3dd45fc965205e902b9d96e%7C0%7C0%7C638422464052828041%7CUnknown%7CTWFpbGZsb3d8eyJWIjoiMC4wLjAwMDAiLCJQIjoiV2luMzIiLCJBTiI6Ik1haWwiLCJXVCI6Mn0%3D%7C0%7C%7C%7C&amp;sdata=JUKEOvufj8LRxacodHBbumcPsYT61uFtUnRzuuGh4II%3D&amp;reserved=0" originalsrc="https://www.myrtlebeachareacvb.com/lodging-dashboard" shash="YgnRvSxwTA8dH9VMIPX2Bd4wE7KYOcb55ECqcpNOkK/DrjK4trm4z2ht9GbIv+NK0Sgwrw0N9ik3Duqtf9ELbs5JHVhQTD3PlZ6Q1dJYfH7YYbSjvP7mrVmZPxHG00O3KP2Sl6h2IWUCQkM63QgmaEAu+iRXX+CX9pSJy3shku8=" title="Original URL: https://www.myrtlebeachareacvb.com/lodging-dashboard. Click or tap if you trust this link.">MyrtleBeachAreaCVB.com</a>&nbsp;and&nbsp;<a data-auth="Verified" data-linkindex="8" href="https://nam12.safelinks.protection.outlook.com/?url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.visitmyrtlebeach.com%2F&amp;data=05%7C02%7Camanda.blomquist%40visitmyrtlebeach.com%7Cb4aa596def9b4356b8e108dc21d9330b%7C81d417a4e3dd45fc965205e902b9d96e%7C0%7C0%7C638422464052834200%7CUnknown%7CTWFpbGZsb3d8eyJWIjoiMC4wLjAwMDAiLCJQIjoiV2luMzIiLCJBTiI6Ik1haWwiLCJXVCI6Mn0%3D%7C0%7C%7C%7C&amp;sdata=y8wXuCP47RW2GXxtCPkT4wQANH8l72ximXDvfuK9KGQ%3D&amp;reserved=0" originalsrc="https://www.visitmyrtlebeach.com/" shash="WUYAqZC2MSEFAiS/YVjrPQPuMDgg398NIcdDvnxU6pS88av4ATblDd5JJCmM0wfKsmKTLHr+tssEyKzid+VVdJVy9jPq1589+FawiP62xbWSvAhp7al6HUH7gNh3LYOJxTNgoLge5OMZ3+v8RiR907G6ORiPB5CXKd1KgjapvIU=" title="Original URL: https://www.visitmyrtlebeach.com/. Click or tap if you trust this link.">VisitMyrtleBeach.com</a>.</p>

<p><b>About Visit Myrtle Beach&nbsp;</b><br aria-hidden="true" />
Visit Myrtle Beach is the destination marketing arm of the Myrtle Beach Area Chamber of Commerce and Convention and Visitors Bureau, which serves 14 communities that stretch 60 miles along the northeast coast of South Carolina, including Myrtle Beach, North Myrtle Beach, Little River, Loris, Atlantic Beach, Carolina Forest, Conway, Aynor, Socastee, Surfside Beach, Garden City Beach, Murrells Inlet, Litchfield Beach, and Pawleys Island. Visit Myrtle Beach promotes tourism through various partnerships and initiatives to advance the economic success of the region, popularly known as the Grand Strand and the &ldquo;Golf Capital of the World.&rdquo; Along with world-class golf and over 90 golf courses, Myrtle Beach offers fresh coastal Carolina cuisine, vibrant entertainment and family attractions, shopping and more. For more information, go to&nbsp;<a data-auth="Verified" data-linkindex="9" href="https://nam12.safelinks.protection.outlook.com/?url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.visitmyrtlebeach.com%2F&amp;data=05%7C02%7Camanda.blomquist%40visitmyrtlebeach.com%7Cb4aa596def9b4356b8e108dc21d9330b%7C81d417a4e3dd45fc965205e902b9d96e%7C0%7C0%7C638422464052840319%7CUnknown%7CTWFpbGZsb3d8eyJWIjoiMC4wLjAwMDAiLCJQIjoiV2luMzIiLCJBTiI6Ik1haWwiLCJXVCI6Mn0%3D%7C0%7C%7C%7C&amp;sdata=%2BGNLpdJTpVyBQrS0oNuXm4zdDWKeNd6ipjw5YObpykM%3D&amp;reserved=0" originalsrc="https://www.visitmyrtlebeach.com/" shash="MA2T3y66lIbR/LgzQJy9eSUjupSwDWf7QPZnixfRq05A6zXCV9rrAv5vIK17/y7pizB1IcpAeBPr/30MZWbEuxKhj3r+mC6bSEpK/iq+qcxmwde/+z0K1imd/jICMNw6SIMapiG4hJ2v1wHKRsSLbh+ElJoMC/6YAeDjX+u3T3M=" title="Original URL: https://www.visitmyrtlebeach.com/. Click or tap if you trust this link.">VisitMyrtleBeach.com</a>.</p>
]]></content>
    <teaser_image_url><![CDATA[https://www.myrtlebeachareachamber.com/img/cache/blog/BlogPosts/668/teaser_image/34836-590-394f-4d22ac6ad028bf35f2a8ff07772b1b94]]></teaser_image_url>
    <teaser_image_alt_text><![CDATA[Stuart Butler smiles with award from CAN.]]></teaser_image_alt_text>
    <categories><![CDATA[MBACC News Release]]></categories>
    <author><![CDATA[by Marlane White, Director of Communications]]></author>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Welcome New Members - January 2024]]></title>
    <date><![CDATA[2024-01-30 8:58:00]]></date>
    <content><![CDATA[<p style="margin-bottom:11px">Myrtle Beach Area Chamber of Commerce encourages investors to do business with other chamber investors. Please consider these new stakeholders the next time you have a need for products/services. New member&nbsp;referral? Contact&nbsp;<a href="mailto:Pam.Wright@%20VisitMyrtleBeach.com">Pam Wright</a>, business development manager, 843-916-7220. Need to make changes to business information? Contact&nbsp;<a href="mailto:Amanda.Bailey@VisitMyrtleBeach.com">Amanda Bailey</a>, business development coordinator, 843-916-7205.</p>

<hr />
<p><a href="https://web.myrtlebeachareachamber.com/Restaurant-Mexican/5-de-Mayo-Restaurant-30718" target="_blank"><strong>5 de Mayo Restaurant</strong></a><br />
<em>Restaurant - Mexican</em><br />
Evelyn Gonzalez<br />
603 S. Kings Hwy.<br />
Myrtle Beach, SC 29577<br />
843-803-9933</p>

<p><a href="https://web.myrtlebeachareachamber.com/MortgageLenders/Academy-Mortgage-Corporation-30572" target="_blank"><strong>Academy Mortgage Corporation</strong></a><br />
<em>Mortgage-Lenders</em><br />
Connor Beckman<br />
9261 SC-707, Ste. J<br />
Myrtle Beach, SC 29588<br />
843-467-6962</p>

<p><a href="https://web.myrtlebeachareachamber.com/Window-Treatments/Bumble-Bee-Blinds-of-Myrtle-Beach-30549" target="_blank"><strong>Bumble Bee Blinds of Myrtle Beach</strong></a><br />
<em>Window Treatments</em><br />
Tony Farah<br />
Myrtle Beach, SC 29577<br />
843-892-1024</p>

<p><a href="https://web.myrtlebeachareachamber.com/Nonprofit/Carolina-Adaptive-Golf-30554" target="_blank"><strong>Carolina Adaptive Golf</strong></a><br />
<em>Nonprofit</em><br />
Brandon Worley<br />
Greenville, SC 29617<br />
864-448-4997</p>

<p><a href="https://web.myrtlebeachareachamber.com/Real-Estate/Celia-A-Klein,-REALTOR-30582" target="_blank"><strong>Celia A. Klein, REALTOR</strong></a><br />
<em>Real Estate</em><br />
Celia Klein<br />
1136 44th Ave. N., Ste. 2<br />
Myrtle Beach, SC 29577<br />
843-321-9646</p>

<p><a href="https://web.myrtlebeachareachamber.com/Self-Storage/Centro-Storage-30546" target="_blank"><strong>Centro Storage</strong></a><br />
<em>Self Storage</em><br />
Melissa Holcomb<br />
103 Sapwood Rd.<br />
Myrtle Beach, SC 29579<br />
843-890-0225</p>

<p><a href="https://web.myrtlebeachareachamber.com/Restaurant-Italian/Ciao-Italian-Restaurant-30603" target="_blank"><strong>Ciao Italian Restaurant</strong></a><br />
<em>Restaurant - Italian</em><br />
Claudia Hysa<br />
5223 N. Kings Hwy.<br />
Myrtle Beach, SC 29577<br />
843-283-3083</p>

<p><a href="https://web.myrtlebeachareachamber.com/BusinessHome-Services/Coastal-Cans-30595" target="_blank"><strong>Coastal Cans</strong></a><br />
<em>Business/Home Services</em><br />
Joseph Sigler<br />
Myrtle Beach, SC 29579<br />
843-467-7777</p>

<p><a href="https://web.myrtlebeachareachamber.com/Lawn-Care/Coastal-Turf-LLC-30571" target="_blank"><strong>Coastal Turf LLC</strong></a><br />
<em>Lawn Care</em><br />
Ross Settle<br />
3100 Dick Pond Rd., Ste. E<br />
Myrtle Beach, SC 29588<br />
843-200-9713</p>

<p><a href="https://web.myrtlebeachareachamber.com/Optometrists/Coastal-Vision-Center-30555" target="_blank"><strong>Coastal Vision Center</strong></a><br />
<em>Optometrists</em><br />
Nicole Fallone<br />
1651 Glenns Bay Rd.<br />
Surfside Beach, SC 29575<br />
843-650-2400</p>

<p><a href="https://web.myrtlebeachareachamber.com/Restaurant-Bakery/Eight-Arms-Keto-Kitchen-30550" target="_blank"><strong>Eight Arms Keto Kitchen</strong></a><br />
<em>Restaurant - Bakery</em><br />
Melissa Burkhalter<br />
5001 N. Kings Hwy., Ste. 207<br />
Myrtle Beach, SC 29577<br />
864-434-9260</p>

<p><a href="https://web.myrtlebeachareachamber.com/Business-Support-Services/Global-Leisure-Management-30570" target="_blank"><strong>Global Leisure Management</strong></a><br />
<em>Business Support Services</em><br />
Alyse Kuhlman<br />
PO Box 510062<br />
Saint Louis, MO 63129<br />
314-258-2499</p>

<p><a href="https://web.myrtlebeachareachamber.com/Gutters/GPS-Gutter-Protection-Services-30690" target="_blank"><strong>GPS Gutter Protection Services</strong></a><br />
<em>Gutters</em><br />
Jerry Linsky<br />
Myrtle Beach, SC 29588<br />
843-999-4939</p>

<p><a href="https://web.myrtlebeachareachamber.com/Legal-Services/Green-Legal-Nurse-Consulting,-LLC-30583" target="_blank"><strong>Green Legal Nurse Consulting, LLC</strong></a><br />
<em>Legal Services</em><br />
Kelly Bickett<br />
Myrtle Beach, SC 29579<br />
843-957-7009</p>

<p><a href="https://web.myrtlebeachareachamber.com/Consultants/GRN-Piedmont-30717" target="_blank"><strong>GRN Piedmont</strong></a><br />
<em>Consultants</em><br />
Harvey Eden<br />
3691 Palmetto Pointe Blvd., Ste. 302<br />
Myrtle Beach, SC 29588<br />
704-601-7798</p>

<p><a href="https://web.myrtlebeachareachamber.com/Apartments/Hawthorne-At-The-Mill-30545" target="_blank"><strong>Hawthorne At The Mill</strong></a><br />
<em>Apartments</em><br />
Kelsy Ryan<br />
208 Windfall Way<br />
Myrtle Beach, SC 29579<br />
843-240-5987</p>

<p><a href="https://web.myrtlebeachareachamber.com/Restaurant-Seafood/Hot-Fish-Club-2939" target="_blank"><strong>Hot Fish Club</strong></a><br />
<em>Restaurant - Seafood</em><br />
Phillip Bates<br />
4911 Hwy. 17 Business<br />
Murrells Inlet, SC 29576<br />
843-357-9175</p>

<p><a href="https://web.myrtlebeachareachamber.com/FinancialServices/Hyams-Financial,-Inc-30566" target="_blank"><strong>Hyams Financial, Inc.</strong></a><br />
<em>Financial-Services</em><br />
Larry Hyams<br />
4763 Hwy. 17 Byp. S.<br />
Myrtle Beach, SC 29577<br />
843-333-0399</p>

<p><a href="https://web.myrtlebeachareachamber.com/HealthClubs/ISI-Elite-Training-Conway-30753" target="_blank"><strong>ISI Elite Training: Conway</strong></a><br />
<em>Health-Clubs</em><br />
Haywood Brandon<br />
1315 4th Ave.<br />
Conway, SC 29526<br />
843-910-6374</p>

<p><a href="https://web.myrtlebeachareachamber.com/HealthClubs/ISI-Elite-Training-Garden-City-30748" target="_blank"><strong>ISI Elite Training: Garden City</strong></a><br />
<em>Health-Clubs</em><br />
Haywood Brandon<br />
2737 Hwy. 17 Business<br />
Garden City, SC 29576<br />
843-910-6372</p>

<p><a href="https://web.myrtlebeachareachamber.com/Fitness/ISI-Elite-Training-Myrtle-Beach-30447" target="_blank"><strong>ISI Elite Training: Myrtle Beach</strong></a><br />
<em>Fitness</em><br />
Haywood Brandon<br />
4007 Belle Terre Blvd.<br />
Myrtle Beach, SC 29579<br />
843-333-7342</p>

<p><a href="https://web.myrtlebeachareachamber.com/HealthClubs/ISI-Elite-Training-North-Myrtle-Beach-30755" target="_blank"><strong>ISI Elite Training: North Myrtle Beach</strong></a><br />
<em>Health-Clubs</em><br />
Haywood Brandon<br />
3608 Hwy. 17 S.<br />
North Myrtle Beach, SC 29582<br />
843-663-0600</p>

<p><a href="https://web.myrtlebeachareachamber.com/Restaurant-Coffee-Bar/Knowledge-Perk-Coffee-Company-30604" target="_blank"><strong>Knowledge Perk Coffee Company</strong></a><br />
<em>Restaurant - Coffee Bar</em><br />
Tammy Wells<br />
4036 River Oaks Dr., Ste. 5<br />
Myrtle Beach, SC 29579<br />
843-236-9333</p>

<p><a href="https://web.myrtlebeachareachamber.com/SpeakersKeynoteSeminarsConsultants/Learning-Point-Group-30579" target="_blank"><strong>Learning Point Group</strong></a><br />
<em>Speakers-Keynote/Seminars/Consultants</em><br />
Julia Weaver<br />
Myrtle Beach, SC 29572<br />
336-207-2197</p>

<p><a href="https://web.myrtlebeachareachamber.com/Restaurant/Liberty-Tap-Room-Grill-14565" target="_blank"><strong>Liberty Tap Room &amp; Grill</strong></a><br />
<em>Restaurant</em><br />
Marissa Carrison<br />
7651 N. Kings Hwy.<br />
Myrtle Beach, SC 29572<br />
843-839-4677</p>

<p><a href="https://web.myrtlebeachareachamber.com/CoachingBusinessPersonal/Mark-Burlinson-Communication-Coaching-21481" target="_blank"><strong>Mark Burlinson Communication Coaching</strong></a><br />
<em>Coaching-Business/Personal</em><br />
Mark Burlinson<br />
Conway, SC 29526<br />
843-246-0094</p>

<p><a href="https://web.myrtlebeachareachamber.com/HealthClubs/Market-Common-Pilates-30734" target="_blank"><strong>Market Common Pilates</strong></a><br />
<em>Health-Clubs</em><br />
Ashleigh Dean<br />
981 Hackler St.<br />
Myrtle Beach, SC 29577<br />
843-222-7292</p>

<p><a href="https://web.myrtlebeachareachamber.com/CoachingBusinessPersonal/Martine-Wiliams-Coaching-30541" target="_blank"><strong>Martine Wiliams Coaching</strong></a><br />
<em>Coaching-Business/Personal</em><br />
Martine Williams<br />
Murrells Inlet, SC 29576<br />
843-602-1924</p>

<p><a href="https://web.myrtlebeachareachamber.com/Cosmetics/Mary-Kay-Cosmetics-Annette-Groff-30548" target="_blank"><strong>Mary Kay Cosmetics - Annette Groff</strong></a><br />
<em>Cosmetics</em><br />
Annette Groff<br />
Conway, SC 29526<br />
843-855-5926</p>

<p><a href="https://web.myrtlebeachareachamber.com/Fitness/NXT-LVL-FIT-30602" target="_blank"><strong>NXT LVL FIT</strong></a><br />
<em>Fitness</em><br />
Santuan Stanley<br />
3552 Northgate Dr.<br />
Myrtle Beach, SC 29588<br />
843-267-3561</p>

<p><a href="https://web.myrtlebeachareachamber.com/Air-Conditioning-Heating/Ocean-Air-Cooling,-LLC-30591" target="_blank"><strong>Ocean Air Cooling, LLC</strong></a><br />
<em>Air Conditioning &amp; Heating</em><br />
Christopher Shrader<br />
525 Snapdragon Ct.<br />
Myrtle Beach, SC 29579<br />
843-283-9995</p>

<p><a href="https://web.myrtlebeachareachamber.com/Optometrists/Pawleys-Eye-Associates-30561" target="_blank"><strong>Pawleys Eye Associates</strong></a><br />
<em>Optometrists</em><br />
Nicole Fallone<br />
10805 Ocean Hwy.<br />
Pawleys Island, SC 29585<br />
843-979-2400</p>

<p><a href="https://web.myrtlebeachareachamber.com/HealthHome-CareStaffService/Peace-Of-Mind-Senior-Care-30575" target="_blank"><strong>Peace Of Mind Senior Care</strong></a><br />
<em>Health-Home Care/Staff/Service</em><br />
Donna Johnson<br />
Myrtle Beach, SC 29588<br />
215-896-5840</p>

<p><a href="https://web.myrtlebeachareachamber.com/EventDecorators/Pick-A-Party-by-Rise-N-Shine-30581" target="_blank"><strong>Pick A Party by Rise N Shine</strong></a><br />
<em>Event-Decorators</em><br />
Rachel Mendolia<br />
3001 N. Kings Hwy., Ste. D175<br />
Myrtle Beach, SC 29577<br />
843-580-1611</p>

<p><a href="https://web.myrtlebeachareachamber.com/Air-Conditioning-Heating/Piedmont-Service-Group-30706" target="_blank"><strong>Piedmont Service Group</strong></a><br />
<em>Air Conditioning &amp; Heating</em><br />
Bryan Oliphant<br />
1600 Dividend Blvd.<br />
Myrtle Beach, SC 29577<br />
843-897-0089</p>

<p><a href="https://web.myrtlebeachareachamber.com/Restaurant-Pizza/Pittsburgh-Pizza-Pub-30696" target="_blank"><strong>Pittsburgh Pizza Pub</strong></a><br />
<em>Restaurant - Pizza</em><br />
Adam Lucas<br />
730 Hwy. 17 S.<br />
North Myrtle Beach, SC 29582<br />
843-353-4444</p>

<p><a href="https://web.myrtlebeachareachamber.com/Amusements-Attractions/Redline-Simcade-LLC-30540" target="_blank"><strong>Redline Simcade LLC</strong></a><br />
<em>Amusements &amp; Attractions</em><br />
Maureen McGrath<br />
Surfside Beach, SC 29575<br />
484-201-6622</p>

<p><a href="https://web.myrtlebeachareachamber.com/Nonprofit/Saltwater-Chamber-Orchestra-30453" target="_blank"><strong>Saltwater Chamber Orchestra</strong></a><br />
<em>Nonprofit</em><br />
Pamela Cuthbertson Dunn<br />
Georgetown, SC 29440<br />
843-240-0400</p>

<p><a href="https://web.myrtlebeachareachamber.com/Fitness/Shanti-Yoga-Studio-30609" target="_blank"><strong>Shanti Yoga Studio</strong></a><br />
<em>Fitness</em><br />
Sissy Castillo<br />
5103 N. Kings Hwy.<br />
Myrtle Beach, SC 29577<br />
843-503-4697</p>

<p><a href="https://web.myrtlebeachareachamber.com/Painter/Sherwin-Williams-Surfside-Beach-30590" target="_blank"><strong>Sherwin Williams - Surfside Beach</strong></a><br />
<em>Painter</em><br />
Courtney Cox<br />
122 Loyola Dr.<br />
Myrtle Beach, SC 29588<br />
843-748-6034</p>

<p><a href="https://web.myrtlebeachareachamber.com/Events-Promotions/Stunning-and-Brilliant-Events-30600" target="_blank"><strong>Stunning and Brilliant Events</strong></a><br />
<em>Events - Promotions</em><br />
Sara McCall<br />
1411 17th Ave. S., Unit 4<br />
Myrtle Beach, SC 29577<br />
704-308-6779</p>

<p><a href="https://web.myrtlebeachareachamber.com/Restaurant-Fine-Dining/The-Brentwood-Restaurant-Wine-Bistro-11009" target="_blank"><strong>The Brentwood Restaurant &amp; Wine Bistro</strong></a><br />
<em>Restaurant - Fine Dining</em><br />
Makayla Cox<br />
4269 Luck Ave.<br />
Little River, SC 29566<br />
843-249-2601</p>

<p><a href="https://web.myrtlebeachareachamber.com/Apartments/The-Veranda-30711" target="_blank"><strong>The Veranda</strong></a><br />
<em>Apartments</em><br />
Brittney Estes<br />
2501 Hammock St.<br />
Myrtle Beach, SC 29577<br />
843-839-2800</p>

<p><a href="https://web.myrtlebeachareachamber.com/BoatRentals/Tiki-Tours-of-Myrtle-Beach-30553" target="_blank"><strong>Tiki Tours of Myrtle Beach</strong></a><br />
<em>Boat-Rentals</em><br />
Sam Pannier<br />
5843 Dick Pond Rd.<br />
Myrtle Beach, SC 29588<br />
843-746-9007</p>

<p><a href="https://web.myrtlebeachareachamber.com/Vacation-Rentals-Beach-Homes-/Tilghman-Beach-Golf-Resort,-LLC-6688" target="_blank"><strong>Tilghman Beach &amp; Golf Resort, LLC</strong></a><br />
<em>Vacation Rentals &amp; Beach Homes</em><br />
Mike Deaton<br />
1819 N. Ocean Blvd.<br />
North Myrtle Beach, SC 29582<br />
843-280-0913</p>

<p><a href="https://web.myrtlebeachareachamber.com/MedicalServices/TyeMed-LLC-30598" target="_blank"><strong>Tye-Med LLC</strong></a><br />
<em>Medical-Services</em><br />
Tye Larimer<br />
Dunwoody, GA 30338<br />
803-971-3845</p>

<p><a href="https://web.myrtlebeachareachamber.com/MedicalServices/Your-Health-30451" target="_blank"><strong>Your Health</strong></a><br />
<em>Medical-Services</em><br />
Monty Parker<br />
3650 Coalition Dr.<br />
Myrtle Beach, SC 29588<br />
843-448-2228</p>
]]></content>
    <teaser_image_url><![CDATA[https://www.myrtlebeachareachamber.com/img/cache/blog/BlogPosts/659/teaser_image/34836-590-394f-4d22ac6ad028bf35f2a8ff07772b1b94]]></teaser_image_url>
    <teaser_image_alt_text/>
    <categories><![CDATA[New Members]]></categories>
    <author/>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Tickets Now Available for 15th Annual Shuckin on the Strand Oyster Roast]]></title>
    <date><![CDATA[2024-01-25 14:00:00]]></date>
    <content><![CDATA[<p><img alt="Oyster Roast 2024" src="/img/cache/lib24watch/Lib24watchFiles/1867/lib24watch_file/0-291e661adb04d1d1b6ff5b57f85faf16" style="width: 300px; height: 250px; margin-left: 10px; margin-right: 10px; float: left;" />MYRTLE BEACH, S.C.&mdash;Tickets are now available for the much-anticipated 15<sup>th</sup>&nbsp;annual Shuckin&rsquo; on the Strand Oyster Roast to take place on Saturday, Feb. 24, 2024, from Noon to 4 p.m. at the Hot Fish Club at 4911 Highway 17 Business in Murrells Inlet, S.C.</p>

<p>Hosted by Grand Strand Young Professionals (GSYP) and sponsored by Grand Strand Health, the roast is a charitable fundraiser for Substitutes for Santa, which provides 150 Horry County students with holiday gifts and festive entertainment in December.</p>

<p>&ldquo;Shuckin&rsquo; on the Strand is a very popular event for Grand Stranders and visitors alike. The food and music are exceptional, yet the true essence lies in the fact that all proceeds go toward our annual charity to support local students,&rdquo; said Isabella Cenatiempo, GSYP liaison for the Myrtle Beach Area Chamber of Commerce.</p>

<p>A limited number of tickets are currently on sale for $40, which includes admission, all-you-can-eat oysters, one plate of chicken bog&nbsp;and fixings, and two&nbsp;beers. Options are available to add a commemorative oyster shucker for $5, and to purchase tickets for children or chicken bog-only for $10.</p>

<p>Learn more and purchase tickets at&nbsp;<a data-auth="Verified" data-linkindex="1" href="https://nam12.safelinks.protection.outlook.com/?url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.grandstrandyoungprofessionals.com%2F&amp;data=05%7C02%7Camanda.blomquist%40visitmyrtlebeach.com%7C41f4a87cd84b4134c3a008dc1d26f6cd%7C81d417a4e3dd45fc965205e902b9d96e%7C0%7C0%7C638417300647687702%7CUnknown%7CTWFpbGZsb3d8eyJWIjoiMC4wLjAwMDAiLCJQIjoiV2luMzIiLCJBTiI6Ik1haWwiLCJXVCI6Mn0%3D%7C3000%7C%7C%7C&amp;sdata=a9tHu07v9m1S7%2B2Bu8L1NL4bX0oMAKsjizsFbozB6pk%3D&amp;reserved=0" originalsrc="http://www.grandstrandyoungprofessionals.com/" shash="RnC0ujFBKW8OqRJes2hSvyk2ELRjt6JhJSpKc9On5pKmO0F20pGPWlqLfwgXKfsC6Es6udEs+uNLz5yU156vF2ceZtFI0qZP6WcGp5Owm7rd/HMKXj/BhwCE/qIWKYUO9toflX00VrIw2bLsmQ5ipdu9tN9tmv17KOBnXCm/wTI=" title="Original URL: http://www.grandstrandyoungprofessionals.com/. Click or tap if you trust this link.">GrandStrandYoungProfessionals.com</a>.</p>
]]></content>
    <teaser_image_url><![CDATA[https://www.myrtlebeachareachamber.com/img/cache/blog/BlogPosts/656/teaser_image/34836-590-394f-4d22ac6ad028bf35f2a8ff07772b1b94]]></teaser_image_url>
    <teaser_image_alt_text/>
    <categories><![CDATA[GSYP]]></categories>
    <author/>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Shannon Detzler Named 2024 Ann DeBock Leadership Award Winner]]></title>
    <date><![CDATA[2024-01-23 11:54:00]]></date>
    <content><![CDATA[<p><img alt="Shannon Detzler" src="/img/cache/lib24watch/Lib24watchFiles/1869/lib24watch_file/0-291e661adb04d1d1b6ff5b57f85faf16" style="width: 300px; height: 450px; margin-left: 10px; margin-right: 10px; float: left;" />Leadership Grand Strand (LGS) is pleased to announce Shannon Detzler, president and CEO of Horry-Georgetown Technical College Foundation, is the recipient of the 2024 Ann DeBock Leadership Award.</p>

<p>Each year, the recognition is given to an LGS graduate who exhibits outstanding leadership and service to their community.</p>

<p>&ldquo;While we had incredible nominees put forth for this award, Shannon truly stood out for the many contributions she has made to our community, including volunteering at events ranging from the United Way Day of Caring to the Myrtle Beach Area Heart Association Walk and Heart Ball to the March of Dimes walk and Star Chefs Auction,&rdquo; said LGS Executive Director Diana Greene.</p>

<p>Her contributions to the community also include serving on the board of Grand Strand Miracle Leagues, raising money for the Multiple Sclerosis Society and generating thousands of dollars for St. Jude Children&rsquo;s Research Hospital by organizing a fundraising event. She&rsquo;s instilling the same spirit of giving in her son, Camp, who at age three, raised more than $1,400 for St. Jude at a Trike-A-Thon event.</p>

<p>&ldquo;From a young age, I was raised with the value of helping others and inspiring those around me to do the same. I strongly believe in instilling this ethos in our children early on, fostering the growth of young leaders who not only grasp the importance of empathy but also harbor a genuine passion for the wellbeing of others,&rdquo; Detzler said.</p>

<p>Her service to the community has earned her several of the region&rsquo;s most prestigious accolades, including the Jefferson Award for Public Service, Volunteer of the Year by Myrtle Beach Area Chamber of Commerce, Volunteer of the Year finalist by The Sun News and Young Professional of the Year by Waccamaw Community Foundation.</p>

<p>The Ann DeBock Leadership Award was commissioned and started by LGS Class 19 in memory of Ann DeBock, the program&rsquo;s first executive director from 1979 to 1998. During the award ceremony to be held on Jan. 26, 2024, three finalists will also receive recognition: Jerome Randall, founder of the Randall Foundation; Kate Curran, executive director of Fresh Brewed Ministries; and Donald Hovis Jr., owner of Tides Eye Photography.</p>

<p>For more information on LGS, visit LeadershipGrandStrand.com.</p>
]]></content>
    <teaser_image_url><![CDATA[https://www.myrtlebeachareachamber.com/img/cache/blog/BlogPosts/651/teaser_image/34836-590-394f-4d22ac6ad028bf35f2a8ff07772b1b94]]></teaser_image_url>
    <teaser_image_alt_text><![CDATA[shannon detzler named 2024 lgs ann debock award winner]]></teaser_image_alt_text>
    <categories><![CDATA[LGS News]]></categories>
    <author><![CDATA[by Marlane White, Director of Communications]]></author>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Zavier Jones Joins Visit Myrtle Beach Group Sales Team as Experience Coordinator]]></title>
    <date><![CDATA[2024-01-19 12:59:00]]></date>
    <content><![CDATA[<p>MYRTLE BEACH, S.C.&mdash;The Myrtle Beach Area Chamber of Commerce (MBACC) and Convention and Visitors Bureau (CVB) is pleased to announce Zavier Jones has joined Visit Myrtle Beach&rsquo;s group sales team as the experience coordinator.</p>

<p><img alt="Zavier Jones" src="/img/cache/lib24watch/Lib24watchFiles/1863/lib24watch_file/0-291e661adb04d1d1b6ff5b57f85faf16" style="width: 250px; height: 267px; margin-left: 10px; margin-right: 10px; float: left;" />In his new role, Jones will collaborate with the group sales team to create unforgettable experiences for meeting and event planners during their destination and venue site inspections and familiarization (FAM) tours, as well as during their meetings or events held within the Myrtle Beach area.</p>

<p>&ldquo;As the group sales experience coordinator, Zavier will showcase the destination&rsquo;s unique selling points and customize offerings to meet the specific needs of the various groups who come here for events from large conventions and sports tournaments to weddings, golf outings and family reunions,&rdquo; said Bob Harris, Visit Myrtle Beach&rsquo;s executive vice president of group sales.</p>

<p>Jones brings valuable hospitality experience to the CVB team, having previously worked for Hiton Hotels and Resorts as a Sales Coordinator. He earned his bachelor&rsquo;s degree in public health from Coastal Carolina University (CCU) and is currently pursuing a master&rsquo;s in clinical psychology from Webster University with goals to defeat the stigma of mental health and athletes.</p>

<p>He has a passion for sharing his experiences as a college and high school football player with rising athletes and since 2010, has served as the Assistant League Commissioner for the S.C. Youth Flag Football Association.</p>
]]></content>
    <teaser_image_url><![CDATA[https://www.myrtlebeachareachamber.com/img/cache/blog/BlogPosts/657/teaser_image/34836-590-394f-4d22ac6ad028bf35f2a8ff07772b1b94]]></teaser_image_url>
    <teaser_image_alt_text/>
    <categories><![CDATA[MBACC News Release]]></categories>
    <author><![CDATA[by Marlane White, Director of Communications]]></author>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Empowering Diversity: Insights from the First-Ever DEI Forum & Small Business Expo]]></title>
    <date><![CDATA[2024-01-18 10:06:00]]></date>
    <content><![CDATA[<p><img alt="Three panelists face crowd inside the Horry Georgetown Technical College auditorium." src="/img/cache/lib24watch/Lib24watchFiles/1862/lib24watch_file/0-291e661adb04d1d1b6ff5b57f85faf16" style="width: 400px; height: 225px; margin: 5px 10px; float: left;" />Being open to tell stories of who you are to build rapport with others was one of the key messages shared at the first-ever Diversity, Equity and Inclusion (DEI) Forum and Small Business Expo, held on Jan. 16, 2024, at the Horry-Georgetown Technical College Business Conference Center in Myrtle Beach.</p>

<p>The event was hosted by the Carolina African American Heritage Foundation (CAAHF), the Myrtle Beach Area Chamber of Commerce (MBACC) and the City of Myrtle Beach and part of CAAHF&rsquo;s Grand Strand Freedom Week.</p>

<p>During the event, participants had the opportunity to hear from panelists Kelvin Waites, DEI director for the City of Myrtle Beach; Amanda Masterpaul, Lecturer, Women&rsquo;s and Gender Studies with Coastal Carolina University; and Les Echols, director of community &amp; minority enterprise with the Greater Florence (S.C.) Chamber of Commerce.</p>

<p>The panelist shared their insight about DEI initiatives and best practices, including these three tips shared in this cumulative overview:</p>

<ol>
<li>Take a look at who is on your leadership team. Diversity is not just about your staff, but also who is on your executive team. Examine the composition of your C-suite and those who hold influence over strategic direction over your organization. They should have the buy-in to understand DEI values and how it impacts your organization.<br />
&nbsp;</li>
<li>Go beyond the diversity statement to see everyday gains. DEI should be more than posting a diversity statement and instead be ingrained as an everyday practice in an organization. The advantages of fostering a diverse and inclusive workplace is not just a matter of compliance but is linked to improved organizational performance and innovation. It shows a commitment to fairness and social responsibility, which enhances employee morale and loyalty. And, daily DEI practices can help create a more adaptive and resilient organization that&rsquo;s better equipped to navigate challenges effectively.<br />
&nbsp;</li>
<li>Give yourself and others grace. Granting grace in a DEI environment is essential for fostering a positive and constructive atmosphere. Acknowledging that individuals may be at different stages of understanding or embracing DEI concepts promotes a learning culture. Offering grace allows room for open dialogue and education, facilitating a more inclusive environment where mistakes can be seen as opportunities for growth rather than punitive measures. It encourages empathy, understanding and collaboration, ultimately contributing to a workplace culture that values diversity and works towards inclusion.<br />
&nbsp;</li>
</ol>

<p>Along with the panelists, Angelique Jarvis-Simmons, bilingual business coach with the S.C. Hispanic Chamber (SCHC), spoke about the advantages Hispanic populations bring to the local business community, including how their cultural diversity enables businesses to cater to a broader range of consumer preferences. She also shared how the SCHC can provide assistance to this growing multicultural community.</p>

<p>Participants also had the opportunity to connect with more than a dozen exhibitors on hand, including South Carolina Association for Community Economic Development; SCORE Grand Strand, which offers free mentorship for entrepreneurs; SPARTA Networking, a leading DEI-focused consulting and staffing firm; Neighbor to Neighbor, a senior care provider; The Lovely Law Firm Injury Lawyers; and others.</p>
]]></content>
    <teaser_image_url><![CDATA[https://www.myrtlebeachareachamber.com/img/cache/blog/BlogPosts/655/teaser_image/34836-590-394f-4d22ac6ad028bf35f2a8ff07772b1b94]]></teaser_image_url>
    <teaser_image_alt_text><![CDATA[Three panelists face crowd inside the Horry Georgetown Technical College auditorium.]]></teaser_image_alt_text>
    <categories><![CDATA[News]]></categories>
    <author><![CDATA[by Marlane White, Director of Communications]]></author>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[MLK Day of Service Project Improves Hidden Gem in Myrtle Beach Neighborhood]]></title>
    <date><![CDATA[2024-01-17 13:09:00]]></date>
    <content><![CDATA[<p><img alt="Volunteers smile in front of Bathsheba Bowens Memorial Park Sign" src="/img/cache/lib24watch/Lib24watchFiles/1868/lib24watch_file/0-291e661adb04d1d1b6ff5b57f85faf16" style="width: 300px; height: 225px; margin-left: 10px; margin-right: 10px; float: left;" />More than 40 volunteers gathered on the Monday, Jan. 15, 2023, the Martin Luther King Jr. Holiday, to take part in a MLK Day of Service at Bathsheba Bowens Memorial Park located in Myrtle Beach&rsquo;s Harlem neighborhood.</p>

<p>Participants removed weeds, debris and litter, then landscaped the park&rsquo;s two entrances by laying mulch and planting flowers around the signs.</p>

<p>The service project was organized by Keep Myrtle Beach Beautiful (KMBB) with the support of the City of Myrtle Beach Parks Department, the Myrtle Beach Area Chamber of Commerce (MBACC) and the Carolina African American Heritage Foundation.</p>

<p>Yaritza Tinoco, MBACC Community Engagement Manager and KMBB Liaison, said it was a collaborative project that took a lot of hands to make happen, but in the end, it wasn&rsquo;t about who made it happen but the neighborhood who will benefit from the upgrades to the park.</p>

<p>&ldquo;We&rsquo;re grateful for everyone who participated in this project and donated their time and tools to make it happen. We know that these small improvements to the community can spread a bit a joy and help to make long-lasting impacts in our everyday lives,&rdquo; Tinoco said.</p>

<p>Keep Myrtle Beach Beautiful plans to return to the park next year to continue to make improvements.</p>
]]></content>
    <teaser_image_url><![CDATA[https://www.myrtlebeachareachamber.com/img/cache/blog/BlogPosts/658/teaser_image/34836-590-394f-4d22ac6ad028bf35f2a8ff07772b1b94]]></teaser_image_url>
    <teaser_image_alt_text><![CDATA[Volunteers smile in front of Junk King truck and Myrtle Beach park]]></teaser_image_alt_text>
    <categories><![CDATA[Keep Myrtle Beach Beautiful]]></categories>
    <author><![CDATA[by Marlane White, Director of Communications]]></author>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Ways to Help Local Nonprofits - January 2024]]></title>
    <date><![CDATA[2024-01-17 9:44:00]]></date>
    <content><![CDATA[<p>In an effort to support the many Grand Strand nonprofits on their missions to supporting the community, Myrtle Beach Area Chamber of Commerce is publishing this monthly roundup of our nonprofit members current needs.</p>

<p>If you&rsquo;re looking to get involved or give back, consider supporting the nonprofits below or in&nbsp;the chamber&rsquo;s&nbsp;<a href="https://web.myrtlebeachareachamber.com/Nonprofit" target="_blank">business directory.</a></p>

<hr />
<p>The <a href="https://web.myrtlebeachareachamber.com/Museums/Franklin-G-Burroughs-Simeon-B-Chapin-Art-Museum-925" target="_blank">Art Museum</a> is looking for volunteers to assist at their first Oysters and Art Festival on Saturday, Feb. 3. Volunteer responsibilities include meet and greet, checking tickets, handing out flatware and the like. Contact the Art Museum to learn more.</p>

<p><a href="https://web.myrtlebeachareachamber.com/Nonprofit/Meals-on-Wheels-of-Horry-County,-Inc-24320">Meals On Wheels</a> is <a href="https://mowhc.kindful.com/" target="_blank">collecting donations</a> for their building fund as they look for a new kitchen facility.</p>

<p>Blood supplies are at critical lows across the country. Consider donating blood with the <a href="https://www.redcrossblood.org/give.html/drive-results?order=DATE&amp;range=10&amp;zipSponsor=29577" target="_blank">American Red Cross</a> or <a href="https://thebloodconnection.org/myrtlebeach/">The Blood Connection</a>. The chamber has partnered with the Blood Connection to sponsor a blood drive on Feb. 13 from 9 a.m. to 5 p.m. at 1217 38<sup>th</sup>&nbsp;Ave. N. You can save time in line by <a href="https://donate.thebloodconnection.org/donor/schedules/drive_schedule/229219" target="_blank">making an appointment</a>.</p>

<p>The <a href="https://web.myrtlebeachareachamber.com/Nonprofit/ALZ-FOUNDATION-27503">ALZ Foundation</a> is seeking grant writing assistance. They also have event sponsorships available and are always accepting donations for their Carol&rsquo;s Closet program.</p>

<hr />
<p><a href="https://web.myrtlebeachareachamber.com/events?ce=true" target="_blank">VIEW NONPROFIT &amp; COMMUNITY EVENTS</a></p>

<p>Want to be on this list? <a href="https://www.myrtlebeachareachamber.com/nonprofit-organizations">Learn</a> how nonprofits can share their current needs.</p>
]]></content>
    <teaser_image_url><![CDATA[https://www.myrtlebeachareachamber.com/img/cache/blog/BlogPosts/654/teaser_image/34836-590-394f-4d22ac6ad028bf35f2a8ff07772b1b94]]></teaser_image_url>
    <teaser_image_alt_text><![CDATA[Ways to help myrtle beach nonprofits]]></teaser_image_alt_text>
    <categories><![CDATA[News]]></categories>
    <author/>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[2024 South Carolina Hall of Fame Induction ceremony to take place Jan. 22 in Myrtle Beach]]></title>
    <date><![CDATA[2024-01-10 13:06:00]]></date>
    <content><![CDATA[<h2>Renowned Naturalist Rudy Mancke and Boxing Legend Smokin&rsquo; Joe Frazier Among 2024 South Carolina Hall of Fame Inductees Induction ceremony to take place Jan. 22 in Myrtle Beach</h2>

<p>MYRTLE BEACH, S.C.&mdash;The South Carolina Hall of Fame Board of Trustees are pleased to announce the 2024 inductees: boxing legend Smokin&rsquo; Joe Frazier, naturalist Rudy Mancke and Francis Salvador. Each of the South Carolina natives will be inducted into the South Carolina Hall of Fame during a ceremony on Monday, Jan. 22, 2024, at 10 a.m. at the Myrtle Beach Convention Center, 2101 N. Oak St. The event is free and open to the public.</p>

<p>&ldquo;The 2024 inductees have made valuable contributions that embody the distinctive spirit of South Carolina. The achievements of Joe Frazier, Rudy Mancke and Francis Salvador have each shaped our state&rsquo;s cultural tapestry, inspiring generations to come,&rdquo; said Randal Wallace, chairman of the Official South Carolina Hall of Fame. &ldquo;We&rsquo;re pleased to induct each of these individuals into the South Carolina Hall of Fame.&rdquo;</p>

<p>Rudy Mancke: Renowned American naturalist and broadcaster Rudy Mancke (April 17, 1941 &ndash; Nov. 7, 2023) was born in Spartanburg, S.C., and is most widely recognized for hosting nature-focused programs such on South Carolina Educational Television &ldquo;NatureScene,&rdquo; which was filmed from 1978 to 2002. His contributions to environmental education and conservation of the region&rsquo;s diverse ecosystems, included founding the South Carolina Association of Naturalists, an organization that continues to thrive, and serving as the Naturalist in Residence at the School of Earth, Ocean and Environment at the University of South Carolina.</p>

<p>Smokin&rsquo; Joe Frazier: Born in Beaufort, S.C., Joseph William Frazier (Jan. 12, 1944 - Nov. 7, 2011) was a legendary American professional boxer who rose to prominence in the 1960s and &lsquo;70s and was nicknamed &ldquo;Smokin&rsquo; Joe&rdquo; for his relentless pressure in the boxing ring. Frazier became the undisputed heavyweight champion of the world in 1970 and is best known for his fierce rivalry with Muhammad Ali, including the iconic &ldquo;Fight of the Century&rdquo; against Ali in 1971 and the &ldquo;The Thrilla in Manila&rdquo; in 1975. Frazier was inducted into the South Carolina Athletic Hall of Fame in 1974 and the Boxing Hall of Fame in 1980.</p>

<p>Francis Salvador: Born in 1747, Francis Salvador was a notable figure in American history as the first person of Jewish faith to be elected to public office in the American colonies. A resident of South Carolina, Salvador played a crucial role in advocating for American independence and represented Ninety-Six District in the Provincial Congress of South Carolina. Tragically, his life was cut short during the American Revolutionary War when he became the first Jewish person to die in combat for the cause of American independence, losing his life in a skirmish with Loyalist forces in 1776. A plaque was dedicated in Salvador&rsquo;s memory in 1950 in Charleston&rsquo;s City Hall Park.</p>
]]></content>
    <teaser_image_url><![CDATA[https://www.myrtlebeachareachamber.com/img/cache/blog/BlogPosts/653/teaser_image/34836-590-394f-4d22ac6ad028bf35f2a8ff07772b1b94]]></teaser_image_url>
    <teaser_image_alt_text><![CDATA[SC Hall of Fame]]></teaser_image_alt_text>
    <categories><![CDATA[MBACC News Release]]></categories>
    <author><![CDATA[by Marlane White, Director of Communications]]></author>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Horry County Combining Precinct Locations for February Primaries]]></title>
    <date><![CDATA[2024-01-02 8:57:00]]></date>
    <content><![CDATA[<p>Horry County will be combining some precinct locations for the February 2024 Presidential Preference Primaries.</p>

<p>The move is temporary and primary locations will return to normal locations for the June 2024 primaries. The Democratic Presidential Preference Primary is Feb. 3 and the Republican Presidential Preference Primary is Feb. 24. Polls are open from 7 a.m. to 7 p.m. for both.</p>

<p>View <a href="https://horrycountysc.gov/media/arxpeeh5/ppp-combined.pdf" target="_blank">a list of the combined precincts</a> to find your polling location.</p>

<p>Voter registration deadlines are coming up fast for the February primaries. Any eligible South Carolina resident must register to vote at least 30 days before an election to vote in that election. The state does not require anyone to register to vote with a specific party, however you may only vote in one of the primaries.</p>

<h3>Important Dates</h3>

<p>Voter Registration Deadlines<br />
Democratic Party Presidential Preference Primary: Thursday, Jan. 4<br />
Republican Party Presidential Preference Primary: Thursday, Jan. 25</p>

<h3>Early Voting</h3>

<p>Early voting is available in three locations for two weeks immediately before each election.</p>

<p>Democratic Party Presidential Preference Primary: Monday, Jan. 22-Friday, Feb. 2 8:30 a.m.-6 p.m. (except Jan. 28)</p>

<p>Republican Party Presidential Preference Primary: Monday, Feb. 12-Friday, Feb. 23 8:30 a.m.-6 p.m. (except Feb.18-19).</p>

<p>You may vote at the Horry County Voter Registration Office at 1515 4th Ave. in Conway, the South Strand Recreation Center at 9650 Scipio Ln. in Myrtle Beach or the North Strand Recreation Center at 120 Hwy. 57 S. in Little River.</p>

<p>Not sure if you&rsquo;re registered? Visit <a href="https://scvotes.gov/voters/register-to-vote/" target="_blank">scvotes.gov</a> to check your voter registration.</p>
]]></content>
    <teaser_image_url><![CDATA[https://www.myrtlebeachareachamber.com/img/cache/blog/BlogPosts/636/teaser_image/34836-590-394f-4d22ac6ad028bf35f2a8ff07772b1b94]]></teaser_image_url>
    <teaser_image_alt_text><![CDATA[Horry County Combining Precinct Locations for February Primaries]]></teaser_image_alt_text>
    <categories><![CDATA[News]]></categories>
    <author><![CDATA[by Amanda Blomquist, Business Development Marketing Manager]]></author>
  </item>
</wpiedata>
